<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix S9300 Point &amp; Shoot Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Black,Silver</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">3.368</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 17,950</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/2000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">4.5 - 81.0 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 25 - 450 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">18x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">215 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">108.7 (W) x 62.3 (H) x 30.6 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc. less</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">Wide Viewing Angle TFT LCD Monitor with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Aspect Ratio">4:3, 16:9</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Microphone">Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Camera Strap, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL12 (with Terminal Cover), Charging AC Adapter EH-69P, USB Cable UC-E6, Audio Video Cable EG-CP16, ViewNX 2 Installer CD, Reference Manual CD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point &amp; Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">S9300</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Auto, On, Off, Red-eye, Slow-sync</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Range">0.5 - 5.1 m (W), 1.5 - 3.0 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F3.5 - F5.9</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 6.9 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">Auto, 125, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200 (Auto gain from ISO 125 - 1600), Fixed Range Auto (ISO 125 - 400, 125 - 800)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Portrait, Close-up, Landscape, Food, Sports, Museum, Night Portrait, Fireworks Show, Party / Indoor, Black and White Copy, Beach, Easy Panorama, Snow, Pet Portrait, Sunset, 3D Photography, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Backlighting), Smart Portrait, Continuous Shooting, Special Effects</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Picture Angle">25 mm Wde-angle to 450 mm Super-telephoto Coverage</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto, Cloudy, Daylight, Flash, Fluorescent, Incandescent, Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">Yes, 4 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="HDMI">HDMI Mini Connector (Type C)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">256-segment Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot, Multi, Spot AF Area</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">29</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4608 x 3456 (16 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Portrait, Close-up, Landscape, Food, Sports, Museum, Night Portrait, Fireworks Show, Party / Indoor, Black and White Copy, Beach, Easy Panorama, Snow, Pet Portrait, Sunset, 3D Photography, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Backlighting), Smart Portrait, Continuous Shooting, Special Effects</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG (3D), EXIF 2.3, DCF, DPOF, MPF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">WAV, AAC Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">MOV, H.264, MPEG-4 AVC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Power Supply">AC Adapter EH-69P</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">26 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/x/2/h/nikon-coolpix-s9300-point-shoot-400x400-imad72u4h3jduvfp.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/x/2/h/nikon-coolpix-s9300-point-shoot-400x400-imad72u4znzugtew.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/x/2/h/nikon-coolpix-s9300-point-shoot-400x400-imad72u4xuz3gdcz.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/x/2/h/nikon-coolpix-s9300-point-shoot-400x400-imad72u4vnykbhqy.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/x/2/h/nikon-coolpix-s9300-point-shoot-400x400-imad72u5jubuzdkm.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/x/2/h/nikon-coolpix-s9300-point-shoot-400x400-imad72u5nfkxfrgb.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/x/2/h/nikon-coolpix-s9300-point-shoot-400x400-imad72u5nydn3gnp.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Vijay Govind</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jun 16, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Just Not worth it and a Let down of Cosmic propotions!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I bought this camera under the assumption that this being nikon there should have been some quality to the product. Well, I was terribly let down. I am not a professional, but I have owned 6 digital cameras to date and I feel that this one is the lowest performing till now. I have listed the problems for everyone to actually see. I don't see any reason how people can give a high rating for this (I would have given zero stars if there was such an option) - 1) The images are extremely blurred and edges seems "fuzzy" and out of focus. I tried several shots in different range &amp; lighting as well as with and without flash (No "sharp images"). The conclusion is the same, the image quality is very bad. 2) The advertised macro range is 4cm, but all I could get in the range 4 - 10cm were blurry images, with or without flash. I tried in many lighting and the effect is almost the same. I am not able to lock focus at 4 cm. To be honest, I got better macro performance with my cell phone camera.3) Nikon claims and Flipkart also has put this on the product description - "The EXPEED C2 image processor boosts shooting speed to unimaginable new levels, recording images and movies with maximum image quality" - Well, not only are the images blurry and out of focus, the image recording happens at an unacceptable speed of around 4-5 seconds per image on a class 4 SD card. Now, I could record high quality 14.1 Mpx JPEG images in less than 2 seconds on a Class 4 card.4) The vibration reduction was also a big let down for me, as I have not been able to capture a image without a distortion when I turn of the flash. There is always a shadow at the edges for the images, except when I use tripod. I didn't buy a point and shoot to use with a tripod; I want to use it when I am on the go. 5) The GPS is okay, if you have clear sky and obviously if you are outside, but that is generally how GPS works. You cannot expect anything more.It is very clear that manufacturers intended the product to be whatever they had written in the product description, but when it was finally manufactured, it failed to meet the product description.I have sent the images and the details to flipkart and I have requested for a refund for this product. I didn't do the right research when I brought this product and now I regret having spend 18k odd for a product that is way below average for a super zoom point and shoot and bad when it comes to nikon. I request people to do a proper research and look at the sample images from review sites before buying this and the version without GPS. </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Sunil Reddy</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Aug 24, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Very poor battery performance</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">My battery doesn't even last for 100 shots per recharge. The temperature of camera becomes extremely high while recording and it stops recording until it cools down.Here is the response from Nikon when I asked for battery replacement:Thank you very much for writing to us. In reference to your query, we like to inform you that during the camera operations, normal heating may happen and the same is mentioned in product manual.Also, we like to inform you that accessories are not considered under warranty, therefore warranty of the same is not possible. We would be delighted to assist you in case of any further query.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Kamalesh Maurya</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 30, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nikon Coolpix S9300, Very bad eperiance with very poor product</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">    I purchaged Nikon S9300 last months, I am very unhappy with this camera.I purchased this expensive camera thinking to keep it for a long time but after purchasethis product I disappointed very much.    I purchaged not from Flipkart but from "Capital Digi World, Pacific Mall". They are also very bad seller, they suggest S9300 with a lot of goodness but all was wrong. Don't go there they will confuse you and sell his unmoved product. Before selling they will promise you a lot but after that who are you.    About pic quility it is very bad, it get burred and unfocussed even you tried to focus a lot.    Low light picture are also always shadow beside the pic.    You can not take pic in night depeding on Flash from more than 1.5 Mtr.    If you want little bit good pic you have to keep the camera unvibrated, a small vibration will give very bad pic over all Vibration reduction is also not work properly.    Flash popup if selected but have to keep it back by pressing it dowing by hand not automatically.    I have not seen anything which make me happy.    I will never suggest this product, if you realy want any good camera you must go to other brand like Canon.     Hope this will help you to choose a good product and you will not feel regrate.Have a happy shopping.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Harshit Gupta</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jun 19, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">gud camera but a little expensive</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Nikon Coolpix S9300 Point &amp; Shoot is a good camera to buyhas compass and GPS competes every other camera but is still a little expensive................................................................................................................................
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Anurag Patra</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 15, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Good One</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I had just ordered this Camera from flipkart a few days back.the Camera was a great one.......It comprises GPS navigation , wi fi, magnetic compass.......and many more features......The flipkart delivery was very fast.It just delivered my camera between 2 days of my ordering.But I was dissatisfied with the pouch that was provided with this camera.The camera was a bit bigger than the camera pouch.So, the camera does not fit in the pouch.......For that I had purchased a new camera bag from the nearest nikon shop.......But the overall performance of the camera was good</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Dilip P</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 30, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">The worst point &amp; shoot camera every made</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						For this price, this is probably the worst camera Nikon has every made. Images are blurry and fuzzy. They are always out of focus. The camera is too shaky. Be prepared to take your tripod along with you for all your vacations. Please do not buy this. Complete waste of money.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">nishant</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Apr 21, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">pathetic camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						This camera is useless. Don't waste your money on this camera. Image quality is bad and is a complete let down. Instead check out Samsung's WB250. Its an excellent camera with some cool wi-fi feature. My friend bought samsung wb250 and i am so jealous.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Gowtham</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Apr 1, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Its not a worthy camera, irritates you.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						It has a focusing problem, and you will get blurred images. takes too much time to focus and capture. Don't go for this camera. Handling is easy but it will not satisfy you zoom is good but picture quality is too bad.. and nobody will believe it is 1080p pics. 
				</specsKey>
</root>