<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix S1100PJ Point &amp; Shoot Camera (Silver)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Silver</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.3</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 10,556</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/1500 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">4 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">14.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR ED Glass Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast Detection</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">5.0-25.0mm / F3.9-5.8</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">5x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">155 g</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">100.8 (W) x 62.7 (H) x 24.1 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">1280 x 720p, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">TFT LCD Touchscreen Monitor</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">460,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB 2.0</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Camera, Camera Strap AN-CP17, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL12, Charging AC Adapter MH-65p, USB Cable UC-E6, Audio Video Cable EG-CP14, View NX 2 CD, Remote Control ML-L5, Stylus TP-1, User Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point &amp; Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">Coolpix S1100PJ</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Silver</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with red-eye reduction, Off, Fill flash, Slow sync</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Range">0.3 - 3.5 m (W), 0.5 - 2.5 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 0.9 fps up to 4 shots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">Auto (Auto gain ISO 80 - 800), Fixed Range Auto (ISO 80 to 200, ISO 80 to 400), Manual selection: ISO 80, 100, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200 (Pixel Addition), 6400 (Pixel Addition)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto, Preset manual, Daylight, Incandescent, Fluorescent, Cloudy, Flash</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto Mode, Scene mode, Scene Auto Selelctor, Smart portrait mode, Movie mode, Subject tracking mode</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">24</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">Spot metering (meters 3.5-mm circle centered on selected focus point)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Additional Features">Projector, Monitor Frame Coverage, PictBridge</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4320 x 3240 (14 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto Mode, Scene mode, Scene Auto Selelctor, Smart portrait mode, Movie mode, Subject tracking mode</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">WAV, AAC Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">mono/wav file, MOV movie</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Power Supply">One Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL12 (Supplied), AC Adapter EH-62F (Available Separately), Still pictures: 220 Shots, Movie: 1 Hr 35 min (HD 720p (1280 x 720)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">79 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/t/b/6/nikon-coolpix-s1100pj-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqfdtnrzh99.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/t/b/6/nikon-coolpix-s1100pj-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqpxg54k6hg.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/t/b/6/nikon-coolpix-s1100pj-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqexwyzrh2n.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/t/b/6/nikon-coolpix-s1100pj-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqjdx4yw47j.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/t/b/6/nikon-coolpix-s1100pj-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqpktya3twy.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Madhav Raj</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Mar 2, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Blindly Go For this!!!!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I have used this camera for four months and now its time to write a review about this camera.Camera Clarity: 10/10The camera clarity is simply awesome. I have used cannon 14 MP, Sony 14MP and this cam to take a same Landscape and this camera clarity is the best among all.Projector: 9/10The description failed to mention that if you use the projector for 30 minutes you must wait for the camera to cool for about 10 minutes before you can resume taking pictures so keep that in mind if you're at a party. Also the projector drinks the battery a lot.Touch sensitive: 7/10Nikon touch sensitive is not good as the sony. However the orientation is cool. The stylus helps me a lot to write a name or comment or to draw something in my favorite snaps in projector mode. It also gives an option to save the edited picture.Flash: 9/10This camera don't have an option to turn on the flash permanently. It just have an Auto flash mode and option to turn off the flash. So the problem is, the images are dull in dawn or lowlight area. However, the flash brightness and image clarity is cool in full dark places.Video Recording: 9/10The one touch video recording button is cool and even a 2 year old child can take videos. The Video resolution is good but not up to my expectation.  Others:  8/10The fisheye effect is not fisheye at all. It's Nikon's way of adding a strange effect (Non-Adjustable) on photos already taken and cannot be used when shooting 16 X 9 photos or with Video recording. It have a build-in stand to use the camera as projector. But the remote is not that much sensitive though it have IR sensors on both sides. The screen turns off if you use remote and go to sleep mode soon. It is very annoying when I wish to see my fav snaps.Though it have few drawbacks, you can blindly go for this since it is coolest camera compare to Sony or Cannon. Over all it is 9/10.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">shashank</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 17, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">mast hai camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						the camera of nikon with projecter is very good u should buy without thinking                                                                                                                                           
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">adi</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Sep 13, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">nice cam with projector..</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						a gud nd clear blur free images with diffrnt modes..
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Niaz Rahaman</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 12, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Very very good camera with great offer from FKT</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						First of all, the items provided with the camera and the offer price FKT provided is undoubtedly awesome.The camera- looks great and picture quality is also excellent. The one and only drawback I found so far (used it for 5-6 days till date) is its touch screen sensitivity, its not good.Blindly go for this &amp; of course from FKT only. 
				</specsKey>
</root>