<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix AW100 Point &amp; Shoot Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.042</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 13,904</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/1500 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">4 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR ED Glass lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast-detect TTL AF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">5.0 - 25.0 mm (35 mm format equivalent to 28 - 140 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">5x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">178 g</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">110.1 (W) x 64.9 (H) x 22.8 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body &amp; lens.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">TFT LCD Monitor with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">460,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB 2.0</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Camera Strap AN-CP23, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL12, Battery charger MH-65P, USB Cable UC-E6, Audio Video Cable EG-CP16, Filter adapter UR-E23, View NX 2 CD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point &amp; Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">Coolpix AW100</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with red-eye reduction, Off, Fill flash, Slow sync</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Range">0.3 - 3.5 m (W), 0.5 - 2.2 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F3.9 - F4.8</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 7.1 fps up to 3 shots (Continuous H), 1.4 fps up to 12 shots (Continuous L)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">Auto (auto gain from ISO 125 to 800), Fixed range auto (ISO 125 to 400), ISO 125, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto mode, Scene mode, Smart portrait, Easy auto mode, Movie mode</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto, Cloudy, Daylight, Flash, Fluorescent, Incandescent, Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">Yes, 1 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="HDMI">HDMI mini connector</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">256-Segment matrix, Center-weighted</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">29</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4608 x 3456 (16 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto mode, Scene mode, Smart portrait, Easy auto mode, Movie mode</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG, EXIF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">WAV, AAC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">MPEG-4 AVC/H.264</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Power Supply">AC Adapter EH-62F</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">83 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/m/b/m/nikon-aw100-point-shoot-400x400-imadfmvzm7vkfrts.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/y/e/w/nikon-coolpix-aw100-point-shoot-400x400-imadfmvzurbfpwpq.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/m/b/m/nikon-aw100-point-shoot-400x400-imadfmvzejmgnuvy.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/m/b/m/nikon-aw100-point-shoot-400x400-imadfmvzzpewnfxn.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/m/b/m/nikon-aw100-point-shoot-400x400-imadfmvpg8e2vb7p.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="subimg">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/m/b/m/nikon-aw100-point-shoot-400x400-imadfmvzm7vkfrts.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img_id">Nikon Coolpix AW100 Point &amp; Shoot Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Atul Madanpotra</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 25, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">WORST PRODUCT</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">Though i am not a technical person but as a lay man i can say it has one of the worst picture quality. here are my reviews in detail:I have recently bought AW100, i was searching the net for waterproof camera and came across your AW100. Now, i curse google for displaying your camera in search result. I have sony digital camera which has 8Mpx Carl Zeiss lens and it is way ahead in image and video quality then AW100. here are the issues i have with this product quality.1) All images i click without flash on are blurred.2) All image i click with flash on are extremely bright (it looks like some1 has painted it all white)3) Video has flashing black lines behind the object (its like old black and white television picture quality).I request NIKON (on their FB page) to discontinue this product  I was so excited to found a waterproof camera from a good company but i am now dissapointed badly and hope that with this post i can save other people from this EXTREMELY BAD PRODUCT. I dont want to rate this product because there is no option in flipkart to give it a negative rating but i have to otherwise i cant submit my review.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Sameer Chavan</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">2</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 6, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Good CMOS censor but bad software. Wrong picture lighting</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I brought this from Flipkart and very instant delivery. The camera has amazing COMS sensor quality and almost no red noise. But the problem lies in Software. Nikon as you know is very backward in software algorithms compared to sony. Most of the time the camera takes pictures with high flooded flash and pictures are white. Many time the Smart mode dont at all ignite the flash and it takes in very high ISO value. It results in camera shakes. Many times the software does not respond fast and it hangs. May be the processor is bad. It stuck in clicking zoom, or changing the mode.Sometime there is a white light reflection on the right side of photos. I think this is because of the gloosy square frame of that lense. The light is bouncing on the lense making some pictures white on right side. I wish they should have rubber/mat  finish lens hood. I tested this for underwater and it does record video. But most of indoor videos are too dark. If i compare my Samsung galaxy note 8mp camera doing a 1080 indoor video, its much better then Nikon video. Though this camera has good CMOS sensor and hardware design, i dont find it has good software to do right flash and picture composition. The GPS do work good. This is one good thing.I am waiting for firmware update. May be it will fix all issues.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">say2 snailhill</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Mar 18, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">impressive product</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						a good product ,specially for people who are sporty in nature.a very strong flash which sometimes proves to be a drawback..a very good water ,break proof product,natural ,live picture quality,good function.flash is the only weak point according to me..if u are planning to buy a ,this camera is the best package in such a low price tagsimply "A WORTH PRODUCT "
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Prashant Gandhi</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 16, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">For Teenagers ! Peace of mind !</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">This rough and tough product is designed for teens I guess ! I bought it for my 15 yrs. son. It's a birthday gift !While buying I naturally consider Nikon for its true picture quality. But my priority was to give my son a camera which suits his age. I was not looking for a great picture quality. My priority was a rough and tough product with a lot of new features in all weather conditions !My son did like it the most because he wanted something like this only. Now he can shoot HD pictures / videos on school trips, our family excursions, trekking with friends.. freely, at peace of mind, in all weather conditions and even underwater ! It has GPS ! Shake it if you are in snow without removing your gloves and you can do lot of things with your camera ! What's more ! Go for it guys !</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Sharad Subramanian</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 5, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nikon AW100 tension free camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Nice Product as it is shook proof and waterproof, So it can also be given to kids to play and with no tension that they it put it in water or play with it.Under water pics really come out good.It is not good when pictures are taken in Auto mode but good when taken in respective modes. its a good buy
</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Gomtesh Upadhye</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Aug 21, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Amazing HD quality in good light and underwater. </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">If you thought you could take great pictures, great videos in HD, great picture quality underwater and in the dark with the same camera, you were wrong. Each camera model (DSLRs included) are good at specific things so please choose and use appropriately else you will be ranting like these other reviewers. This camera is great for HD videos ONLY. You will be amazed at the HD picture quality this bad boy produces at this size. I have shot with this camera extensively under seas of India and Thailand and i have got amazing results. So if your requirements are HD videos in good light and underwater, this camera is for you. Else it definately is not. </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Subhrangshu Mandal</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jun 6, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nikon AW 100</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						This camera is not so bad as described by others. Its GPS function is excellent. Picture quality also good &amp; colour are realistic not like over burned colour. Its only problem is taking picture of any moving objects without flash are became blurred.... 
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">UNNIKRISHNAN PS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">2</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 3, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">16 MP and Underwatar!  Only that.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						The 16mp cmos censor and underwater mode is that make this camera worthy.  all other features we will get in other models with better performance.  The camera is sturdy and evan a laymans knowledge of operation will not help you take good photos with this.  Camera really looks good and sturdy but the pictures are not realistic in preview.  
				</specsKey>
</root>