<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix S2600 Point &amp; Shoot Camera (Silver)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Silver</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.515</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 5,534</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">14 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">4.6 - 23.0 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 26 - 130 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">5x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">121 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">93.8 (W) x 58.4 (H) x 19.5 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc. less</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">2.7 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Aspect Ratio">16:09</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL19 (with battery case), Camera, USB Cable UC-E6, ViewNX 2 Installer CD, Charging AC Adapter EH-69P, Audio Video Cable EG-CP14, Reference Manual CD, Camera Strap</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point &amp; Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">S2600</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Silver</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Range">0.5 - 4.5 m (W), 0.5 - 2.2 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F3.2 - F6.5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 0.9 fps up to 8 Frames</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">Auto ISO 80, 100, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200 (Auto Gain ISO 80 to 1600), Fixed Range Auto (ISO 80 to 400, 80 to 800)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Picture Angle">26 mm Wide-angle</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party, Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk, Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Smart Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">Yes, 10 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">26</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">256-segment Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4320 x 3240</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party, Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk, Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Smart Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG, DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">WAV</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">AVI (Motion-JPEG)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Power Supply">AC Adapter EH-69P</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">39 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/v/r/z/nikon-s2600-400x400-imad73spdngedaqr.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/x/s/a/nikon-s2600-400x400-imad73spgxsfhacw.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/v/r/z/nikon-s2600-400x400-imad73sps352e4kh.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/v/r/z/nikon-s2600-400x400-imad73spdgztnfsh.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="subimg">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/v/r/z/nikon-s2600-400x400-imad73spdngedaqr.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img_id">Nikon Coolpix S2600 Point &amp; Shoot Camera (Silver)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">K K</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">3</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 12, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">very Light and handy</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">First thanks for flipcart , they delivered in 3 days ( on diwali ) . but mentioned time was 6-7 days but got 4 days earlier ,good job. Now we have a good e-shopping guy in india.The camera is very light and small , you can keep it in pocket and wont feel that its heavy . The pic quality is ok , not so great indoor pics you need to be careful else it will get blur , out door pics are good ( i am comparing it with my canon sx230hs , not fair to compare 15 K with 5.5 K ) . the battery charger is in built so you dont need to carry one charger ( unless you want a spare battery and charge ). the card i got as free with this is class - 4 ( kind of useless ) , it takes lot of time to save pic ( pic to pic time is ~5 second ) , better to give a 2 gb but higher speed . buy a class - 10 ( 30 mbps write speed )card. Overall its value for money and can take pics on any occasion with auto mode ( ladies , kids who don't want or don't know how to play with control ) </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Dinesh</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">3</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 4, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Deal Deal...</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Its really a good camera with Panorma Assistance. i got this cam from Nikon outlet with Paker Pen, Tripod Stand, Card Reader, Screen Gaurd. all in 5800 only. This is really a very good camera with very good deal. Love it :)
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Parth Bavishi</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">May 23, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Amazing...</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Nikon lens are always the best... Very sleek, color is stunning... packing is damage proof... can connect directly to d TV and watch snaps n videos. Good clarity.. Zoon is great.. Face detection gives good personal snaps. carrying case is very stylish...
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Randhawa Verma</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 10, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Yep its actually cool!!! ...</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">This is my first digital camera so m very much excited for taking hands on it. Previously i have Kodak reel camera, but now these types of camera are going to be extinct as their place is taken all n all by point n shoot cameras.Talking about this camera -First of all, floral design look on this camera is awesome. great picture quality however video is not that much but its good.Battery life is also great! It has different functions and scene selection options for better photography. Its UI and buttons are very easy to use.All n all its one of the best cameras in this range. I am a newbie in using these cameras so for me its more than what i want :)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Ajay Mahajan</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Apr 24, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Coolpix - A Cool One :)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Bought this as an entry level Camera for my daughter. What made this stand apart from some of the other camera options was the Lithium battery as compared to rechargeable pencil cells offered by most other entry level cameras.Already own a Nikon DSLR - so the Nikon quality was already proven. Overall - I would recommend this over almost all other entry level cameras. And its availability in my daughters favorite color was another factor in its favor.
</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Jeevan kumar Shetty</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Sep 4, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">!!!!! just try it  ;) !!!!!!!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						The camera is very stlyish, slim and is very easy to carry, the quality of the picture is also very good, better than Sony Cybershot. Overall  the product is worthy.About fflipkart, the service is very fast and very good. We Expect the same in future. Overall  I am very happy with the service of Flipkart. Thankyou very much to the Flipkart Team.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Ayush Gupta</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jun 25, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">REALLY COOLPIX</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I bought this camera a month ago , its fun clicking pics all with HD. It has a special 5x wide optical zoom.It has 14 MP. The features are GR8. It has Li-ion battery which minimumly gives 2-3 hours to enjoy. It has auto scene selector mode which allows to click pics very minorly.It also come in some impressive colors which gives it a neat and beautiful look. Just one thing is there which creats problem, thats its voice quality.I was recording sumthing from TV ,but when I saw the video i was not able to hear it properly.Sound could be heard but u have to open ur ears wide to hear it.Allover its a decent camera and if u r looking for a cam buy this,u'll be impressed !!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName"> Mayank D'souza</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 4, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nikon Coolpix S2600</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Nikon Coolpix S2600 is One of the Best Digital Cameras by Nikon...___________________________Always Remember Nikon Gives you a real image, without any extra effects..Best Cameras, Best Images, Best Everything..__________________________Always Remember if you want to purchase a good camera below 12000rs., purchase either nikon or sony, only.. it's my experience..__________________________
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">KRISHNAN S</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 4, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Great product for its range</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Brought this about an year ago.have had no issues with it so far.A sure shot recommendation for those planning to buy the same.Had brought a Fujifilm from Flipkart earlier in the same range which turned out be a not so good product.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">UTKARSH GARG</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jul 23, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Cool pix .. Really Cool !!!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						This camera i gifted to my sister on her birthday  and she loved it . Actually the design on the camera makes it more cool . The purple color is best for girls . About the camera , 14 megapixel is enough for normal use and its picture Quality is awesome .  There were so many gifts with this product - Parker pen , 4 GB card , Pouch . Best Buy camera in this range . 
				</specsKey>
</root>