<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix P7700 Point &amp; Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 23,204</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">60 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">12.2 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Resolution">3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), 640 x 480 (VGA), 3984 x 2656 (3:2), 3968 x 2232 (16:9, 9 M), 3000 x 3000 (1:1)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast-detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">6.0 - 42.8 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 28 - 200 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">7.1x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">392 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">118.5 (W) x 72.5 (H) x 50.4 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">Wide Viewing Angle TFT LCD with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Aspect Ratio">3:2, 16:9, 1:1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Microphone">Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="PictBridge">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL14, Camera Strap, Battery Charger MH-24, USB Cable UC-E17, Audio Video Cable EG-CP16, ViewNX2 CD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point &amp; Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">P7700</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Rear Curtain Sync, Fill-in Mode, Slow Sync, Auto Mode, Flash Off Mode, Red-eye Reduction</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Range">0.5 - 10 m (W), 0.5 - 5.5 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="External Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/1.7 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F2 - 4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Picture Angle">28 mm Wide-angle</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">Matrix (224 Segment Matrix), Center-weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 6 Shots at 8 fps (Top Continuous Shooting Speed at Full Resolution)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">ISO 80 - 1600, 3200, Hi 1 (Equivalent to 6400)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto 1 (Normal), Auto 2 (Warm), Choose Color Temperature, Cloudy, Daylight, Flash, Fluorescent, Incandescent, Preset Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene, Special Effects, Program, Shutter Priority, Aperture Priority, Manual, User Settings</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 1, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">Yes, 2 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="HDMI">Type C Mini HDMI Connector</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">29</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Additional Features">12.76 Total Megapixels, Lens Construction: 13 Elements in 10 Groups (2 ED Lens Elements), Digital Zoom Movie: 2x (Equivalent to 400 mm Lens in 35 mm (135) Format), Min Focus Range: 50 cm (W) - 80 cm (T), Focus-area Selection (Face Priority, Auto (9-area Automatic Selection), Center (Wide, Normal), Manual with 99 Focus Areas, Subject Tracking, Target Finding AF), Brightness (5 Level Brightness Adjustment, Vari-angle TFT LCD), LCD Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode): 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical, LCD Frame Coverage (Playback Mode): 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical, Scene Mode (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Movie Resolution (HD 720p: 1280 x 720 at 30 fps, VGA: 640 x 480 at 30 fps, HS 120 fps: 640 x 480, HS 60 fps: 1280 x 720, HS 15 fps: 1920 x 1080), Exposure Control (Programmed Auto Exposure with Flexible Program, Aperture Priority Auto, Exposure Bracketing (Tv, Av, Sv) Enabled), Exposure Modes (Aperture Priority (A), Manual (M), Programmed Auto (P), Shutter Priority (S)), Exposure Compensation Still: 3 in increments of 1/3, Exposure Compensation Movie: 2 in increments of 1/3, Shutter Mechanical and CMOS Electronics Shutter, Shutter Speed: 1 - 1/4000 secs, Aperture: Electronically-controlled 7 Blade Iris Diaphragm, Aperture Range (13 Steps of 1/3 EV (W) (A, M Mode), Flash Control (TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Pre-flashes and Manual Flash Enabled), Flash Compensation: 2 in increments of 1/3 EV, Accessory Shoe (ISO 518 Hot-shoe with Sync and Data Contacts and Safety Lock), Nikon Creative Lighting System (i-TTL Flash Control Support in Combination with Nikon Creative Lighting System-compatible Speedlights (Only Standard i-TTL Flash Control Supported During Spot Metering Mode), Flash Color Information Communication Supported, Advanced Wireless Lighting Supported by Setting SB-910, SB-900, SB-800 or SB-700 to Master Flash or by Setting SU-800 to the Commander Mode (Remote Flash Setting Only Applicable to Group A), Advanced Wireless Lighting Supported by Setting the Built-in Flash to Commander Mode (Only Applicable to Group A and Fixed at 3 CH), Data Transfer Protocol (MTP, PTP), HDMI Output (Auto, 480p, 720p, 1080i), Still Pictures (330 Shots When Using EN-EL14), Movie Recording (1 hr 10 mins When Using EN-EL14), Tripod Socket (1 / 4 (ISO 1222), Voice Memo Function, Operating Temperature: 0° - 40° C, Operating Humidity: 85%</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4000 x 3000 (12 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene, Special Effects, Program, Shutter Priority, Aperture Priority, Manual, User Settings</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG, NRW (RAW), MPO, DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF, MPF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">AAC Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">MOV (H.264, MPEG-4 AVC)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Power Supply">AC Adapter EH-5b (Sold Separately)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Operating System">Windows 7 SP1, Windows Vista SP2, Windows XP SP3, Mac OS X 10.6.8 - 10.7.4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">86 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/j/y/m/nikon-coolpix-p7700-point-shoot-400x400-imadef9mz3fagfvr.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/j/y/m/nikon-coolpix-p7700-point-shoot-400x400-imadef9fvyxxfn3f.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/j/y/m/nikon-coolpix-p7700-point-shoot-400x400-imadef9rggzmjsbu.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/j/y/m/nikon-coolpix-p7700-point-shoot-400x400-imadef9hmb98v93m.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/j/y/m/nikon-coolpix-p7700-point-shoot-400x400-imadef9rqhah2mcn.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/j/y/m/nikon-coolpix-p7700-point-shoot-400x400-imadef9hgnzpj9wv.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/j/y/m/nikon-coolpix-p7700-point-shoot-400x400-imadef9gqpnwnhd8.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/j/y/m/nikon-coolpix-p7700-point-shoot-400x400-imadef9sr2h2vzhw.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Rahul Verma</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 11, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">The Best!!!!!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">Nikon P7700 is one of the best point and shoot camera currently available. Some say Sony RX100 is the best it gives near DSLR quality. But I say at a price Tag of Rs 34500/- its just an expensive toy which definitely gives awesome quality but stands no where near a Full Frame sensor or even an APS-C sensor.The performance of Nikon P7700 is noisy at higher ISO levels (400+) but I don't think any professional photographer needs to go to those levels when this has a hot shoe and also supports remote flash.The lens of this camera is where it wins the race, f2 at wide angle which might seem small compared to the competitors but f4 at telephoto (200mm) is pretty awesome for this camera.Manual controls are way better than going into menu and changing settings for semi pro people this is a very good camera to learn the techniques of photography before one can invest in DSLR's.The expansion capabilities of this camera is another feature which sets it apart from others, it has filter threads (40.5mm) so if you are done with experimenting with shutter, aperture etc.. you can go get a bunch of filters and continue with the fun. Built in ND filter is added bonus along with a mic jack which might not seem like a necessity to most of the users till they actually use it and see the difference.None of the latest advanced compacts can match this camera in all round performance. In some specific features they are definitely better like Panasonic Lumix LX7 has a f1.4, Sony RX100 with its 1 inch sensor, Canon g15 with a view finder. But a good photographer knows that its the balance of all these features that provides good photos and not a single feature alone.All in all this is a fantastic camera who's premium price is totally justified by the features included in it.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">SandeepRaj</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 31, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">pocket sized dslr</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">Nikon Coolpix P7700 brings a more "DSLR-like" experience to pocket-sized camerashe Nikon Coolpix P7700 is the new "professional model in Nikon’s extensive range of Coolpix compact digital cameras. The Coolpix P7700 is the successor to the one-year-old P7100, the main additions being a back-illuminated 12-megapixel, 1/1.7-inch CMOS sensor, faster lens, vari-angle LCD screen and full 1080 video recording. The Nikon P7700 features a mechanically-stabilized 7.1x optical zoom with a focal range of 28-200mm and maximum apertures of f/2.0-4.0, built-in neutral density filter, sensitivity range of ISO 80 to 6400, RAW file support, 8fps burst shooting, external flash hotshoe, PASM shooting modes, 1080p HD video recording with stereo sound and a microphone jack, GPS support and a 3-inch, 920,000-dot LCD screen. Designed to appeal to the keen enthusiast photographer,</specsKey>
</root>