<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix P7800 Advanced Point &amp; Shoot Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 25,480</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">12.2 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Resolution">3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), 640 x 480 (VGA), 3984 x 2656 (3:2), 3968 x 2232 (16:9, 9 M), 3000 x 3000 (1:1)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">6.0 - 42.8 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 28 - 200 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">7.1x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">399 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">118.5 (W) x 77.5 (H) x 50.4 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">Vari-angle TFT LCD with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30p</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Viewfinder">Yes, Electronic Viewfinder</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Aspect Ratio">3:2, 16:9, 1:1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ViewFinder">Yes, Electronic Viewfinder</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Advanced Point &amp; Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">P7800</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Range">0.5 - 10 m (W), 0.5 - 5.5 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="External Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/1.7 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F2 - F4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 120 fps (Continuous H, The Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is about 120 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 60), 60 fps (Continuous H, The Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is about 60 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 60)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">ISO 80 - 1600 ISO 3200, Hi 1 (Equivalent to ISO 6400) Available When Using P, S, A or M Mode</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene, Special Effects, Program, Shutter-priority, Aperture-priority, Manual, User Settings (U1, U2, U3), Movie, Movie Custom Setting</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 1, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">Yes, Minimum 2 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="HDMI">Type C Mini HDMI</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">34</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Additional Features">12.76 Total Megapixel, Lens Construction: 13 Elements in 10 Groups (2 ED Lens Elements), Digital Zoom Magnification: 4x (Angle of View Equivalent to that of 800 mm Lens in 35 mm (135) Format), Movies: 2x (Angle of View Equivalent to that of 400 mm Lens in 35 mm (135) Format), Minimum Focus Range: 50 cm (W) - 80 cm (T), Focus-area Selection (Face Priority, Auto (9-area Automatic Selection), Center (Wide, Normal), Manual with 99 Focus Areas, Subject Racking, Target Finding AF), Viewfinder (0.5 cm, 921,000 dots, LCD with the Diopter Adjustment Function (-3 to +1 m-1), Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode): 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture), Frame Coverage (Playback Mode): 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture)), LCD (Wide Viewing Angle, 6 Level Brightness Adjustment, Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode): 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture), Frame Coverage (Playback Mode): 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture)), Scene Mode (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party/Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk/Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and white Copy, Backlighting, Panorama, Pet Portrait), Exposure Metering Mode (Also when AF Area Mode is Set to Manual, the AF Area can be Coupled to the Metering Range Using Focus-coupled Metering), Exposure Control (Programmed Auto Exposure with Flexible Program, Shutter-priority Auto, Aperture-priority Auto, Manual, Exposure Bracketing (Tv, Av, Sv) Enabled, Exposure Compensation: +/- 3.0 EV in increments of 1/3 EV (Still Picture), +/- 2.0 EV in increments of 1/3 EV (Movie), Mechanical and CMOS Electronic Shutter, Shutter Speed (1/4000 - 60 sec (When ISO Sensitivity is Set to 80 - 400 in M Mode), When the Aperture Value is Set to f/4.5 - f/8 (Wide-angle Position) or the Value is Set to f/7.1 - f/8 (Telephoto Zoom Position), Aperture: Electronically-controlled 7 Blade Iris Diaphragm, Aperture Range (13 Steps of 1/3 EV (W) (A, M Mode)), Flash Control: TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Preflashes, Manual Flash, Flash Exposure Compensation: +/- 2.0 EV in increments of 1/3 EV, Accessory Shoe (ISO 518 Hot-shoe with Sync and Data Contacts and Safety Lock), Nikon Creative Lighting System (i-TTL Flash Control Support in Combination with Nikon Creative Lighting System-compatible Speedlights (Only Standard i-TTL Flash Control is Supported During Spot Metering Mode), Flash Color Information Communication is Supported, Advanced Wireless Lighting is Supported by Setting SB-910, SB-900, SB-800 or SB-700 to Master Flash or by Setting SU-800 to the Commander Mode (the Remote Flash Setting is Only Applicable to Group A), Advanced Wireless Lighting is Supported by Setting the Built-in Flash to the Commander Mode (Only Applicable to Group A and Fixed at 3 CH)), Data Transfer Protocol: MTP, PTP, HDMI Output (Can be Selected from Auto, 480p, 720p, and 1080i), I/O Terminal (Digital I/O (USB), External Microphone Connector (Stereo Mini-pin Jack (3.5 mm Diameter), Plug-in Power Type) Accessory Terminal), Battery Life: 350 Shots with EN-EL14, Movie Recording (Actual Battery Life for Recording): 1 hr 15 min when Recording in NTSC Mode Using EN-EL14, 1 hr 20 min when Recording in PAL Mode Using EN-EL14, Tripod Socket: 1/4 (ISO 1222), Temperature: 0° C - 40° C, Humidity: 85% (No Condensation)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4000 x 3000 (12 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene, Special Effects, Program, Shutter-priority, Aperture-priority, Manual, User Settings (U1, U2, U3), Movie, Movie Custom Setting</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG, RAW (NRW) (Nikon's Own Format), DCF, EXIF 2.3 and DPOF Compliant</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">WAV, AAC Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">MOV, H.264 / MPEG-4 AVC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Power Supply">AC Adapter EH-5b</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">86 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/v/z/t/nikon-coolpix-p7800-advance-point-and-shoot-400x400-imadqgb7jfvvnmbg.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/v/z/t/nikon-coolpix-p7800-advance-point-and-shoot-400x400-imadqgb7m3b4fu3k.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/v/z/t/nikon-coolpix-p7800-advance-point-and-shoot-400x400-imadqgb7zwhkufdp.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/v/z/t/nikon-coolpix-p7800-advance-point-and-shoot-400x400-imadqgb7hhxhgaub.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/v/z/t/nikon-coolpix-p7800-advance-point-and-shoot-400x400-imadqgb7fhx8apb4.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/v/z/t/nikon-coolpix-p7800-advance-point-and-shoot-400x400-imadqgb7frqqk2fu.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/v/z/t/nikon-coolpix-p7800-advance-point-and-shoot-400x400-imadqgb7vprdh2tk.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">vishal</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 12, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Great all-rounder camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I bought this camera mainly for my parents. Well, selected, actually--they paid for it :) There's already an SLR in the house, so the reasoning behind buying this camera was that there should be a camera in the family that's light and compact enough to be carried around easily everywhere. Yes, the price is well into the entry-level SLR territory, and SLRs do seem more attractive for a lot of reasons, some valid, some not. However, having spent A LOT of time shooting DSLRs, I can tell you that their weight and bulk quickly gets annoying. At times, it'll simply feel silly to be toting a huge camera bag, say, to small events, or in a restaurant. On such occasions, you'll want a camera that can take good pictures (or videos) but also isn't an awkward burden to carry.But enough ranting and on to the camera.The P7800 is the at the very top of the Coolpix P-series, which stands for Performance, which means that this is at the very high-end of Nikon's non-DSLR, feature- and performance-wise. As I see it, it's aimed at people who'd like more control over technical parameters, as in SLRs, and also comparable image quality, but in a compact form.The main, outstanding features (ie. the specifications that actually matter, but don't get as much mention) are:1) Lens equivalent focal length 28-200mm (7x zoom) with VR (vibration reduction) : What this means is that you can comfortably take wide-angle shots like landscapes, family portraits, etc, and also zoom in to reasonably distant subjects. No, you'll never need the 20x, 30x &amp; 60x that you see in a lot of similar models. That usually compromises on other aspects of lens quality. If you had to be clicking snow leopards for Nat Geo, you wouldn't be reading this review.2) Large lens aperture f/2-4 : These numbers are very good for this segment of camera, and they matter A LOT. This translates to much better results in low-light. That means not just night-time, but most indoors shots. Even a regular phone camera can yield impressive image-quality in bright daylight; true quality shows up only in poor lighting which is where a lot of photos get easily blurred or come out grainy.3) Large sensor 1/1.7 inches : Again, this is very good. This also translates to less grainy pictures in poor light and overall better image sharpness &amp; quality. Megapixels mean nothing, sensor size is everything.4) Professional-oriented dials/buttons &amp; shooting modes: Depends on personal preferences. If you're familiar with the technicalities and want more control, the dedicated controls mean not having to dive into menus every time. If you just want to point and shoot, just set it on full-auto and ignore all those other dials, as my parents do. The auto mode nowadays is smart enough so you never have to select those scene-specific modes like 'beach', 'landscape', 'night-portrait', etc.5) Electronic viewfinder - the little window that you peek through. Very useful when, on a very bright day, the glare makes it hard to see the image on the screen. Also, when you're running low on battery. The screen, btw, is very good, and has an anti-glare coating, but it's still good to have the EVF.6) Popup flash - there's a separate button to make it pop out; you need to push it back in manually. This is good because you can choose when to activate the flash easily, rather than have the camera pop it up when you son't need it, or having to change flash settings in a menu.7) Flip out screen: not a must, but good to have sometimes, say, if you're shooting a flower on the ground and you don't want to have to lie down for it. You can also turn and close it to protect the screen.On the whole, image and video quality on this has been excellent. It feels nice &amp; comfortable in the hand. There are a couple of issues.1) The camera case supplied with it is terrible. It's clearly not designed for this model. You have to literally push and squeeze it into the case till it's bulging.2) The lens cap doesn't have a hole for a loop, so it can't be secured to the camera. Some jugaad required.On the whole, I'd say that the number of physical controls and menu options on this camera can seem pretty intimidating at first to someone who isn't too tech-savvy, specially compared to cameras that sacrifice the controllability for a sleek, minimalistic design. So it's likely that many people will find it a bit chunky or boxy or unnecessarily complex. However, those sleeker cameras also have lower specs in several vital areas simply because of the bussiness-sense of clubbing point-and-shoot level specs with point-and-shoot design. And you can always just ignore all those controls and shoot in full-auto mode, which is excellent, and you'd still be getting the advantage of the better lens, sensor, processing chip and sturdy metallic body of this camera.P.S.- Another great and much cheaper alternative to this model is the Nikon Coolpix P340. Well worth consideration.</specsKey>
</root>