<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon 1 J1 (White)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Red,White</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.583</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 23,204</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">1 J1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">White</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/y/d/g/nikon-1-j1-400x400-imad7cqgfvy2tpzw.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="subimg">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/g/g/5/nikon-1-j1-400x400-imad7dzvjjcdt7h4.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img_id">Nikon 1 J1 (Red)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="subimg">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/s/n/z/nikon-1-j1-mirrorless-400x400-imadwr2swzuhzgg8.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img_id">Nikon 1 J1 (White)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Mandav</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 5, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nice camera but has it sides of flaws</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">The camera is good enough for carrying around. The 10.2 Mp factor is still gives a tight space to crop still the overall ability of the camera is good as compared to bulky dslr. If you compare this camera with Nikon D3100 and Canon 1100D ,the image quality and performance is much better. Due to 2.7 Crop ratio factor,the aperture wouldn't be able to go beyond f/16 still it is more than enough for shooting landscapes.The video shooting capability is way beyond and only few know. That this camera is mostly used for video shooting purpose thanks to its phase detection.For price around 21k it is a good camera. The lens are few yet u can use FT-1 adapter for use of additional Nikon Lens.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Subrata Sarkar</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 17, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Excellent</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Recently I buy this camera, this is excellent, I want sear a story, my friend also buy a camera ( Nikon D3100), we have took a same picture in same angle, J1 picture quality is much better than  D3100,  J1 Sutter speed is better than D3100, many more features are better than D3100.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Anoop Joshi</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 15, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">go for Sony istead</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						really guys if you are not buying a bulky dslr than go for Sony's in mirrorless instead. sony's innovation in mirrorless is light years ahead than any other brand you can also consider Olympus but that only applies for super high end range...and for this one i really don't see a point of purchasing a mirrorless with just a 10 MP sensor. but yeah i havent actually used this one. so i just cannot complain bout it.   
				</specsKey>
</root>