<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix S8200 Point &amp; Shoot Camera (Red)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Red</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.65</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 12,509</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/1600 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">4 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR ED Glass lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast-detect TTL AF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">4.5 - 63.0 mm (35 mm format equivalent to 25 - 350 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">14x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">2x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">213 g</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">103.7 (W) x 59.3 (H) x 32.7(D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body &amp; lens.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">TFT LCD Monitor with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB 2.0</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Camera Strap AN-CP19, USB Cable UC-E6, Audio Video Cable EG-CP16, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL12, Charging AC Adapter EH-69P, View NX 2 CD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point &amp; Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">Coolpix S8200</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Red</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with red-eye reduction, Off, Fill flash, Slow sync</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Range">0.5 - 5.5 m (W), 1.0 - 3.0 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F3.3 - F5.9</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 10 fps up to 5 shots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">Auto (auto gain ISO 100 to 1600), Fixed range auto (ISO 100 to 400, ISO 100 to 800), Manual selection: ISO 100, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto, Preset manual, Daylight, Incandescent, Fluorescent, Cloudy, Flash</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto mode, Scene mode, Night Landscape, Backlight, Continuous, Special effects, Pet Portrait, Movie mode</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">Yes, 1 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="HDMI">HDMI mini connector</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">29</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">224-Segment matrix metering, Center-weighted metering</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Additional Features">Frame Coverage, Voice Memo Function, In-Camera Image Editing, Operating Temperature: 0Deg - 40Deg C</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4608 x 3456 (16 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto mode, Scene mode, Night Landscape, Backlight, Continuous, Special effects, Pet Portrait, Movie mode</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG, EXIF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">WAV, AAC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">MPEG-4 AVC/H.264</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Power Supply">AC Adapter EH-62F</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">89 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/7/s/4/nikon-coolpix-s8200-400x400-imad6vyf2mhy4hha.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/7/s/4/nikon-coolpix-s8200-400x400-imad6vyfgkvxjggm.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/7/s/4/nikon-coolpix-s8200-400x400-imad6vyfdrqh6gyu.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/7/s/4/nikon-coolpix-s8200-400x400-imad6vyf7aaaesqx.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Himanshu Jain</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 5, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Awsome Camera............</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						gud quality....  worth buying it....features are also awsome... CMOS sensor adds life to d pics... the drawback is of its continuous Auto FOcus.... it becomes hazy while zoming n recording  videos but adjusts after a second or two...the mono color mode is also great.sleek looks and around battery life around 300 pics is also gud.overall 4.5 out of 5....
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Naseer</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 3, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">COOLPIX S8200 - Great camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I bought this camera last week and I am totally satisfied with the performance of it, the image quality is extremely good even at night shoots.Very few things which I see as drawbacks of this camera are: - Location of Flash which many times comes under your finger while shooting, you would require some time to tune your mind not to put your finger over it and move away. - Location of Power Button might also give some trouble for the new user. - This camera can be charged even with USB cable through a PC or from cars music player which is a good feature but whats bad about it is, if you are looking to have an additional battery for this you need to buy a battery charger (MH-65) since the charger provided with the camera charges the battery without the need to take it out from the camera.*** Overall it is really a very good camera if you can adjust with few design issues *** </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Raja Anirudh Reddy</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 5, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Great camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I am a huge camera buff, i already own a nikon d90(SLR) a canon 60D(SLR) and now this... I prefer the D90 which despite it compactness provides a breathtaking 14x optical zoom, features are awesome including realtime video selective colouring and macro mode which focuses on objects as close as 1cm from the lensOverall: This is perhaps THE best compact digital point and shoot cameraRating:4.7/5.0
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Sankara Narayanan S</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 12, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Absolutely Awesome :)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Wow!! the shipment was super fast, I received a brand new, authentic Nikon coolpix  8200 in just 2 days after the order,I found this camera very useful for freezing my happy times with friends,family..Thanks to flipcart!!
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Manit Samal</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 27, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">DON'T buy this camera...</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I bought Nikon Coolpix S8200 two weeks back and I would seriously advise you all to keep a distance with this camera and go for other good cameras available in market. This camera has a serious issue and I would call it a manufacturing flaw. In Flash mode when you press shutter-release button the Flash pops up automatically and if you want to click next photo without flash, you need to turn off the Camera to lower the flash otherwise it will remain keep open although you are clicking photos in NO FLASH mode. This is the worst feature of this camera, now days in market you may find many other cameras where you can push the flash option down manually and it’s safe too.It may look a small issue but it’s very annoying when in the auto Flash mode the flash screen pops up first time and it remains open till the time you turn off your camera although you have sufficient lighting for following photos.Before buying this camera I was die heart fan of Nikon but now I would say Nikon could not provide a very basic feature in this camera to its customer. You may buy Sony DSC-HX10, its bit expensive than this but it’s worth to buy rather than this camera. One of my friends bought Sony DSC-HX10 on the same day when I bought Nikon Coolpix s8200 and now I am really regretting on my decision. In Sony DSC-HX10 you may easily push the flash option down if you switch from Flash mode to No Flash mode, you do not required to restart the camera every time or you may look for any other camera but do not waste your money on this camera.  ManitNew Delhi</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Nabendu Das</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 27, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Probably best point &amp; shoot camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I have purchased this camera few days ago &amp; it is really awesome..The pic. quality is amazing &amp; video can be recorded in various qualities including 1080p..zoom mood also very effective &amp; clear..I suggest u to buy it if ur budget is bellow 14k..
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Hrishi</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 26, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Best Digicam To Invest In</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I have been using this cam for more than 1 year....... And its pretty competitive against other cams at this price list.............. It has a nice and powerfull flash light with tonnes of shooting modes....... My opinion go for it............
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Vibhav Srivastava</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 10, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Designed to perfection, Awesome Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Awesome camera to click pictures at night as the night landscape mode works quite well,picture quality is amazing even in the low light conditions.S8200 is a great buy and comes loaded with cool features....
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Siddhartha Deb Sarkar</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jul 23, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">very good camera with great picture quality</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						gud quality.... worth buying it....features are also awsome...Pros:1. Very good point and shoot camera, has lot of features.2. Worth the price.3. Zoom is very goodhe drawback is of its continuous Auto FOcus.... it becomes hazy while zoming n recording videos but adjusts after a second or two... overall rating : 8.5 out of 10.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Ramana Rao</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jul 19, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Best in this budget category</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I've checked many websites &amp; many articles that compare and tell you which camera is the best. And I've included all the cameras that are around 15k.Just for 14k this turned out to be the winner, far beating other leading cameras.The macro mode that lets you take focused pictures of close objects while leaving the rest of the background out of focus is AWESOME. You can even manually(using the arrow keys) point out the portion of the screen you want to focus.After using this camera I have to say "YES, BUY THIS ONE"
</specsKey>
</root>