<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix S31 Waterproof Point &amp; Shoot Camera (Brown)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Brown</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.125</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 5,534</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/2000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">10.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Resolution">Image Size: 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), Movie: Large 1280 x 720 / 16:9 / 30 fps, Small (640): 640 x 480 / 4:3 / 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">4.1 - 12.3 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 29 - 87 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">3x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">185 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">105.4 (W) x 64.8 (H) x 41.5 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">1280 x 720, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">TFT LCD with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">2.7 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">230,400 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Aspect Ratio">4:3, 16:9</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL12 (with Terminal Cover), Camera Strap, USB Cable UC-E16, ViewNX 2 CD, Brush, Reference Manual CD, Battery Charger MH-65 (with Power Cable)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point &amp; Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">S31 Waterproof</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Brown</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Range">0.5 - 3.5 m (W), 0.5 - 2.0 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/2.9 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F3.3 - F5.9</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 4 Shots at 1.5 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">ISO 80 - 1600</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">Yes, 5 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">32</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Additional Features">"Lens Construction: 6 Elements in 5 Groups, Focus-area Selection Center, Face Detection, Frame Coverage Shooting Mode: 97% Horizontal and 97% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture), Frame Coverage Playback Mode: 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture), Shooting Modes: Point and Shoot, Choose a Style (Shoot Close-ups, Photograph Food, Shoot at Intervals, Shoot Under Water, Take Series of Pictures, Photograph Fireworks, Mirror, Take Soft Pictures, Create Diorama Effect, Take Series of Pictures: Four Images at Rate of About 1.5 fps, Exposure Control Programmed Auto Exposure and Exposure Compensation: -2.0 - .0 EV in increments of 1 EV, Shutter: Mechanical and Charge-coupled Electronic Shutter, Aperture Electronically-controlled ND Filter (-3 AV) Selection, Range 2 Steps (f/3.3 and f/9.3 [W]), Flash Control: TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Preflashes, Data Transfer Protocol: MTP, PTP, 1/4 inch Tripod Socket, Operating Temperature: 0° C - 40° C, Humidity: 85%, Waterproof, Dustproof, Shockproof, Fun Filters, Motion Blur Reduction, Easy to Handle, One Button-one Function, Crisp 720p Video Recording, Automatic Power-off"</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">3648 x 2736 (10 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG, DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">WAV</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">AVI (Motion-JPEG Compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">26 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/z/h/m/nikon-coolpix-s31-waterproof-point-shoot-400x400-imadjf5rhhsge8q6.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/z/h/m/nikon-coolpix-s31-waterproof-point-shoot-400x400-imadjf5rmug8mres.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/z/h/m/nikon-coolpix-s31-waterproof-point-shoot-400x400-imadjf5rftpymhh3.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/z/h/m/nikon-coolpix-s31-waterproof-point-shoot-400x400-imadjf5rgsepphpf.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/z/h/m/nikon-coolpix-s31-waterproof-point-shoot-400x400-imadjf5rw6ef2kxw.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Sumit Kulkarni</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Apr 25, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Best Point and Shoot for Home as well as Outdoors.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I've ordered same from flipkart because this product was not available in any retail store.Build quality and protection of this camera is awesome. I took it to beach and it survived very well in water and beach sand.It is something that you can wash after getting dirty.Interface is pretty simple, basic modes, flash, brightness adjustments. Simple that anyone can pick up and go on.I personally use Canon 650D DSLR, but it needs to be taken care of. You cannot take it anywhere in rains, muds you want.Even if you are having very high budget for P&amp;S, I'll suggest to either add up your budget and buy DSLR,or go for this rugged one.Because there are no significant photo quality differences in Day photography of P&amp;S.Go for it. </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Lisa Dearman-Valles</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jul 27, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Great for the monsoon on the beach! </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Fantastic camera for heavy rain and also shock proof which is great for kids and simple to use!!!!! The free pouch is too small for this particular camera. Great water depth for a camera for the swimming pool. 
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Prangshu Phukan</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Mar 22, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Worry free camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">Checked the camera at a local store and for the price point, it is pretty good buy. Image Quality is as good as any camera available in the range and those sport this 1/2.3 sensor. But the selling point is that it is a rugged camera, which gives the buyer peace of mind. Any other rugged camera costs anything around 15k(off course they have better specification), but here you can get this for less than 6k. I already have added this to my wishlist and I know it will be very good secondary camera that I can carry to a pool, river or beaches (or even playing holi) without have to worry. About damaging it accidentally dropping it in water</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Mayank Mishra</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 6, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Best buy in this price</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I gifted this to a friend of mine who has two very naughty children at home.  This camera was best for him as it is shockproof, dustproof, and waterproof.  He is really very happy with it.  It obviously takes good pictures too :-)
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Praveen Mani</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 18, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">A Good Camera to gift Kids</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">Bought this camera for my 7 year old. She has been throughly enjoying the camera. Have been using it for a month now. The Daylight pictures are good. Pictures indoors need to be taken with care as there is no Image Stabalization. The packaging as usual was good. Time taken to receive the camera though within the SLA seemed longer than the usual time taken by Flipkart. Could have been an issue with the vendor.Received a TIMEX wrist watch as a gift along with the camera. :-) which was a surprise. - Simple buttons. Top Left of Video and Top Right for Photographs. - Not much of controls and hence the ropes of photography can be picked up quickly. - The only available phone in this price range that can withstand rough use.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Leonid Joseph</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 16, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Cheapest Rugged Camera.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I have used it for a while now. Battery is ok. Picture quality is very good for the price. Best thing is that although it is rugged and water proof, it does not look like one. Big buttons at the back is too simple to use even for kids. Overall a very good purchase.
				</specsKey>
</root>