<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix AW110 Waterproof Point &amp; Shoot Camera (Silver)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Silver</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 13,560</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/1500 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point &amp; Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">AW110 Waterproof</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Silver</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Range">0.5 - 5.2 m (W), 0.5 - 4.5 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F3.9 - F7.8 (W)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 6 Shots at 8 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">ISO 125 - 1600, ISO 3200 (Auto Mode)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Easy Auto, Scene</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto, Cloudy, Daylight, Flash, Fluorescent, Incandescent, Preset Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">Yes, 1 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="HDMI">Type D, Micro HDMI Output</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">32</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Additional Features">16.79 Total Megapixels, 11 Elements in 9 Groups (2 ED Lens Elements), Digital Zoom Magnification (560 mm Lens in 35 mm (135) Format), Motion Blur Reduction (Motion Detection (Still Pictures)), Autofocus Focus-area Selection (Auto (9-area Automatic Selection), Center, Face Priority, Manual with 99 Focus Areas, Subject Tracking), Min Focus Range: 50 cm (W) - 1 m (T), Focus Lock, 5 Level Brightness Adjustment, Shooting Mode Monitor Frame Coverage (97% Horizontal, 97% Vertical), Playback Mode Monitor Frame Coverage (100% Horizontal, 100% Vertical), Recording Reslution (HD: 1280 x 720p at 30 fps, HS: 1920 x 1080 at 15 fps, 1280 x 720 at 60 fps, HS: 640 x 480 at 120 fps, 320 x 240 at 24 fps, iFrame: 960 x 540 at 30 fps), Voice Memo Function, Exposure Control (Programmed Auto Exposure, Exposure Compensation), Exposure Modes (Programmed Auto), Scene Modes (Back Light, Beach, Black and White Copy, Close-up, Dusk / Down, Easy Panorama, Fireworks Show, Food, Landscape, Museum, Night Landscape, Night Portrait, Part / Indoor, Pet Portrait, Scene Auto Selector, Snow, Sunset, 3D Photography, Underwater), In-camera Image Editing (Crop, Data Imprint, D-lighting, Glamour Retouch, Quick Effects, Quick Retouch, Small Picture), Exposure Compensation: 2 EV in incremetns of 1/3, Mechanical and CMOS Electronic Shutter, 4 secs Shutter Speed (Fireworks Show), Aperture (Electronically Controlled ND Filter (-2.0 AV) Insertion), TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Preflashes, Interface Data Transfer Protocol (MTP, PTP), HDMI Output (Auto, 480p, 720p, 1080i), Charging Time (2 hrs 30 mins When Using MH-65 Battery Charger), 250 Shots Battery Life, Tripod Socket (1/4, ISO 1222), Land Operating Temperature: -10 to ° C, Underwater Operating Temperature: 0 to 40° C, Operating Humidity: 85%, Waterproof (Depth of 18 m and for 60 mins), Shockpoof, Wireless LAN (IEEE 802.11b/g/n, ARIB STD-T66 (Standard for Low Power Data Communications Systems), Communications Protocols (IEEE 802.11b: DBPSK, DQPSK, CCK IEEE 802.11g: OFDM IEEE 802.11n: OFDM), Range (Line of Sight): 30 m (32 yd) (Varies with Location), Operating Frequency (2412 - 2462 MHz (1 - 11 Channels)), Data Rates Actual Measured Values (IEEE 802.11b: 5 Mbps IEEE 802.11g: 12 Mbps IEEE 802.11n: 12 Mbps), Security (Open / WPA2), Access Protocols (CSMA / CA), Electronic Compass (16 Cardinal Points (Position Correction Using 3-axis Acceleration Sensor, Automatic Correction for the Deviated Angle and Automatic Offset Adjustment), Dustproof, Continuous Shooting (Best Shot Selector, Continous H, Continous H 60, Continous H 120, Continous L, Multi-shot 16, Pre-shooting Cache, Single), Built-in GPS (Receiver Frequency 1575.42 MHz (C/A Code), Geodetic System WGS 84)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">5 - 25 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 28 - 140 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Resolution">3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), 640 x 480 (VGA), 4608 x 2592 (16:9,12 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4608 x 3456 (16 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Easy Auto, Scene</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG, MPO, DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF, MPF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">WAV, AAC Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">MOV, H.264 / MPEG-4 AVC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">5x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">193 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">110.1 (W) x 65.3 (H) x 24.5 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">21 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">OLED Monitor with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">614,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Aspect Ratio">16:09</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/v/u/e/nikon-coolpix-aw110-waterproof-point-shoot-400x400-imadjsazu5knzyhf.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/v/u/e/nikon-coolpix-aw110-waterproof-point-shoot-400x400-imadjsazefzsffzp.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/v/u/e/nikon-coolpix-aw110-waterproof-point-shoot-400x400-imadjsazvxywdwbw.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/v/u/e/nikon-coolpix-aw110-waterproof-point-shoot-400x400-imadjsazabz9g6sn.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="subimg">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/v/u/e/nikon-coolpix-aw110-waterproof-point-shoot-400x400-imadjsazu5knzyhf.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img_id">Nikon Coolpix AW110 Waterproof Point &amp; Shoot Camera (Silver)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Sanket Shah</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">May 6, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Awesome</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">This is a great point and shoot camera for the novice people who like to play it rough. - It works very well underwater and I took some videos using it during scuba diving. It doesn't provide an extensive mounting like GoPro camera's which come at about same price but works well if you can carry it around. - The GPS works well saving EXIF data into images which make upload online a breeze but will creep you out on your privacy. So use GPS only if you want others to know your location. The Maps are quite helpful. - The wifi doesn't connect to existing wifi networks but makes one of its own and lets your smartphone connect to it to take images from a distance. This is a useful feature but don't be mislead by wifi here.- The pouch is not that great but works ok.- The screen works well in shade and sunlight and is big enough to give you a good display.- Some menus are tough to navigate specially to change modes.All in all, a good buy for people looking for something that will survive tough weathers like treks in monsoon, underwater imagery, biking etc. Only problem is to find a secure way to mount it.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">RAMAN ADHIKARY</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">May 21, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">NICON COOL PIX AW110</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						YES IT'S WATER PROOF, CAMERA FEATURES ARE GREAT , CAMERA ARE GOOD IN UNDER WATER AND NORMAL .BUT THE UNDER WATER VIDEO QUALITY IS A LITTLE BIT LOW ,RELAY HARDY AND SHAKE PROOF.BATTERY  DEPENDS ON WEATHER CONDITION.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Mathew Peedikayil</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">May 8, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Cool underwater videos and pics and 240 fps videos</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						This little Nikon Camera is perfect for any weather and also for underwater photography and videos. The battery lasts over a week with average use. The underwater videos are great. As a still camera it does fumble especially when trying to macro focus. It can take video at 60, 120 and 240 fps, though for a limited time, and needs very bright lighting for the faster frame rates. So indoors or in the evenings you may not see anything if you shoot at 240 fps.Makes a great gift for your kids. Virtually indestructible!
</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Harisankar Kumar</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">May 7, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Good Product For the price</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Good one, the only problem is the battery, very low quantity, if u use flash... i recommend u to buy 2 or 3 if u r planning for a long night photographs. other than, it is good
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Nitin Mittal</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Apr 1, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">So far so good..</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Took it on a holiday.. read it Beach Holiday.. didn't exploit it much.. was scared by my first time diving experience, hence relied on the experts camera.. need to test real underwater capabilities.. did submerge it under a feet deep in sea water.. took clear pics.. fingers crossed..
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Joel Miranda</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Mar 15, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">GOOD CAMERA NIKON COOLPIX AW110</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Excellent camera for underwater shots ... amazing video recording. Sturdy excellent features. The delivery took longer than expected but ...the flipkart customer care were very helpful . 
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">AJAY KUMAR</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">2</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 11, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">POOR IMAGES</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Picture Quality is very poor. Please only purchase this product if you really needs to take under water images.
				</specsKey>
</root>