<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix L24 Point &amp; Shoot Camera (Silver)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Silver</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.067</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 5,069</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/2000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">14 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Glass Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">TTL Contrast Detection</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">6.7 - 24.0 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 37 - 134 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">3.6x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">182 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">96.7 (W) x 60.5 (H) x 28.3 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">640 x 480</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Camera, Camera Strap AN-CP19, LR6/L40 (AA-size), Alkaline Batteries, USB Cable UC-E6, View NX 2 CD, User Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point &amp; Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">Coolpix L24</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Silver</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with Red-eye Reduction, Flash Off, Fill Flash, Slow Sync</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Range">0.5 - 7.0 m (W), 0.5 - 3.0 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F/3.1 F/6.7</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 0.7 fps (upto 3 Shots)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">Auto (Auto Gain ISO 80 - 1600)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto, Preset Manual, Daylight, Incandescent, Fluorescent, Cloudy, Flash</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto Mode, Scene Modes, Easy Auto Mode, Smart Portrait Mode, Movie Mode</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">Yes, 5 cm (W)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">26</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">256 Segment Matrix Metering, Center Weighted Metering, Spot Metering</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Additional Features">Shutter Speed: 4 sec (when Scene Mode is Set to Fireworks Show), Lens Construction: 6 Elements in 5 Groups, Autofocus (AF) Focus-area Selection (Center and Face Detection), Min Focus Range: 30 cm (W) - 70 cm (T), Focus Lock, Monitor Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode): (98% Horizontal and 98% Vertical), Monitor Frame Coverage (Playback Mode): 100% Horizontal, Exposure Control (Programmed Auto Exposure with Motion Detection), Exposure Compensation ( 2.0 EV in increments of 1/3 EV), Exposure Modes (Programmed Auto), Scene Modes (Back Light, Beach / Snow, Close Up, Copy, Dusk / Dawn, Fireworks Show, Food, Landscape, Museum, Night Portrait, Panorama Assist, Party / Indoor, Portrait, Sports, Sunset), In-Camera Image Editing (Crop, D-lighting, Small Picture), Shutter (Mechanical and Charge-coupled Electronic Shutter), Built-in Flash Control (TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Preflashes), Interface Data Transfer Protocol (MTP, PTP)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4320 x 3240 (14 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto Mode, Scene Modes, Easy Auto Mode, Smart Portrait Mode, Movie Mode</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG, EXIF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">AVI Movie JPEG Compliant</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">AA Alkaline Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Operating System">Windows 7</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">17 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/y/y/k/nikon-coolpix-l24-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqnpgbyuz2g.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/y/y/k/nikon-coolpix-l24-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqe3g2jnnwe.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/y/y/k/nikon-coolpix-l24-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqhwtnhfzff.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/y/y/k/nikon-coolpix-l24-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqqjbme6taq.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Ankur Agarwal</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 13, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Amazing quality &amp; value for your cash.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						The picture quality is extremely good. Nice value for money, quite handy too. Zoom works wonderful.My experience about it is really awesome. Even the battery life for this camera is nice.I would surely recommend to all the users who are looking for a 14MP camera in 5-6K range, when compared to Sony or Canon.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Nilesh Kumar</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 28, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">A GREAT Deal</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">A very beautiful camera. The red color of the camera is very attractive. It takes very clean shots. The display is quite larger than others, very fast processing feature. The great things are the freebie gifts we are getting with this product. We are getting four batteries(two rechargeable with a charger, and two non rechargeable), the D'signer Pen is very nice although the watch is not attractive. One more thing is that its speaker is not good. We don't get a good sound while we are playing movies taken with this. Overall I recommend anyone to buy this product. If you are looking for a good megapixel camera then prefer this rather than Sony's or Canon's.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">vikas prateek</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 6, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">value for price</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						i got this camera from flipkart and got it on the third day.i had good expirience with this.some pros and cons are:pros:1.it has a good resolution2.it has an efficient flash3.it has a great screen4.it is easy to use5.it is the best camera in this rangecons:1.it is quite bulky as compared to cameras of these days2.the battery backup it not so efficient3.it has optical zoom of 3.6X only but it goes to 10X digitally but it affects qualityoverall it is the best camera if you dont want to spend a lot of money
</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Arun Kamble</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jul 12, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nikon L24 my Rewieve</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Hi I have purchase Nikon L24 online.Just couple of time i used this camera &amp; i face battery leakage problem &amp; camera is unusable , i reported in Nikon service center but after week got reply they unable to rectified &amp; saying it is not covered in warranty &amp; helplessThanks..
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">pavankisna</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Mar 5, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">FULL SATISFACTION AND PRICE OF U'R MONEY </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						very beautiful camera.Nice value for money, quite handy too.It is very easy to use.The pictures are good &amp; camera is worth the money paid .Comming to recording,recording  feature has no pause option. One can record only in a single shot without pausing. The D'signer watch is attractive.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">sanjit kumar</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">3</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 26, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Good Camera but..??</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						It is a good camera..nice picture quality. No doubt I am enjoying with this camera...but recording feature has no pause option. One can record only in a single shot without pausing. If you stop or pause the recording, then it complete one file and can not continue again with recording. Not good for recording purpose but Amazing for picture quality.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Biju Isaac (Cochin)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 26, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nice  camera  with free gifts !!!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						 This is first time that I purchase goods other than books from Flipkart. The camera is good . Got Deepavali free gifts like designer watch &amp; free memory card. The pictures are good &amp; camera is worth the money paid . Slightly  thicker than new generation cameras.I shall give 8 marks out of 10 for this camera.Thanks for Flipkart for excellent service !
				</specsKey>
</root>