<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix S9500 Advanced Point & Shoot Camera (Red)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Red</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.524</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 17,055</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/1500 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">18 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Resolution">3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), 640 x 480 (VGA), 4864 x 2736 (16:9,13 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">4.5 - 99 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 25 - 550 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">22x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">205 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">110.1 (W) x 60.3 (H) x 30.7 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">Wide Viewing Angle OLED Monitor with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">614,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Aspect Ratio">16:09</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL12 (with Terminal Cover), Reference Manual CD, Camera Strap, Audio Video Cable EG-CP16, Charging AC Adapter EH-70P, USB Cable UC-E6, ViewNX 2 CD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Advanced Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">S9500</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Red</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Range">0.5 - 6.0 m (W), 1.5 - 3.5 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F3.4 - F6.3 (W)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 5 Shots at 7.5 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">ISO 125 - 1600, ISO 3200 (Auto Mode)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene Auto Selector, Scene</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Picture Angle">25 mm Wide-angle</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto, Cloudy, Daylight, Flash, Fluorescent, Incandescent, Preset Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">Yes, 1 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="HDMI">Type D, Micro HDMI Output</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">32</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Additional Features">18.91 Total Megapixels, 12 Elements in 10 Groups (1 ED Lens Element), Digital Zoom Magnification (2200 mm Lens in 35 mm (135) Format), Motion Blur Reduction (Motion Detection (Still Pictures)), Focus-area Selection (Face Priority, Center, Manual with 99 Focus Areas, Subject Tracking, Target Finding AF), Min Focus Range: 50 cm (W) - 1.5 m (T), 5 Level Brightness Adjustment, Focus Lock, Shooting Mode Monitor Frame Coverage (98% Horizontal, 98% Vertical), Playback Mode Monitor Frame Coverage (100% Horizontal, 100% Vertical), Recording Reslution (HD: 1280 x 720p at 30 fps, HS: 1280 x 720 at 60 fps, 640 x 480 at 120 fps, 320 x 240 at 24 fps, iFrame: 960 x 540 at 30 fps), Voice Memo Function, Exposure Control (Programmed Auto Exposure, Exposure Compensation), Exposure Modes (Programmed Auto), Scene Modes (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Night Landscape, Night Portrait, Backlighting, Special Effects, Smart Portrait), In-camera Image Editing (Crop, Data Imprint, D-lighting, Glamour Retouch, Quick Effects, Quick Retouch, Small Picture), Exposure Compensation: 2 EV in incremetns of 1/3 EV, Mechanical and CMOS Electronic Shutter, Shutter Speed: 1/4000 - 1/120 sec (Continuous H: 120 fps) 1/4000 - 1/60 sec (Continuous H: 60 fps) 4 sec (Fireworks Show Scene Mode), Aperture (Electronically Controlled ND Filter (-2.0 AV) Insertion), TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Preflashes, Interface Data Transfer Protocol (MTP, PTP), HDMI Output (Auto, 480p, 720p, 1080i), Charging Time (3 hrs 50 mins When Using EH-70P Battery Charger), 230 Shots Battery Life, Tripod Socket (1/4, ISO 1222), Operating Temperature: 0 - 40° C, Operating Humidity: 85%, Wireless LAN (IEEE 802.11b/g/n (Standard Wireless LAN Protocol), ARIB STD-T66 (Standard for Low Power Data Communications Systems), Communications Protocols (IEEE 802.11b: DBPSK, DQPSK, CCK IEEE 802.11g: OFDM IEEE 802.11n: OFDM), Range (Line of Sight): 30 m (32 yd) (Varies with Location), Operating Frequency (2412 - 2462 MHz (1 - 11 Channels)), Data Rates (Actual Measured Values): IEEE 802.11b: 5 Mbps IEEE 802.11g: 12 Mbps IEEE 802.11n: 12 Mbps, Security (Open / WPA2), Access Protocols (CSMA / CA), Electronic Compass (16 Cardinal Points (Position Correction Using 3-axis Acceleration Sensor, Automatic Correction for the Deviated Angle and Automatic Offset Adjustment), Built-in GPS (Receiver Frequency 1575.42 MHz (C/A Code), Geodetic System WGS 84), Continuous Shooting (Single (Default Setting), Continuous L (31 Images at 1.9 fps), Pre-shooting Cache (12 fps / 25 Frames), Continuous H: 120 fps (50 Frames at the Speed of 1/120 sec or Faster), Continuous H: 60 fps (25 Frames at the Speed of 1/60 sec or Faster), Best Shot Selector, Multi-shot 16)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4896 x 3672 (18 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene Auto Selector, Scene</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG, MPO, DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF, MPF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">WAV, AAC Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">MOV, H.264 / MPEG-4 AVC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">23 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/b/a/m/nikon-coolpix-s9500-advance-point-and-shoot-400x400-imadgznjzgvrahgh.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/b/a/m/nikon-coolpix-s9500-advance-point-and-shoot-400x400-imadgznjhddyrfep.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/b/a/m/nikon-coolpix-s9500-advance-point-and-shoot-400x400-imadgznjf6h5bxfy.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/b/a/m/nikon-coolpix-s9500-advance-point-and-shoot-400x400-imadgznjxvpahzzy.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/b/a/m/nikon-coolpix-s9500-advance-point-and-shoot-400x400-imadgznjgwzsaaee.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Girish Krishnamurthy</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jul 27, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nikon S9500 is a very good/advanced camera, but...</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I purchased this one month ago. It was very easy to setup. The picture quality is great for normal photography. The 22X zoom is better than any other camera in point-and-shoot category. But the 4X digital zoom is not useful because of heavy pixilation. So if you are buying to shoot wildlife or nature etc., it may not be useful, you are advised to go for digital SLR with appropriate zoom lens.. There are a few things which are irritating-1. The Flash is on left side on top, and when it pops up, our fingers will obstruct it's pop up mechanism, I wish Nikon had put it in the center above the lens.2. The stereo mics are small holes on the top side of the camera which again could get covered with your fingers, wish they were facing the front of the camera, which would be more logical to capture all sound. Being on top, they capture mainly the voice of the person shooting, which is not useful.3. The GPS feature and Compass feature, which interesting are useless for normal photography so maybe S9400 might be better since it's the same camera but without these features and can save some money4. The software for video editing is almost useless, I have still not understood how to use it, while I am not a geek techie, I am fairly IT savvy to learn most software by trial and error. Here I am not even sure how to begin, there is almost no intuitive feature.5. The Panaroma mode, is only at Infinity zoom, so if you take the digital image and try to zoom in on the image on your computer, you see heavy pixilation.But overall, it is best in class product you can get at this price point.. Most average consumers will not be unhappy with this product. Only those who are looking for some wildlife zooming might be a bit disappointed.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Mandar Kadekar</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 17, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nikon coolpix: Its a cool pics......... :)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I got this camera yesterday.Its awesome camera...Photo quality is awesome.There is only one probs is that the flash.This camera is no use for left handlers. The 22X zoom is very good.Well its a nikon so dont worry about colors & image clarity.The well-priced Nikon Coolpix S9500 has an impressive zoom range for its size and weight. It has a full assortment of automatic shooting options and can capture HD movies as well as slow-motion clips. Built-in Wi-Fi allows you to directly send photos from the camera to iOS or Android devices.With its long lens and compact size, plus extras like built-in Wi-Fi and GPS, the Nikon Coolpix S9500 is a very good point-and-shoot travel companion.Picture quality:Picture quality is good to very good.Detail is very good at its base ISO, By the time you get to ISO 800, subjects start to look soft and flat and colors start to look dull.There's a Fixed Range Auto option that will limit you to ISO 125-400 or ISO 125-800; I recommend using the former outdoors and latter indoors when possible.& Its is a higher end camera in coolpix series now...So guys its a very good camera..... </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Arjun Malhotra</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Apr 9, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Needs a little improvement</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Pros - Great Specs          Really Small          Great Quality imagesCons - The pop up flash is placed at the wrong position. It should have been in the centre.           Adds too much of saturation ( turns images yellowish ) but only if you click the           image without flash.            Focusing is faulty sometimes. The green box comes but the object stays out of focus.I'd recommend this camera for daily use. 
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Manohar Jazzy</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">3</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 31, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">your price of NIKON S9500 is more than market </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I have purchased NIKON S9500 from Muzaffarpur, BIHAR at Rs16,500.00 only(sixteen thousand and five hundred).but flipkart is selling at Rs17,055.00overall this S9500 is great camera for personal use.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">amarpreet singh singh</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 11, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">love this take it without a blink.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						love this the 22x optical zoom is awesome and works like charm. the image quality is superb. always consider the silver colour because it gives the camera a luxury and levish look but hte other three colours are waste of money.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Aritra Banerjee</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 16, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nikon Coolpix s9500 is very Delicated, Usefull, and Coolest gadget....Use it well .. (^_^)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						This camera is awesome .. 22x Zoom is better. In Short it's one of the Good, handful, and Updated camera..
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Aravindh Raaj Velayutham</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">May 1, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nikon coolpix the real pix </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Nikon 9500 , this gadget i purchased before 5 days . the handling is been in good touch . the image clarity brights good ,only probs is that the flash elevation should have been above the lens . If u want to have Nikon cool pix , go for this ..
				</specsKey>
</root>