<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix L25 Point & Shoot Camera (White)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">White</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.386</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 4,176</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">10.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">4.0 - 20.0 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 28 - 140 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">5x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">171 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">96.2 (W) x 60.4 (H) x 29.2 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc. less</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Aspect Ratio">16:09</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">LR6/L40 (AA-size) Alkaline Batteries (x2), Camera Strap, ViewNX 2 Installer CD, USB Cable UC-E16, Reference Manual CD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">L25</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">White</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Range">0.3 - 4.2 m (W), 0.6 - 1.6 m (T) (ISO Auto)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F2.7 - F6.8</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 1.2 fps up to 4 Images</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">Auto (Auto Gain) ISO 80 to 1600</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Picture Angle">28 mm Wide-angle</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Easy Auto, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party, Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk, Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">Yes, 3 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">27</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">256-segment Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">3648 x 2736 (High)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Easy Auto, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party, Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk, Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG, DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">AVI (Motion-JPEG)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Power Supply">AC Adapter EH-65A (Sold Separately)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">20 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/n/c/7/nikon-l25-400x400-imad73hphavazuxf.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/n/c/7/nikon-l25-400x400-imad73hr8ehgsg7y.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/n/c/7/nikon-l25-400x400-imad73srsftkaybz.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="subimg">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/n/c/7/nikon-l25-400x400-imad73hphavazuxf.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img_id">Nikon Coolpix L25 Point & Shoot Camera (White)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Raj Bhavya</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 28, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Awesome!!!!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Gr8 camera for its price....good picture quality....gr8 HD video recording...compared it to my canon...far better then it in all respects...better lens, better finish, sturdy build quality, good flash, good battery life...easy to use, gr8 modes...ideal for persons new in photography... all in all gr8 deal by nikon and flipkart!!!
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Ashish Behera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Apr 5, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Very good camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						For the price it is a very good camera. It supports 720p video recording which is a rarity in this price range. Compared to other cameras, this camera definitely has more features. The ease of use is what made me buy it. It is to be used by my younger sister who is still in College and thus, she wanted a sassy easy to use camera. This fits all the criteria (in red color too) and finally the price is very enticing.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Debashis Nath</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">May 20, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">A Very Good Camera in its Range</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						A very good camera for regular use, official photography use and for new photographers. Clarity is excellent for 10.1 megapixel even in zooming to some extent. Options available to choose your pixel size thus adjusting memory consumption while saving. Video recording is average. However, clicks in poor light conditions is not very satisfactory. Another drawback is the use of AA Batteries for power. But the same has been compensated with free gift of two rechargeable batteries alongwith the charger. 
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Sourav Kundu</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 13, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">What else at this Price Tag</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						An amazing beginner's snapping machine topped with the creamy service from Flipkart, really loved it!!You can expect to get value for each penny spent, be it the design, looks, user friendly buttons and menu’s and last but not the least the picture quality. If you are planning to give a kick start to your little hobby of freezing time through a lens, I bet, this is you tool.The built is a bit fragile and the display is a bit noisy, in spite, you won’t find a matching piece with such featured packed and looks at this price tag.
</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">kartikay</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 7, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">excellent product</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						this camera is totally worth for money. before purchasing i have compared around 8 cameras but i found only this one the more efficient at my budget.this is good one for those who are fond of photography.
</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">ankush agnihotri</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jun 25, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">ankush</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Gr8 camera for its price....good picture quality....gr8 HD video recording...compared it to my sony...far better then it in all respects...better lens, better finish, good flash, good battery life...easy to usegr8 deal by nikon and flipkart!!!
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Bobby Raju</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jun 5, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">awesome!!!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						firstly..,kudos 2 d flipkart team for excellent delivery service... d camera was delivered within 24hrs of ordering...very impressedfor somethin dat costs just 4.8k.,dis small cam blows ur mind away...image quality is very good,...although indoor images r grainy,..can still be fixed using flash mode(n other options)d various modes provided r easy 2 use n delivers good quality imagesimage quality ISN'T affected much even upon zooming...overall a wonderful camera.... a must buy for starters who r taking baby steps into d world of photography.....delighted!!!!!
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Md Mustafizur Rahman (Pintu)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 4, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Greatly Bad Camera In this World</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I purchase this camera,But picture quality is so poor,& also poor Zoom.Red eye is unavailable,that is used in night.I suggest you,Plz...Do not purchase this camera....My Best camera is 1)Nikon coolpix S3300 (RS.6600) &  2)Sony DSC-W690(RS.8200).
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Mridul Malgudi</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 20, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nice Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Its very nice camera i just buy it last sunday. Its picture quality is gr8. Its video Recording is also gr8. I like this Camera and avice people to buy this camera if they want to buy camera.It has lots of things like hd video recording,anti flicker,and many more things
</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">RamakrishnaVidhatha A</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 1, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Very Bad Product</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Flipkart was good in delivering the product within 2 days but Iam Completly disappointed with Nikon...Worst product...ONLY CONS:_Very poor lensvery poor image qualityBlur Images without flashPoor Zoom andworst Battery....Please do'nt buy....Did'snt expect a product like this from Flipkart and Nikon...
				</specsKey>
</root>