<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon D700 DSLR Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 120,854</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/8000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB 2.0</specsKey>
<specsKey name="PictBridge">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Camera Body, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL3e, Quick Charger MH-18a, USB Cable UC-E4, Video Cable EG-D100, Camera Strap AN-D700, Body Cap BF-1A, Accessory Shoe Cover BS-1, LCD Monitor Cover BM-9, Software Suite CD-ROM, User Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">D700</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes, Pop-up</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">TTL, i-TTL Balanced Fill-flash, Auto Aperture, Non TTL Auto, Distance-priority Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="External Flash">Yes, (Hot-shoe, Wireless Plus Sync Connector)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">Full Frame</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Format">36.0 x 23.9 mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">12.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Resolution">3184 x 2120 (M), 2128 x 1416 (S), DX Format (2784 x 1848 (L), 2080 x 1384 (M), 1392 x 920 (S))</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">Nikon F Bayonet Mount</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">TTL Phase Detection</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sync Terminal">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 5 fps (Continuous High-speed Mode (CH)), 1 - 5 fps (Continuous Low-speed mode (CL))</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">ISO 200 to 6400 (Steps of 1/3, 1/2, or 1 EV), Low 1 (ISO 100), High 1 (ISO 12800), High 2 (ISO 25600)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto (2 Type), Auto (TTL White-balance with 2016-pixel RGB Sensor), Cloudy, Direct Sunlight, Fine Tune by Kelvin Color Temperature Setting (2500 K - 10000 K), Flash, Flourescent (7 Type), Incandescent, Preset Manual, 7 Manual Modes with Fine-tuning, Shade</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Single Frame Shooting Mode, Continuous High-speed Mode (5 fps), Continuous Low-speed Mode (1 - 5 fps), Live View Mode, Self-timer Mode, Mirror-up Mode</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="HDMI">Type C Mini HDMI</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">15</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">3D-Color Matrix Metering II, Color Matrix Metering II, Color Matrix Metering, Center-weighted</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Additional Features">12.87 Total Megapixels, LCD Monitor (170° Wide-viewing Angle, 100% Frame Coverage), Playback Function (Full-frame, Thumbnail (4, 9 Images) Playback with Playback Zoom, Slide Show, Histogram Display, Highlight Display, Auto Image Rotation, Image Comment (upto 36 Characters), Delete Function (Card Format, All Frames Delete, Selected Frames Delete, 1.5x Focal Length (Picture Angle (35 mm (135) Format Equivalent), Focusing Screen (Type B BriteView Clear Matte VI), Viewfinder Frame Coverage (5% Horizontal and 95% Vertical, 0.72x Maganificatin (50 mm Lens at Infinity, -1.0 m-1)), Autofocus (51 Focus Points by Nikon Multi-CAM 3500FX Autofocus Module, Detection Range: -1 to EV (ISO 100 at 20° C/68° F)), Focus Modes (Single-servo AF (AF-S), Continuous-servo AF, Manual Focus), Exposure Metering System (Color Matrix Metering II (Other CPU Lenses), Color Matrix Metering (Non-CPU Lenses If User Provides Lens Data), Center-weighted: Weight of 75% Given to 8-, 12-, 15- or 20-mm Circle in Center of Frame, Spot: Meters 4.0 mm Circle (about 1.5% Frame) Centered on Selected Focus Point (On Center Focus Area when Non-CPU Lens is Used), Exposure Control (Programmed Auto (P) with Flexible Program, Shutter Priority Auto (S), Aperture Priority Auto (A), Manual (M)), Auto Exposure Lock (Luminosity Locked at Detected Value with AE-L / AF-L Button), Auto Exposure Bracketing ( 5 in increments of 1/3, 1/2 or 1 EV), Shutter (Electronically-controlled Vertical-travel Focal-plane Shutter), Flash Control (TTL, i-TTL Balanced Fill-flash, Auto Aperture, Non-TTL Auto, Distance-priority Manual, Accessory Shoe (Standard ISO 518 Hot-shoe Contact with Safety Lock), Depth of Field Preview Button, Remote Control (Via 10-pin Remote Cord MC-22/30/36 (Optional)), GPS (GPS: NMEA 0183 (Ver. 2.01 and 3.01) Interface Standard), Supported Languages (Chinese (Simplified and Traditional), Dutch, English, Finnish, French, German, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Polish, Portuguese, Russian, Spanish, Swedish), 1000 Shots Battery Life (Fully Charged)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4256 x 2832 (L)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Single Frame Shooting Mode, Continuous High-speed Mode (5 fps), Continuous Low-speed Mode (1 - 5 fps), Live View Mode, Self-timer Mode, Mirror-up Mode</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">NEF (RAW) 12, TIFF (RGB), JPEG, NEF (RAW)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">995 g (without Battery, Memory Card or Body Cap)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">147 (W) x 123 (H) x 77 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body & lens.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Operating System">Windows Vista</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">Compact Flash (Type I, Compliant with UDMA)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">Low-temperature Polysilicon TFT LCD with Brightness Adjustment</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">920,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Viewfinder">Fixed Eye-level Pentaprism</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ViewFinder">Fixed Eye-level Pentaprism</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/x/g/b/nikon-d700-slr-400x400-imadyh8ujvxfwrgx.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/x/g/b/nikon-d700-slr-400x400-imacxmkgpgp8c9tg.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/x/g/b/nikon-d700-slr-400x400-imadg2vcg83tg8hs.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/x/g/b/nikon-d700-slr-400x400-imadg2vca5gghuqk.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/x/g/b/nikon-d700-slr-400x400-imadg2vccarfhwwh.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/x/g/b/nikon-d700-slr-400x400-imacxmkr8huzc4vr.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Swarup Roy</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Aug 17, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">the best camera ever made..better than D800</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Awesome Camera!What i like about this camera:1. Focusing2. The look and feel of the photos (can't be explained)3. Co lours coming out of it!!!4. The FPS rate5. No, i'am not taking about the ISO6. great MP for user like me who just take photos for myself and upload it to my website.
</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Rajeev Kohli</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 5, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">D700 from Flipkart</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">Got a very good deal at Flipkart - 126k body plus 70-300 G lens.Terrific performance. Very low noise - goes to ISO 6400 with good results. Better to shoot RAW at high ISO and PP for noise reduction. Out of camera Jpegs are also very good.Good white balance.Its 12 Megapixel full frame sensor is exceptional.Nothing better than this for the serious amateur.Use with good quality lens (suggest Nikon only) for best results.CONS -Mirror slap is noisy (you get used to it after some time)Uses CF cards. - Suggest you buy 2 No's 8 or 16GB UDMA CF cards which should see you through most shoots.</specsKey>
</root>