<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix P500 (Red)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Red</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.733</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 19,484</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">Coolpix P500</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Red</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/m/z/f/nikon-p500-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqjrwgpsxrm.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/m/z/f/nikon-p500-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq7tmgtwfbs.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/m/z/f/nikon-p500-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqc2jdskpgf.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/m/z/f/nikon-p500-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqnerkv3ahd.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/m/z/f/nikon-p500-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq7r6w6gwnw.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/m/z/f/nikon-p500-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq7uh6hzzsz.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="subimg">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/m/z/f/nikon-p500-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqjrwgpsxrm.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img_id">Nikon Coolpix P500 (Red)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">DR. MADAN GOPAL AGARWAL</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Sep 9, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">FULL SATISFACTION AND PRICE OF U'R MONEY</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">With a zoom that's both remarkably wide and extremely long, the Nikon P500 exceeds all expectations in a long zoom digital camera with only a few optical compromises. This is the camera you grab when you don't want to heft the SLR and a bag full of lenses.The Nikon P500 takes only 1.5 seconds to power on and take a shot. That's very fast for an ultra-zoom camera.Full autofocus shutter lag is very fast, at 0.158 second at wide angle and 0.119 second at full telephoto; faster than most DSLRs. Prefocused shutter lag is 0.012 second, which is excellent.The camera's AF system was able to focus down to just above the 1/4 foot-candle light level without AF assist, though the camera was able to focus in complete darkness with the AF assist lamp enabled.Connected to a computer or printer with USB 2.0, the Nikon Coolpix P500's download speeds are moderately fast. We measured 4,942 KBytes/sec.SO ENJOY KEEPING THIS WONDERFULL GADGET</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Shanti Swaroop Swain</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 7, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Awesome Camera. Loved It :)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">Loved this camera. As usual, flipkart service was great and packaging was very good. Received the product exactly on the date expected (on my birthday). So here is my experience with this camera.This camera is great if u can use it properly. U need to knows the settings and the environment so as to adjust your camera to get the best picture quality. It even takes awesome pics in low light conditions. I read a lot of reviews and found a number of bad reviews regarding this product. But still I bought it as it was the best in my budget.Now I am glad I didnt believe those reviews. Time for Pros and cons.Pros : 1) Great camera, great build, stable.2) Fast startup, max 2 seconds. Very less time lag between flash charge.3) Low light pictures are great with proper camera settings.4) Normal light pictures are quite great. Well u cant expect SLR type picture quality. But still its very crisp and clear.5) Battery life is good too. Was able to take around 250 pics one day, although I was saving battery by using the viewfinder most of the time and flash only when required.6) Video recording is ultimate. The quality is too good. Only problem is shaking, but i think that can be solved using a tripod.7) U'll surely love the super zoom. Just reduce the shaking and u can take extremely nice close ups.Cons:1) Still photography in low light is great, but if the subject is moving or in case of disco lights, taking gud pictures becomes a little difficult.2) In low light, u need to wait a couple of seconds before u can shoot another picture. I don't know why it waits, but it doesn't starts focusing immediately after a pic is taking.3) High Speed video recording is a mystery to me still. I dont know why I am not able to take good videos in it. When I try to take videos, the videos are very dark. But in the same conditions, the HD video is great.4) charging of fully exhausted battery takes around 5 hours or more.It has been only 15 days since I purchased it, and I haven't faced any technical problems yet. I hope I don't face any.In a nut shell, if u are good with camera settings u can take ultimate pictures with this camera. This is the best point and shoot camera providing SLR features ... </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">manik batalvi</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Sep 28, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Amazing</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						The decision to buy Nikon P500 was taken after a long research. Wanted to buy a SLR but the simplicity of this camera caught my eye. Its so easy to use and the results are really good.This was my first major order through Flipkart. Earlier orders were books and DVDs only. So i was  a little apprehensive to be honest.The camera was deliverd to me in three days in pristine condition with everything  as listed on the site. Got a 2 GB  Go Gear USB player with it for free.Kudos to Flipkart Team .
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Rohit Dhawan</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 29, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Packs a punch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">PROSUltra Zoom is great.Full HD Recording.Slow Motion Recording.Ease of use.Excellent burst mode shooting.Macro mode is highly impressive.Variety of shooting modes and scenes.Good for its price.CONSGets grainy in Telephoto zoom.Battery runs out of juice quickly.Camera freezes if turned on with lens hood.Can't click pictures in video mode (compared to other camera).Noisy when zooming during video capture.Picture quality mediocre in low light.In my opinion, this camera is worth money but you will have to spend a little extra on another battery. Picture quality is quite impressive. Buy it if you do not want to carry a Handycam and a camera together. It is a great tool combines in one.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Adithya Das</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 27, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Amazing!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">Simply superb. i bought this camera after months of deliberation and almost went in for a nikon DSLR,but this stopped me in my tracks.. great wide angle and even better telephoto (albeit with a bit of chromatic aberration at 1:1).with this cam i was assured of any pic i ever wanted. video is great @1080p and the stereo sound recording is exquisite. a bit distortion when taking closeup pics.(to be expected from this sort of lens).but that counts for nothing.. great macro and in camera editing options.. but keep at least a 32GB card and a spare battery handy for trips or events..runs out of juice a bit faster than your typical cybershot..MUST BUY FOR A SERIOUS NON PRO Photographer </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Abhishek Verma</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 25, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">NIKON P 500 is magical,magnificent.... What a camera !!!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">Well, must I say , it took about 20 days of intensive research, comparison, guidance from some of the good known photographers in the city as well as reviews from youtube and other internet sites including Flipkart, for finalizing this amazing camera called NIKON P 500 !! what a camera..!, what a performance !!...what a zooooom !!!I am really impressed with its features which even beats , sometimes the close SLRs/DSLRs also ...( i know few of you may have your eyebrow raised on this comment , but trust me... I have taken few snaps with N P 500 as well as a DSLR and found both to be at par)The red color adds spice.smooth functioning is a plus plus.Very small two issues ( being an honest reviewer, I must add here) :(1) the display is adjustable... which is ok for photography but it should have that swing/rotation effect in CANON SX40s..(2) deleting the unwanted snaps is a tedious affair, especially the selection is a bit time consuming and confusing.But rest, This is a 9.5/10 camera ! Go for it.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Jason Samuel</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 11, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Great Product:-)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I was looking for a SLR when this Cam caught my eye.The features offered are pretty high and to-operate its pretty simple.Not to mention the weight...its damn light compared with SONY HX100V(the only match in its category).P500 stands out due to its wide viewing angle (handy in sight-seeing locations).Thanks to Flipkart for their great service and the prompt delivery!Wish they bring-in more product categories:-P
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Biswajeet Patra</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 29, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Superb Camera....</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I have used this camera....its having superb functionality and features.Its 36x zooming performance is too good, I have just taken this camera from one of my friend for few days.I just love this camera, Now I also planning to buy one butI cant spent tht much amount at once and i also dont have credit card, i only hve debit card and i wanna pay whole amount in 6 installment or Post dated cheque. But as per Flipcart.com its not possible, so this is my problem but This camera is Superb once again.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Jondeep Das</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 11, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">p500</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">The Nikon Coolpix p500 is really a nice camera.the main advantage of this camera is the 36x optical zoom which enables us to reach clearly then our eye.i think the price of the camera is much less in comparison to the features of the camera.It has dual image processor,CMOS technology,Red eye reduction etc.i found the camera to satisfactory up to the full extent.it is suitable for those who wants much clear image and full hd videos and who doesnot want to carry a huge DSLR with the extra lenses.I have been discovering a new function daily in the camera.it has lots of features.so those who are planning or in doubt to buy it should buy it with out any tension.in my openion the camera doesnot have any disadvantages. </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Mandeep Singh</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 22, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Good Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Camera with cool feature, using it for last 6 months no issues. Only problem is with high zoom when you need a more stable hand though the image stabilizer is available but still it takes time to get a clear image.
				</specsKey>
</root>