<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon D300s DSLR Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.909</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 79,004</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/8000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 Sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">USB 2.0</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Camera Body, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL3e, Quick Charger MH-18a, USB Cable UC-E4, Video Cable EG-D2, Strap AN-DC4, LCD monitor cover BM-8, Body cap, Eyepiece Cap DK-5, Rubber Eyecup DK-23, Software Suite CD-ROM, Power Cable, Accessory shoe cover BS-1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">D300s</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Front curtain, Rear curtain, Red-Eye, Slow, Red-Eye Slow</specsKey>
<specsKey name="External Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">APS-C</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">12.3 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Resolution">3216 x 2136, 2144 x 1424</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">Nikon F mount</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">TTL phase detection, 51 focus points (15 cross-type sensors) by Nikon Multi-CAM 3500DX autofocus module; Detection -1 to EV (ISO 100 at 20C/68F)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">1.5x lens focal length</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Picture Angle">Approx. 1.5x lens focal length</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">3D-Color Matrix Metering II (type G and D lenses); Color Matrix Metering II (other CPU lenses); Color Matrix Metering (non-CPU lenses if user provides lens data), Center-weighted: Weight of 75% given to 8 mm circle in center of frame; Diameter of circle can be changed to 6, 10, or 13 mm, or weighting can be based on average of entire frame (fixed at 8 mm when non-CPU lens is used), Spot: Meters 3.0 mm circle (about 2% of frame) centered on selected focus point (on center focus area when non-CPU lens is used)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sync Terminal">1/200 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Continous low shooting mode: 1-7fps, Continous high shooting mode: 7fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">200 - 3200 in 1, 1/2 or 1/3 EV steps (100 - 6400 with boost)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Single frame shooting mode, Continuous shooting mode: approx. 3fps, Self-timer mode, Quiet Shutter Release</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto (TTL white balance with 1,005-pixel RGB sensor); Incandescent, Fluorescent, Direct sunlight, Flash, Cloudy, Shade, Choose Color temp., White balance preset</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="HDMI">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">17</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4288 X 2848</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Single frame shooting mode, Continuous shooting mode: approx. 3fps, Self-timer mode, Quiet Shutter Release</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">NEF (12 or 14-bit lossless compressed, compressed, or uncompressed RAW), TIFF (RGB), JPEG (Baseline-compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">AVI movie</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Power Supply">EH-5a AC Adapter (Optional)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">840 g</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">147 (W) x 114 (H) x 74 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body & lens.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">CompactFlash (CF) Card (Type I, compliant with UDMA); SD memory card (SDHC compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">1280 x 720</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">Low-temperature Polysilicon TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Viewfinder">Fixed eye-level pentaprism; built-in diopter adjustment (-2.0 to .0 m-)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ViewFinder">Fixed eye-level pentaprism; built-in diopter adjustment (-2.0 to .0 m-)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/8/h/z/nikon-d300s-slr-400x400-imacxmk97ghrp2pq.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/8/h/z/nikon-d300s-slr-400x400-imacxmkzefjfz63d.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/8/h/z/nikon-d300s-slr-400x400-imadg2vmzjpfpkgr.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/8/h/z/nikon-d300s-slr-400x400-imadg2vmnjrkryqk.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/8/h/z/nikon-d300s-slr-400x400-imadg2vmz2khaez6.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="subimg">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/8/h/z/nikon-d300s-slr-400x400-imacxmk97ghrp2pq.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img_id">Nikon D300s DSLR Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Hemant Kulkarni</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 17, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Good body, nice feel good feature set</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I have been using this camera for almost 1.5 years now and it has never disappointed me. I do a lot of nature photography particularly birds/animals and I find the high 7 fps or 8fps in case you use MB10 battery grip to be very useful. The autofocus motor inside the body makes it compatible with lot of lenses viz. AF-S , AF and other lenses for autofocus capability.I have put up approximately 18000 shots on this and the camera is still kicking fine. The camera is made up of magnesium alloy and rubberized exterior gives a great feel to grip it. The body has withstood cold, heat wind and dust. I have shot it from temperature ranging from  -9C to 45C and it never has never complained. This is the best DX sensor camera body available until D400 is announced which Nikon did not do this year. This camera also has some great handy buttons that other DSLR in DX format do not- viz: quicker access to shutter release modes, dedicated white balance button. It also has "mirror up mode" which makes it very useful when shootign with high power lenses such as 800mm super telephoto lens. All in all I'd highly recommend this product to serious enthusiasts. </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Manu Holla</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jun 3, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Camera for Professionals</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I'm writing this review after using this camera for about 1 year. I'm a wedding/event photographer & Videographer. I took nearly 25000 shots using this cam. Overall very good camera. Very impressive colour & sharpness. In terms of colour & depth, I think there is no other compitator for this camera on this range. I had brought with 18 200mm f/3.5 5.6 lens. A very good combination. If you are thinking to buy this, don't think much.But remember, next version D9300 is about to release. which may have lot of improvements.Pros - High speed focus. It focuses very quickly with my 18 200mm lens. Which I love most on this cam & lens.Super colour, sharpness (also in jpeg).Very excellent Video quality in Daylight & Hallogen lights (equivalent to Panasonic AGAC 90) I had tried to mix the video's of D300s and Sony NX 5, you can't say which result is from which camera at first sight. Cons - Very poor ISO performance. I think my old D80 stands good in ISO performance compared to this. You cant go after ISO 1250 in RAW & ISO 640 in JPEG. Which results in poor quality pics.It gives AVI video Not HD. Ahhhh.. which is soo bad. Since most of my works are on AVI, so it will not bother me lot. but sometimes Yes.One Important thing that I had notised that Battery backup is not good as they have shown. It consumes about 1 and half battery to take around 750 shots in my case.5 stars for its quivk focus, colour, sharpness, quality of the image & Video performance.2 stars for its ISO performance.Thank You</specsKey>
</root>