<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon D5100 DSLR Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 35,260</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">USB 2.0</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">D5100</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL14, Audio Video Cable EG-CP14, USB Cable UC-E6, Eyepiece Cap DK-5, ViewNX 2 CD, Strap AN-DC3, User Manual, Body Cap BF-1B, Camera Body, Battery Charger MH-24, Rubber Eyecup DK-20, Accessory Shoe Cover BS-1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Fill-flash, slow sync, auto slow sync, red-eye reduction, auto with red-eye reduction, slow sync with red-eye reduction, auto, slow sync with red-eye reduction, rear-curtain sync, rear-curtain with slow sync.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">APS-C</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Picture Angle">Approx. 1.5x lens focal length</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">3D color matrix metering II</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sync Terminal">1/200 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Continuous shooting mode: Approx: 4fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">ISO 100 to 6400 in steps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Single frame, Continuous: 4fps, Self-timer, Delayed remote, Quick-response remote, Silent shuttle release, D-Movie.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto (TTL white-balance with main image sensor and 420-pixel RGB sensor), Incandescent, Fluorescent ( 7 types ), Direct, Sunlight, Flash, Cloudy, Shade, preset manual.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="HDMI">HDMI output (Type C mini-pin connector)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">22</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">Nikon F mount</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">TTL phase detection,11 focus points</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16.2 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4928 x 3264 (L)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Single frame, Continuous: 4fps, Self-timer, Delayed remote, Quick-response remote, Silent shuttle release, D-Movie.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">NEF (12 or 14-bit lossless compressed or compressed RAW), JPEG (Baseline-compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">MOV movie (H.264, MPEG-4 AVC compression format with Linear PCM sound; Stereo sound with external microphone)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Power Supply">EH-5a AC Adapter</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">509 g</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">128 (W) x 96.9 (H) x 78.7 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body & lens.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Viewfinder">Eye-level pentamirror</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ViewFinder">Eye-level pentamirror</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/z/h/e/nikon-d5100-dslr-400x400-imadvuvc3aphg5pk.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="subimg">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/2/e/t/nikon-d5100-slr-400x400-imacyd59duzjqj8s.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img_id">Nikon D5100 DSLR Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Manan Ramnani</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">3</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 10, 2015</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">The right body. The wrong Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">The body D5100 is amongst the best a beginner could get. But not the LENS.1. D5100     PROS : i)  Decent Low Light Performance                ii) 11 focus points with 1 cross type (again, its sufficient)               iii)  Ergonomic Design and easy to carry/hold.               iv)  Flip Screen (much needed while shooting videos)    CONS : i)  Has NEF Compression (not good if you are an astrophotographer)                ii) The colours appear mostly neutral and sometimes a bit under-saturated,                     unlike the canon options. (Maybe good / bad, varies on personal opinion)               iii)  A bit under performing than the D5200/D5300, they being a bit costlier may                    seem to be better options to invest in(D5100:if you are hard on budget)2. LENS : Tamron 18-200 f3.5-6.3 Di II (Aspherical)     PROS : i)  The Aspherical Optics - Hence an internal focus system.                 ii)  The range of the complete kit lens + that added telephoto range                 iii)  Good for almost all purposes ( Landscapes/Portraits/Stage )     CONS : i)   A very slow aperture ( min. f3.5 @18mm and f6.3 @200 mm )                 ii)  Slow and Noisy focus motor (Not good for videos at all)                iii)  Tight Zoom Ring (Its very rigid)                iv)  Below Average performance when compared to the nikon counterparts                 v)  No Manual override mode for auto focus                vi)  A bit heavySome of the better options for the lens at this pricing point are :    1. The KIT Lens (18-55mm f/3.5-f/5.6) with VR II (Vibration Reduction) {A decent lens}   2. Nikon Nikkor 55-200 mm with VR ( Not advisable for lanscapes )   3. Nikon 35mm f/1.8g DX ( Good for street photography and potraits )   4. Nikon 50mm f/1.8g DXIf you can have a budget of upto 30k for the lens try going for  TAMRON 17-50mm f/2.8 (Without the VC~26k , with VC ~ 32k)Its the best replacement for the kit lens , since it gives you a fixed f/2.8 aperture all along the zoom length and has a very fast focus performance and also a brilliant colour reproduction. </specsKey>
</root>