<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix L23 Point & Shoot Camera (Red)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Red</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.204</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 4,176</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">10.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Resolution">3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2592 x 1944 (5 M), 2048 x 1536 (3 M), 1024 x 768 (PC), 640 x 480 (VGA), 3584 x 2016 (16:9)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">TTL Contrast Detection</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">4.0 - 20.0 mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">5x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">170 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">96.7 (W) x 59.9 (H) x 29.3 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">640 x 480</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">2.7 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Aspect Ratio">16:09</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="PictBridge">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Camera Strap AN-CP19, LR6/L40 (AA-size) Alkaline Batteries, USB Cable UC-E6, CD, Camera, User Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">Coolpix L23</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Red</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with Red-eye Reduction, Flash Off, Fill Flash, Slow Sync</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/2.9 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F/2.7 F/6.8</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 1.4 fps (upto 4 Shots)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">Auto (Auto Gain ISO 80 - 1600)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto Mode, Scene Modes, Easy Auto Mode, Smart Portrait Mode, Movie Mode</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto, Preset Manual, Daylight, Incandescent, Fluorescent, Cloudy, Flash</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">Yes, 3 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">256 Segment Matrix Metering, Center Weighted Metering, Spot Metering</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">26</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Additional Features">30 mins Video Recording Time, 30 cm Normal Focus Range, Scene Modes (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist), 320 x 240 (QVGA) Video Size, Supported Languages (Arabic, Chinese (Simplified and Traditional), Czech, Danish, Dutch, English, Finnish, French, Greek, German, Hungarian, Indonesian, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Polish, Portuguese, Norwegian, Romanian, Russian, Spanish, Swedish, Thai, Turkish, Ukrainian), 250 Shots (Alkaline Batteries), 660 Shots (Lithium Batteries), 420 Shots (EN-MH2 Batteries (Based on CIPA Standard))</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">3648 x 2736 (10 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto Mode, Scene Modes, Easy Auto Mode, Smart Portrait Mode, Movie Mode</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG, EXIF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">AVI Movie</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">AA Alkaline Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Operating System">Windows 7</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">22 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/9/h/3/nikon-l23-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq39jhqkeeh.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/9/h/3/nikon-l23-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq8z8ph4ggy.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/9/h/3/nikon-l23-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqhhpqdfhcc.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/9/h/3/nikon-l23-point-shoot-400x400-imad4vpzrh9wcnp7.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/9/h/3/nikon-l23-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq6ht8tzjys.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/9/h/3/nikon-l23-point-shoot-400x400-imad4vpz5dryqggh.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/9/h/3/nikon-l23-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqpycfmzwff.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="subimg">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/9/h/3/nikon-l23-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq39jhqkeeh.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img_id">Nikon Coolpix L23 Point & Shoot Camera (Red)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Arun Prakash</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Aug 22, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Gud One...........</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						This is my 4th Online buy from flipkart i got my cam to the very nxt wrkng day itself, i bought this camera for my sister the camera is very sleek and easy to handle and its very simple and the pics are very gud wen compared other models in the same price.The zoom is very excellent and pics which i took in night are as same as dat i took in the day time there are many modes wch we can use and take pics in very diff styles.....8/10 for the product.I got one camera bag,camera pouch,Two rechargeable batteries with charger and a 4GB card im very happy and as usual 10/10 to flipkart.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Neel Bose</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Sep 30, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle"> Brilliant Service from Flipkart</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						 Ordered it on a wednesday at 5.30 am  & got it delivered to      my  address in the afternoon a day later having all the contents in proper order & condition.Well,on coming to the camera I must say that it is one of the most basic ones u get in market but the best too ,,,, changing the properties of the brightness,exposure and other specs is not allowed apart from the presets which aren't too good ... so not a good buy for Pros.Go for a better Cam with more flexiblities. 
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Srinivas</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Sep 22, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">VFM product, fast delivery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						bought this camera as a gift. Great price (and freebies) and super fast delivery by Flipkart. When received, found the SD CARD missing, but rest of the package was in perfect condition. Flipkart had the memory card sent immediately without an fuss upon my request. Overall a good experience. 
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Akshay Sharma</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">2</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 19, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Great zoom..worst image quality</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I have been using this product for more than 6 months now. I didn't purchase this product from Flipkart but thought of writing a review with my experience. Nikon L23 offers a high 5x optical zoom but don't ever go for the zoom to ruin your pictures. Extremely worse quality pics in little low light and indoors. The image stabiliser is almost useless. Takes a lot of effort to take a photo in even 2x zoom,the pic gets distorted almost everytime i take a pic with zoom. Low priced and cool looks but also very low performance. Try not to go for this cam unless you are impressed by its outer looks and pricing.Pros :More zoomCool looksLow priceCons :Extremely bad picture qualityUseless image stabiliserLow mp of 10  </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">sunil</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 3, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Good camera,cheap plastic - Beware</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						At 5k  This camera is good. Nice picture quality  and features.But its made up of low quality plastic. I broke a a tiny chip off the battery covering lid and was told by the service center that I need to pay 3000/- as they need to change entire body ! all this happened within 3 months of buying the camera.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Archanaa Raja</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Mar 27, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Aweeeesssoooommmmeeee!! :)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Hey all, I jus wanna thank FLIPKART for their wonderful services. I ordered n got it delivered in a day. Woooowwww...tats amazing!! :)Abt d Coolpix - its really cool as d name takes it away..too gud for d price u pay...i had gifted it for my parents wedding day...my father had took pics n he loved it totally.....Thank u Nikon! :)Dear Flipkart, I Love U!! :)))
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Bala Amarnath chandrasekaran</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Mar 18, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">***Gud cam for a starter***</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">A good camera for a person who is just entering photography field. Light weight, powered by AA battery, clear display, so many automatic per-programmed function that gives user-friendly touch... Pros:     * Gud model and great value for money as a starter.     * Freebies included Carry-case, charger and rechargeable         battery, memory card, designer watch and pen.Cons:     * optical zoom is only 5X, no other go bcoz in this price        range longer is not possible.     * rechargeable charger and battery is not from Nikon, its        from other company, any have the is good only working        good till now, so user don't expect nikon charger and        battery.Last But Not Least---- Hats off to Flip-kart packaging, its really nicely packed and delivered in-time.. </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">PRASOON SINHA</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 7, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">best for this price range.....</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						picture quality is very good. flesh is awesome for night images.more than 17 modes of operation. zooming feature is quite good. over all a best buy for the price range.if you are not looking for a reliable cam from nikon or canon then this product is the best buy for anything less than 5000...
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Rahul C.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 10, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nice starting range camera....great flipkart support</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Bought this camera as a gift for my sister. The initally shipped camera had some heating problem and the battery drained off when the camera was in switched-off condition. Reported the problem to flipkart and to my great pleasure the guys arranged a replacement in 4-5days to reach me. Really pleased with flipkart. KudosAs for the cam, a nice cam really. Shoots amazing pics though an antiblur mode is seriously missing. An image stabilisation problem is there in pics taken in certain modes esp without flash. Overall rating 5/5 as value for money. Go for it.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Shell</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Sep 28, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Hope its best :)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						just ordered this model for my Mom... hope i would get fast and easy handover and good service... is there any issue cozd vd dis model so far?
				</specsKey>
</root>