<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon D5200 DSLR Camera (Bronze)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Black,Bronze</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.273</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 39,900</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Microphone">Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="PictBridge">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">D5200</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Bronze</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with Red-eye Reduction, Auto Slow Sync, Auto Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Fill-flash, Red-eye Reduction, Slow Sync, Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Rear-curtain with Slow Sync, Rear-curtain Sync, Off</specsKey>
<specsKey name="External Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">APS-C</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">24.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Resolution">4496 x 3000 (M), 2992 x 2000 (S)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color Filter">Primary (RGB) Color Filter</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">Nikon F Mount</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">TTL Phase Detection</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dust Reduction">Image Sensor Cleaning</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">Matrix Metering: 3D Color Matrix Metering II (Type G and D Lenses), Color Matrix Metering II (Other CPU Lenses), Center-weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sync Terminal">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 4 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">ISO 100 - 6400</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto, Incandescent, Fluorescent (7 Types), Direct Sunlight, Flash, Cloudy, Shade, Preset Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Portrait, Child, Close Up, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Pet Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="HDMI">Type C, Mini HDMI</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">26</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Additional Features">24.71 Million Total Pixels, Single-lens Reflex Digital Camera, Effective Angle of View (Nikon DX Format, Focal Length Equivalent to 1.5x, Picture Control System (Standard, Neutral, Vivid, Monochrome, Portrait, Landscape, Selected Picture Control, Custom Picture Controls), Frame Coverage (95% Horizontal and 95% Vertical), Magnification (0.78x, -1.0 - m-1), 17.9 mm Eyepoint, Diopter Adjustment (-1.7 - .7, m-1), Type B BriteView Clear Matte Mark 7 Screen Focusing Screen, Reflex Mirror Quick Return, Lens Aperture (Instant Return, Electronically Controlled), Compatible Lenses (Autofocus is Available with AF-S and AF-I Lenses, Autofocus is Not Available with Other Type G and D Lenses, AF Lenses (IX NIKKOR and Lenses for the F3AF are Not Supported), and AI-P Lenses, Non-CPU Lenses, Electronic Rangefinder Lenses that have a Maximum Aperture of f/5.6), Shutter Type: Electronically-controlled Vertical-travel Focal-plane Shutter, Flash Sync Speed: X=1/200 sec, Sync with Shutter at 1/200 sec, Release Mode (Single Frame, Continuous L, Continuous H, Self-timer, Delayed Remote ML-L3, Quick-response Remote ML-L3, Quiet Shutter Release, Photography Supported), Frame Advance Rate: Upto 3 fps (L), 5 fps (H), Range (ISO 100, f/1.4 Lens, 20° C, 68° F), Matrix or Center-weighted Metering: 0 - 20 EV, Spot Metering: 2 - 20 EV, Exposure Compensation (5 EV in increments of 1/3 or 1/2 EV, P, S, A, and M Modes), Exposure Bracketing: 3 Shots in Steps of 1/3 or 1/2 EV, White Balance Bracketing: 3 Shots in Steps of 1, Active D-Lighting Bracketing: 2 Shots, Exposure Lock, Active D-Lighting (Auto, Extra High, High, Normal, Low, Off), Detection Range: -1 - EV (ISO 100, 20° C, 68° F), Lens Servo (Autofocus (AF), Single-servo AF (AF-S), Continuous-servo AF (AF-C), Auto AF-S / AF-C Selection (AF-A), Manual Focus (MF), Electronic Rangefinder), 11 Focus Point, AF-area Mode (Single-point AF, 9-, 21-, or 39- Point Dynamic-area AF, 3D-tracking, Auto-area AF, Focus lock, Color Sketch: Auto Flash with Auto Pop-up (P, S, A, M), Food: Manual Pop-up with Button Release, i-TTL Flash Control Using 2016-pixel RGB Sensor, Flash Compensation (-3 - EV in increments of 1/3 or 1/2 EV), Flash-ready Indicator, Accessory Shoe, Nikon Creative Lighting System (CLS), Advanced Wireless Lighting Supported, AS-15 Sync Terminal Adapter, Lens Servo: Autofocus (AF), Single-servo AF (AF-S), Full-time-servo AF (AF-F), Manual Focus (MF), AF-area Mode: Face-priority AF, Wide-area AF, Normal-area AF, Subject-tracking AF, Automatic Scene Selection, Frame Size (pixels) and Frame Rate: 1920 x 1080 (60i / 50i), 1920 x 1080, (30 p / 50 p / 60 p), 640 x 424, (30 p / 25 p), Playback Full-frame and Thumbnail (4, 9, or 72 Images or Calendar), Playback with Playback Zoom, Movie Playback, Photo Movie Slide Shows, Histogram Display, Highlights, Auto Image Rotation, Image Comment (upto 36 Characters), Audio Input Stereo Mini-pin Jack (3.5 mm Diameter), Operating Temperature: 0° - 40° C, Operating Humidity: 85%</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">6016 x 4000 (L)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Portrait, Child, Close Up, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Pet Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG, NEF (RAW), NEF (RAW) JPEG, EXIF 2.3, DCF 2.0, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">Linear PCM</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">MOV, MPEG-4 / H.264</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Power Supply">EH-5b AC Adapter</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">555 g (with Battery and Memory Card but without Cap), 505 g (with Camera Body Only)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">129 (W) x 98 (H) x 78 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC / Compatible with UHS-I</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30p</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">TFT LCD Monitor with 170° Viewing Angle</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Viewfinder">Yes, Eye-level Pentamirror</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ViewFinder">Yes, Eye-level Pentamirror</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/4/e/h/nikon-d5200-slr-400x400-imadfacekfaeyc5b.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/4/e/h/nikon-d5200-slr-400x400-imadface38gjbkdb.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/4/e/h/nikon-d5200-slr-400x400-imadfacehfdjgzxg.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/4/e/h/nikon-d5200-slr-400x400-imadfacedz4u7hrm.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Prianka Singh</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 24, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Great buy</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I've been thinking of buying an SLR for ages now. I wasn't quite convinced with the D3100 or the D5100, but when I read reviews of this camera I knew this is what I wanted. If you are a novice like me, but interested in a DSLR, this is a great fit. Its a brilliant camera, with enough features and options to ensure even as I improve as a photographer, I won't need to consider an upgrade. For a powerful camera, it is also ridiculously easy to use with lots of great options to allow a novice to get professional shots.Ever since the camera was launched, I've been keeping an eye out on all the listed retailers and other online sites. Flipkart was not only the first one to offer it, but also the only one to place so much importance on customer service. I wrote in to check if the camera could be delivered a day early, since I was travelling on the expected date of delivery and was eager to play around with it before I left. They wrote back saying they'd try but it was unlikely. And then surprised me by delivering it 3 days early!All in all, a great buy. Its easy to use, powerful, and has inbuilt effects which are easy to figure and yield great shots. The lens included is a great start (although one would need to buy a zoom lens eventually and a uv filter separately), the included bag appears to be of decent quality. All in all: a good buy</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Ritankar Bera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">May 21, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">4 months usage</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">This camera is one of the best entry level DSLRs out there. The image quality is just mesmerizing! And the low light auto focusing is pretty decent as well. Honestly, I was always a Nikon fan because Canon cameras tend to lack image quality. And this was my poison. Great product from Nikon. This is a outstanding upgrade over the previous Nikon D5100. 9 cross point AF! It's way more easy to focus on moving subjects. And the ISO performance is awesome. The only cons I've noticed is that it's not weather sealed and hence not suitable for using in the rain or stuff. And it doesn't have a focus motor. But that's not really an issue because most lenses today have built-in AF motors. People out there looking for an entry level DSLR with a budget of 50k, go for this! It's quite undoubtedly the best option. </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Fapa</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 3, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Great camera  Nikon D 5200 with18-105 lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">Camera General- Bought from Snapdeal (Order number 2559904891) with 105 lens as didnot wish to change lenses frequently purely for personal  interests. Pros- Great PQ, Cons- Bty life is average- appx 250 pics in a period of 3 days.    - Lens is heavy.     - Camera bag provided looks cheap.    - Even the strap looks cheap with the logo pasted on it.     - Packing was average.Camera is strongly recommended.Snapdeal- -Got it cheaper than other sites.-But got only 1 week return policy.Other site offers 1 month return.-Warranty offered was 2 years- but the warranty card mentioned only 1 year.-Snapdeal took one month and five reminders and finally telephonically convinced that the product will be taken care for two years.No written documents to support.-The product was dispatched by some different sellers name than that I had selected after paying a premium (as per seller rating).- Refused to entertain my review!!! even after five attempts.-Think if you want to save a thousand ruppes or need peace of mind.</specsKey>
</root>