<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix L28 Point & Shoot Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">3.938</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 4,000</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/2000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">20.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Resolution">Image Size: 5152 x 3864 (20 M), 3648 x 2736 (10 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), VGA 640 x 480, 16:9 Aspect Ratio: 5120 x 2880, Movie: 720 / 30p, 1280 x 720 / 16:9 / 30 fps, 480 / 30p, 640 x 480, 4:3 / 30 fps, 240 / 30p, 320 x 240 / 4:3 / 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">4.6 - 23 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 26 - 130 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">5x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">164 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">94.5 (W) x 59.8 (H) x 29 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">TFT LCD with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">1280 x 720, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">230,400 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Aspect Ratio">4:3, 16:9</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Camera Strap, Reference Manual CD, LR6/L40 (AA-size) Alkaline Batteries (x2), USB Cable UC-E16, ViewNX 2 CD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">L28</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Range">0.5 - 4.3 m (W), 0.8 - 2.1 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F3.2 - F6.5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Picture Angle">26 mm Wide-angle</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 6 Shots at 1.1 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">ISO 80 - 1600</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Easy Auto, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama, Pet Portrait), Smart Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto, Cloudy, Daylight, Flash, Fluorescent, Incandescent, Preset Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">Yes, 10 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">32</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Additional Features">Compact Digital Camera, Lens Construction: 6 Elements in 5 Groups, Focus-area Selection Center, 5 Level Brightness Adjustment, Frame Coverage Shooting Mode: 98% Horizontal and 98% Vertical, Frame Coverage Playback Mode: 98% Horizontal and 98% Vertical, Continuous Shooting: Single, Continuous (Six Images are Captured Continuously at Rate of About 1.1 fps), BSS (Best Shot Selector), 16 Multi-shot, Exposure Metering Mode: Matrix, Center-weighted, Spot, Exposure Control: Programmed Auto Exposure, Exposure Compensation: -2.0 - .0 EV in increment of 1/3 EV, Shutter: Mechanical and Charge-coupled Electronic Shutter, 2 Steps Aperture Range, Flash Control: TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Preflashes, Data Transfer Protocol: MTP, PTP, Input / Output Terminal: Audio / Video (A/V) Output, Digital Input / Output (USB), 1/4 inch Tripod Socket, Temperature: 0 - 40° C, Humidity: 85%, One-touch 720p HD Movie Recording, Smart Portrait System, Motion Blur Reduction, Easy-to-hold Handgrip Design Stylish Body with High-grade Metallic Exterior, Color Variations for Aluminum Lens Ring and Lens Barrel, EXPEED C2 Image Processing System, Wireless Transfer, Frame the Perfect Shot, Motion Detection</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">5152 x 3864 (20 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Easy Auto, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama, Pet Portrait), Smart Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG, EXIF 2.3, DCF, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">AVI (Motion-JPEG Compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">AA Alkaline Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">27 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/u/g/q/nikon-coolpix-l28-point-shoot-400x400-imadhwn7zzgqvmzg.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/u/g/q/nikon-coolpix-l28-point-shoot-400x400-imadhwn7gahjxjbp.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/u/g/q/nikon-coolpix-l28-point-shoot-400x400-imadhwn7gbpt4tu4.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/u/g/q/nikon-coolpix-l28-point-shoot-400x400-imadhwn7gxfphnzz.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/u/g/q/nikon-coolpix-l28-point-shoot-400x400-imadhwn7phq2vgzr.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/u/g/q/nikon-coolpix-l28-point-shoot-400x400-imadhwn7nrnrh4ky.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Amit Kesarwani</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Mar 8, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Gr8888888888888888t Camera!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Gr8888888888888888t Camera!I just one word don't miss it. it's very cheap with 20mp. great picture quality wiht 720p hd, and many more stuff.package includes all items flipkart mentioned...maximum image resolution 5152 x 3864 (Image size above 8 MB)..Wide screen Resolution 5120 x 2880 (Image size above 3 MB)..Shutter speed is fast...video 720p HD recording..Overall its gud camera for low budget..If anyone purchase a camera below Rs.6000 buy this one...
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Vishalaxi Patil</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Mar 18, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Flipkart - at its wrong part while servicing !!! </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">Hi,The product seems promising but NOT the service from flipkart. I ordered this camera on 14th Mar and I was told that I would get it in 2-3 days. I recieved a PHILIPS EPILATOR !!!!!! to my surprise. The bill which was in the corrier box was addressing correctly + the amount and product name. But the product in the box IS different. When Talked to customer care, they told me that they will revert with what I have ordered by 21st Mar.Package - Poor. Worst. Could peep from the corners of the box. HAve pics taken the time Its been handed over to me. If required can pass on. lemme know.Really disappointed with Flipkart as I was NOT expecting this from it. Would like to look forward for my product soon.Thank you.VishalaBengaluru</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Amit Chopra</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 5, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Slow Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						This is a useless camera for me. IT is slow in processing the picture, my Nokia E71 will process faster than this. Purchase it as my earlier Kodak Camera (Free with Printer) was broken. I still miss that cameraThe offer and goodies were good but thing twice before purchasing this camera, as during your good moments you might get frustrated as Flash will not work, will be very slow.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">ANAS S</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Mar 8, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">                           ...........Awesome Camera.........</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						This camera is cool..image & video quality is nyc..Gud packing & fast delivery..package includes all items flipkart mentioned...maximum image resolution 5152 x 3864 (Image size above 8 MB)..Wide screen Resolution 5120 x 2880 (Image size above 3 MB)..Shutter speed is fast...video 720p HD recording..Overall its gud camera for low budget..If anyone purchase a camera below Rs.6000 buy this one...
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Dibash phukan</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">May 10, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Superb</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I bought it a few days ago from flipkart and trust me it is really a good buying.20 megapixel and that too within 6000k is something that is indeed praiseworthy for Nikon as the other rivals failed to offer such,maximum of which may be of 16 megapixel.I have always been a fan of Nikon from the beginning and going by the performance till now i am truly satisfied.Crystal clear picture quality with 5x zoom.Gives True HD pictures when you connect it via data cable to laptop.You need not have to install anything.Just plug in the cable via a usb port to the camera and that's it.May be the use of AA pencil batteries may sound a little bit old-fashioned,but it is indeed suitable as you don't have to recharge it now and then.Just carry it as a back up and when the other batteries are down,you have the options to use them.And to say about after maintenance,you all know Nikon excels in it's service.They have a dedicated after maintenance service.And to say about Flipkart's delivery,it was good.Good packaging and on time delivery within 2-3 days.So guys,go for it without giving a second thought as it would be a worth buying.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">santhosh prabhakaran</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">2</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Mar 18, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Not worthy</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						It take 2-3 seconds to get the focus right and you misses the timing for the perfect moments.Better stay away from this .Useless 20 Mp sensor.better oo any sony or canon or 8 MP Smartphones
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Usha</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">2</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 26, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Not upto the hype given</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						i bought this product after reading many reviews but was shocked to see the actual product in hand.The body is made up of very cheap material compared to Fujifilm cameras, the 20 mp actually doesnt look like its 20 mp
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Mohit Raj</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jun 13, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">good camera at good price </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Now this time thanks to Flipkart service got camera with in 24 hours. But price is higher than other websites.+ ve points ..  1, Very Nice quality 20 mp , 5152*3864                   2.  Motion sensor, You can take snap of  rotating fan without any blurriness.                      3. It start just in 1 sec.                      4. Eye-fi technology                      5 . it use AA battery.  -ve Point : It take about 15 second to get ready to take next snap 
</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Subhash Ghimire</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Sep 25, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nikon CoolPix L28. Great Point and Shoot Camera for Day-to-Day Photography.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I had ordered Nikon Coolpix L28 (Black) on Sunday 22 Sep 2013 and by Tuesday afternoon 24 Sep 2013 it was delivered. Awesome delivery service by Flipkart and WS retail team. Regarding the products was delighted to get freebies like 4 GB memory card, Camera Pouch with Nikon logo, strap, Extra pair of batteries (rechargeable) and a cool Timex wrist watch. The camera has 20 MP CCD sensor and 5X optical Zoom. I clicked few Pics and Picture quality and color reproduction was good. However the picture looks grainy on camera Screen. It was easy to transfer the Pics from camera to my Desktop. I tried Zoom feature at low light and was delighted with its quality of snap taken. Also did HD recording and it captured excelled video recording with zoom facility. The photo file size is in around 4.5 MB and about 1 minute video takes 100 MB size. Of the 11 Pics that I clicked 6 turned out super sharp, 2 good quality , 1 average and 2 were blur and hence not as expected. These shots were taken in Auto mode. Overall a good point and shoot for day to day use.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Arun </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Mar 31, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">very bad and poor quality.....</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">Hiii all,I have purchased Nikon Coolpix L28 in month of october. First when i received this product, this was not as described on website. Thanks to Flip Kart they returned that. When i received another replaced camera Nikon coolpix L28, its speed is too much slow. I thought it may be due to setting.. but till today, Its speed is too slow. When i take a pic and pose for another then the time in two click is much larger and believe me too harashing, when you are with cam of 20mgpxl but taking too much time. I want to replace but they are not doing for same. I have decided not to buy any product by flip kart coz they only sold bad product. </specsKey>
</root>