<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix AW120 Point & Shoot Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Black,Blue,Camouflage,Orange</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">3.688</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 13,346</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Connectivity Features">Data Transfer Protocol: MTP, PTP, HDMI Output: Can be Selected from Auto, 480p, 720p and 1080i</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Wi-Fi Connectivity">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Wi-Fi Standard">IEEE 802.11b/g/n</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Wireless Connectivity">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Tripod Socket">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/1500 Sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shutter Type">Mechanical, CMOS Electronic Shutter</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shutter Speed in other Modes">4 sec (when Scene Mode is Set to Fireworks Show), 1/4000 sec (Maximum Speed During High-speed Continuous Shooting)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">AW120</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Format">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F2.8 - F4.9</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Single (Default Setting), Continuous H (The Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 6.9 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 5), Continuous L (The Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 2.2 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots 33), Pre-shooting Cache (The Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting 20 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 25, Maximum of 5 Frames Captured in the Pre-shooting Cache), Continuous H: 120 fps (The Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting 120 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 50), Continuous H: 60 fps (The Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting 60 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 25), BSS (Best Shot Selector), Multi-shot 16</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">ISO 125 - 1600 (Manual), ISO 3200, 6400 (Auto)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Easy Auto, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, Underwater), Special Effects, Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dust Reduction">JIS / IEC Protection Class 6 (IP6X) Equivalent (Under Testing Conditions)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Features">ISO Sensitivity (Auto): 0.5 - 5.2 m (W), 0.5 - 5 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">1 cm (0.4 inch) - Infinity</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Temperature">-10° C - 40° C (for Land Use), 0° C - 40° C (for Underwater Use)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Humidity">85%</specsKey>
<specsKey name="HDMI">Type D Micro HDMI Out</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering Modes">Matrix, Center-weighted (Digital Zoom Less than 2x), Spot (Digital Zoom 2x or More)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">Arabic, Bengali, Bulgarian, Simplified Chinese, Chinese (Traditional), Czech, Danish, Dutch, English, Finnish, French, German, Greek, Hindi, Hungarian, Indonesian, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Marathi, Norwegian, Persian, Polish, Portuguese (European and Brazilian), Romanian, Russian, Serbian, Spanish, Swedish, Tamil, Telugu, Thai, Turkish, Ukrainian, Vietnamese</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Additional Features">Vibration Reduction: Lens Shift and Electronic VR, Motion Blur Reduction (Still Picture), Tripod Socket: 1/4 (ISO 1222), Charging Time: 2 hr 20 min (when Using Charging AC Adapter EH-71P and when No Charge Remains), Still Pictures: 350 Shots when Using EN-EL12, Electronically-controlled Preset Aperture (-1 AV) and ND Filter (-2 AV) Selections, Range: F2.8, F4.1, F8.2 Aperture 3 Steps, Movie (Actual Battery Life for Recording): 1 hr 15 min (1080 / 30 fps) when Using EN-EL12, 1 hr 20 min (1080/25 fps) when Using EN-EL12, Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode): 98% Horizontal and 98% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture), Frame Coverage (Playback Mode): 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture), Communications Protocols: IEEE 802.11b: DBPSK/DQPSK/CCK, IEEE 802.11g: OFDM, IEEE 802.11n: OFDM, Range (Line of Sight): 30 m (32 yd), Operating Frequency: 2412 - 2462 MHz (1 - 11 Channels), Data Rates (Actual Measured Values): IEEE 802.11b: 5 Mbps, IEEE 802.11g: 17 Mbps, IEEE 802.11n: 17 Mbps, Security: Open/WPA2, Access Protocols: CSMA/CA, Shockproof: Cleared Testing Conditions, 3 Compliant with MIL-STD 810F Method 516.5 Shock, Waterproof: JIS / IEC Protection Class 8 (IPX8) Equivalent (Under Testing Conditions), Capacity to Shoot Images Underwater upto Depth of 18 m (59 ft) for 60 min, Electronic Compass: 16 Cardinal Points (Position Correction Using 3-axis Acceleration Sensor, Automatic Correction for the Deviated Angle and Automatic Offset Adjustment), Location Data: GPS / Receiving Frequency: 1575.42 MHz, Geodetic System: WGS 84 Glonass / Receiving Frequency: 1598.0625 - 1605.3750 MHz, Geodetic System: WGS 84, Barometer: Operating Range 500 - 1100 hPa, Altimeter: Operating Range -300 - 4500 m (-984 - 14, 760 ft), Depth Gauge: Operating Range 0 - 20 m (0 - 65 ft), Lithium Battery (EN-EL12)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">4.3 - 21.5 mm (35 mm (135) Equivalent 24 - 120 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Construction">12 Elements in 10 Groups (2 ED Lens Element)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Focus Features">Focus Area Selecton: Face Priority, Manual with 99 Focus Areas, Center, Subject Tracking, Target Finding AF, Digital Zoom Magnification: 35 mm (135) Equivalent 480 mm, Flash Control: TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Pre-flashes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focus Range">50 cm (1 ft, 8 inch) - Infinity (W), 50 cm (1 ft, 8 inch) - Infinity (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Total Pixel/Gross Pixel">16.79</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Resolution">Movie (1080/30 fps (Default Setting)): 1920 x 1080 (16:9), 1080/25 fps (Default Setting): 1920 x 1080 (16:9), 1080/60i: 1920 x 1080 (16:9), 1080/50i: 1920 x 1080 (16:9), 1280 x 720 (16:9) at 720/30 fps, 1280 x 720 (16:9) at 720/25 fps, iFrame: 1280 x 720 (16:9) at 720/30 fps, iFrame: 1280 x 720 (16:9) at 720/25 fps, 640 x 480 (4:3) at 480/30 fps, 640 x 480 (4:3) at 480/25 fps, HS 480/4x: 640 x 480 (4:3), HS 720/2x: 1280 x 720 (16:9), HS 1080/0.5x: 1920 x 1080 (16:9))</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Easy Auto, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, Underwater), Special Effects, Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Features">3456 x 3456 (1:1)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">File System: DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF Compliant</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Size at Megapixels">Fine (4608 x 3456 (16M) (High)), (4608 x 3456 (16M)), (3264 x 2448 (8M)), (2272 x 1704 (4M)), (1600 x 1200 (2M)), (640 x 480 (VGA))</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">Audio: LPCM Stereo, WAV</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Still Image Size 16:9">4608 x 2592</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">JPEG Sound Files (Voice Memo), Movies: MOV (Video: H.264 / MPEG-4 AVC)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Size at Aspect Ratio">16:9, 1:1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">5x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focus">Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Power Supply">EH-71P AC Adapter</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">213 g</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">110.1 (W) x 66 (H) x 25.8 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">329 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Wi-Fi">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">OLED with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Exposure Modes">Programmed AE</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Display Viewing Angle">5 Levels Brightness Adjustment</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Exposure Compensation">1/3 EV Steps +/- 2.0 EV</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/e/h/s/nikon-coolpix-aw120-point-shoot-400x400-imadvfghugfwehjg.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/e/h/s/nikon-coolpix-aw120-point-shoot-400x400-imadvfghwg4zxeqr.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/e/h/s/nikon-coolpix-aw120-point-shoot-400x400-imadvfgheqypqfyh.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/e/h/s/nikon-coolpix-aw120-point-shoot-400x400-imadvfghspxggb8w.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/e/h/s/nikon-coolpix-aw120-point-shoot-400x400-imadvfgh6ghxz7yw.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/e/h/s/nikon-coolpix-aw120-point-shoot-400x400-imadvfghbsgsmydp.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Chella Kumar P M</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 18, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Good camera to carry around all the time</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Pros1) Compact and light weight2) Waterproof, I would rather call it kid proof3) GPS works really well4) Wifi Tranfer - This is a feature worth having all the time, it works really well and you can even use your phone as a view finder and shoot photos5) Excellent Battery backup - I think Nikon is being modest by saying 200, it can go on for even 300+Cons1) None, cos I didn't pay for a DSLR camera to expect so
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Venkatraman M</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">3</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Sep 4, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">It could not replace a regular Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I am using the camera and didn't bought it from flipkart. The videos quality is very good. The photo quality is average. The normal Canon/Nikon point and shoot cameras can give better picture than this camera.This is water proof camera. This will be useful when you are going for hiking/trekking. I have tried in underwater also. If the lighting is good, it can take very good under water videos. I am just using this as backup camera.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Sandeep</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Aug 6, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nikon Coolpix AW120 - Small Package, decent features</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Just bought this Nikon Camera. Found it very handy and well built. Picture quality is better than average even in low light. GPS takes about 4-5 minutes to activate, but is fairly accurate. Pictures also record altitude information, which could be interesting when compiling those hiking trip pics.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Rajaram Sivananda</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">2</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 5, 2015</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Well built, natural light photos are great but flash photos are very different</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">The camera feels solid, though there is a little rattle of the lens when you shake the camera. Understand this rattle is normal from the service centre. The natural light photos are nice, but the ones taken with flash are terrible, quite often. I don't know whether it is my camera or generally so will take it to the service centre. With flash some photos are fine, but some photos are all bleached with excessive light. As you can see I am not a photography wizard, but am using this in auto, and have used several camera in the past. This is the worst with flash. Well I have got used to changing the more from Easy Auto for natural light and Auto for flash photos. Have dunked in water and no issues with that. Well built and solid. I would buy another camera if I had to again.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Abhideep</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 21, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Real Rugged Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">Pros:1- Real rugged (Read further for this)2- Very good in macro3- Very nice video quality4- Geo taggingCons:1- Manual focus, app for Windows fone and RAW format are missing2- App should be improved to take video3- Slow motion video is not so effectiveAfter a week of purchase when I was with this camera in the beaches of Goa, I realized that the sand went into the zooming lever section and zooming lever was not moving at all. This was real bad but I cant blame Nikon for this because they never claimed that its dust proof. It was my fault and I was sad on that because the camera was not even 7 days old. Reached back to guest house and thought is cleaning the camera. Kept it under tap water and used the brush came along with the kit. After 5 mins of cleaning, I realized all was well. Zoom lever started working. I could remove the sand properly. The camera was back like a brand new one. This was an awesome feeling and gave me confidence on the ruggedness of the camera. Anything is wrong of this sort, wash it.I go for swimming. I have taken it many times for in the pool, close to 16 feet deep. It works like charm. Video quality is very good.Images are quite sharp and colorful.I did a lot of food photography. It does this job wonderfully good. HDR works decently good. High speed, night portrait, beach, fireworks, etc. mode are good. Geo tagging does a good work. I have used WiFi and app for a live tweeting of an event and it went very good. Within 2 mins pics were online. Click + transfer + tweet = Done quick.Even if you have a DSLR, this is a must buy. I was taking pics easily when my DSLR friends were running away from waves and I clicked a star fish under water. Loving it.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Rajaram Sivananda</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">2</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 27, 2015</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Terrible low light photographs. Flash photos are very inconsistent</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Don't buy this product, I am disappointed with the way the flash works. Daylight photos are good, and the camera robust. There is a rattle in the lens when the camera is off, apparently this is normal.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">MVP</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">2</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 6, 2015</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Very Average for a 16MP camera.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						The picture quality of the camera in auto mode is worse than a phone camera. Please refrain from buying this product.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Kmayyank</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 25, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Awesome Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">Its The Best digicam you can buy within ₹ 15000. I bought during the diwali mela and got it for around 14k. It actually is a Damn good Water proof device. Used it in Mauritius and very easy to clean also. I recommend it to every one. 5* to flipkart for awesome delivery, ie, in just 3 days. A definite must buy. The pouch, however, i received was smaller and had to buy separatly from Nehru Place, Delhi. I enquired abt the same model there, which i was getting around ₹2000 cheaper, ie, around ₹ 11500 but honestly i dont trust those shop keepers there. With Flipkart you have some sense of piece of mind that incase anything goes wrong, they can replace the item.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Kern Martis</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">2</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 1, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Camera quality is bad</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Picture quality not good. Bad low light photos and bad flash. Also i got the wrong camera case with my camera. The pouch is smaller than the camera.
				</specsKey>
</root>