<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon D750 (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.2</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 129,990</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Nikon D750 Body, EN-EL15 Li-Ion Battery, MH-25 Battery Charger, DK-21 Rubber Eyecup, DK-5 Eyepiece, BM-14 LCD Cover, BF-18 Body Cap, BS-1 Hot-Shoe Cover, AN-DC12 Camera Strap, UC-E22 USB Cable, ViewNX 2 CD-ROM</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">D750</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">24.3 MP</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Slow Motion">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium-ion</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/r/f/z/nikon-d750-400x400-imaefpvj8np8u3d5.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/r/f/z/nikon-d750-400x400-imaefpvjt8qt3h73.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/r/f/z/nikon-d750-400x400-imaefpvj4sgwk6jd.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/r/f/z/nikon-d750-400x400-imaefpvjnbjadjhf.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/r/f/z/nikon-d750-400x400-imaefpvjm9jfnst3.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/r/f/z/nikon-d750-400x400-imaefpvjxf8u3zc4.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/r/f/z/nikon-d750-400x400-imaefpvjggutgrkz.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/r/f/z/nikon-d750-400x400-imaefpvjmhvtwx7w.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/r/f/z/nikon-d750-400x400-imaefpvgvhtserch.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/r/f/z/nikon-d750-400x400-imaefpvgdfesgmgz.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="subimg">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/r/f/z/nikon-d750-400x400-imaefpvj8np8u3d5.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img_id">Nikon D750 (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Dr. Ameya</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 23, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Fantastic </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">i wont write much about the product as all the products by flipkart are very genuine and the delivery was made within 3 days which is astonishing. I just have to suggest something for the people who would be buying this in future and to flipkart that the official invoice received along with the product (e-copy) doesn't mention the serial number of the product, the only link between the invoice and the said product. Since the invoice is going to serve the purpose of 'warranty card' , it needs to have the serial number or else there is nothing that would connect it to the purchase. This will become extremely important in the scenario of service center visits. It is a very expensive purchase and customers should be fully protected warranty wise.Kindly make a note of this. </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Gaurav Mohan</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 28, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Why to buy it from Flipkart when you can this product around 16-17k less somewhere else !!!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">This camera has been a great challenger to Canon 5D Mark III 2. Moreover if you look at the full frame DSLRs from Nikon this is something that stands out amongst Nikon D610, D800, D800E and the beast Nikon D810. Loaded with features that you may not find in anything else, fist time introduction of a tilt-angle screen to the lightest FULL FRAME DSLR but still other sites are selling the same exact product, same exact warranty with a price tag   lesser than what Flipkart is selling here. Not sure whats the strategy Flipkart has for this product around its price. I am putting 5 stars for the Product but not the price which Flipkart is offering. </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Pratik Rana</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 8, 2015</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">best Nikon I have ever used</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						The D750 is the champion in it's league. It simply blows away its competitors. I bought this around 1.37L with 24-85 lens in China recently. Everything is amazing in this camera. Recommended if you are a pro.
				</specsKey>
</root>