<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix S9700 Point & Shoot Camera (Red)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Red</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">3.833</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 15,255</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/2000 Sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shutter Type">Mechanical, CMOS Electronic Shutter</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shutter Speed in other Modes">1/2000 - 8 sec (when ISO Sensitivity is Fixed at ISO 125 - 200 in S, A, or M Mode) 1/4000 sec (Maximum Speed During High-speed Continuous Shooting) when the Aperture Value is f/5.6 - f/8 at the Wide-angle Position</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Connectivity Features">Data Transfer Protocol: MTP, PTP, HDMI Output: Can be Selected from Auto, 480p, 720p and 1080i</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Wi-Fi Standard">IEEE 802.11b/g/n</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Wi-Fi Connectivity">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Wireless Connectivity">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Tripod Socket">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">S9700</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Red</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Format">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Total Pixel/Gross Pixel">16.79</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Resolution">Movie (1080/30 fps (Default Setting)): 1920 x 1080 (16:9), 1080/25 fps (Default Setting): 1920 x 1080 (16:9), 1080/60i: 1920 x 1080 (16:9), 1080/50i: 1920 x 1080 (16:9), 1280 x 720 (16:9) at 720/30 fps, 1280 x 720 (16:9) at 720/25 fps, iFrame: 1280 x 720 (16:9) at 720/30 fps, iFrame: 1280 x 720 (16:9) at 720/25 fps, 640 x 480 (4:3) at 480/30 fps, 640 x 480 (4:3) at 480/25 fps, HS 240/8x: 320 x 240 (4:3), HS 480/4x: 640 x 480 (4:3), HS 720/2x: 1280 x 720 (16:9), HS 1080/0.5x: 1920 x 1080 (16:9))</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">4.5 - 135 mm (35 mm (135) Equivalent 25 - 750 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Focus Features">Focus Area Selecton: Face Priority, Center, Manual with 99 Focus Areas, Subject Tracking, Target Finding AF, Digital Zoom Magnification: 35 mm (135) Equivalent 3000 mm, Flash Control: TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Pre-flashes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Construction">13 Elements in 11 Groups (3 ED Lens Element)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focus Range">50 cm (1 ft, 8 inch) - Infinity (W), 2 m (6 ft, 7 inch) - Infinity (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F3.7 - F6.4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Single (Default Setting), Continuous H (The Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 6.9 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 5), Continuous L (The Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 2.2 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots 36), Pre-shooting Cache (The Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting 20 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 25, Maximum of 5 Frames Captured in the Pre-shooting Cache), Continuous H: 120 fps (The Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting 120 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 50), Continuous H: 60 fps (The Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting 60 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 25), BSS (Best Shot Selector), Multi-shot 16</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">ISO 125 - 1600, ISO 3200 - 6400 (Available when Using P, S, A or M Mode)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait), Smart Portrait, Special Effects, P, S, A, M</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Features">ISO Sensitivity (Auto): 0.5 - 6 m (W), 1.5 - 3.5 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">1 cm (0.4 inch) - Infinity</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Temperature">0° C - 40° C</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Humidity">85%</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering Modes">Matrix, Center-weighted, Spot (Digital Zoom 2x or More)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="HDMI">Type D Micro HDMI Out</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">Arabic, Bengali, Bulgarian, Simplified Chinese, Chinese (Traditional), Czech, Danish, Dutch, English, Finnish, French, German, Greek, Hindi, Hungarian, Indonesian, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Marathi, Norwegian, Persian, Polish, Portuguese (European and Brazilian), Romanian, Russian, Serbian, Spanish, Swedish, Tamil, Telugu, Thai, Turkish, Ukrainian, Vietnamese</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Additional Features">Vibration Reduction: Lens Shift and Electronic VR, Motion Blur Reduction (Still Picture), Tripod Socket: 1/4 (ISO 1222), Charging Time: 2 hr 20 min (when Using Charging AC Adapter EH-71P and when No Charge Remains), Still Pictures: 300 Shots when Using EN-EL12, Electronically-controlled 3-blade Iris Diaphragm, Range: 14 Steps of 1/6 EV (W) (A, M Mode), Movie (Actual Battery Life for Recording): 1 hr 5 min when Using EN-EL12, Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode): 98% Horizontal and 98% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture), Frame Coverage (Playback Mode): 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture), 60x Dynamic Zoom, Communications Protocols: IEEE 802.11b: DBPSK/DQPSK/CCK, IEEE 802.11g: OFDM, IEEE 802.11n: OFDM, Range (Line of Sight): 30 m (32 yd), Operating Frequency: 2412 - 2462 MHz (1 - 11 Channels), Data Rates (Actual Measured Values): IEEE 802.11b: 5 Mbps, IEEE 802.11g: 15 Mbps, IEEE 802.11n: 15 Mbps, Security: Open/WPA2, Access Protocols: CSMA/CA, Electronic Compass: 16 Cardinal Points (Position Correction Using 3-axis Acceleration Sensor, Automatic Correction for the Deviated Angle and Automatic Offset Adjustment), Location Data: GPS / Receiving Frequency: 1575.42 MHz, Geodetic System: WGS 84 Glonass / Receiving Frequency: 1598.0625 - 1605.3750 MHz, Geodetic System: WGS 84, Lithium Battery (EN-EL12)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">30x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focus">Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait), Smart Portrait, Special Effects, P, S, A, M</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Features">3456 x 3456 (1:1)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Size at Megapixels">4608 x 3456 (16 M), 3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), 640 x 480 (VGA)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">File System: DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF Compliant</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">Audio: LPCM Stereo, WAV</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Still Image Size 16:9">4608 x 2592 (12 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">JPEG Sound Files (Voice Memo), Movies: MOV (Video: H.264 / MPEG-4 AVC)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Size at Aspect Ratio">16:9, 1:1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Power Supply">EH-71P AC Adapter</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">232 g</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">109.6 (W) x 63.5 (H) x 34.5 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">329 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Wi-Fi">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Exposure Modes">Programmed AE with Flexible Program, Shutter-priority Auto, Aperture-priority Auto, Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">OLED with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Display Viewing Angle">5 Levels Brightness Adjustment</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Exposure">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Exposure Compensation">1/3 EV Steps +/- 2.0 EV</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/6/6/d/nikon-coolpix-s9700-point-shoot-400x400-imadvfgpxnrcpyew.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/6/6/d/nikon-coolpix-s9700-point-shoot-400x400-imadvfgpw5yf9gyb.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/6/6/d/nikon-coolpix-s9700-point-shoot-400x400-imadvfgpzknbaf8k.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/6/6/d/nikon-coolpix-s9700-point-shoot-400x400-imadvfgpz5rtjrs7.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/6/6/d/nikon-coolpix-s9700-point-shoot-400x400-imadvfgpzqzyvznz.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/6/6/d/nikon-coolpix-s9700-point-shoot-400x400-imadvfgpzcpaxmtn.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/6/6/d/nikon-coolpix-s9700-point-shoot-400x400-imadvfgpzgxmczuc.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/6/6/d/nikon-coolpix-s9700-point-shoot-400x400-imadvfgpcumxnnzc.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/6/6/d/nikon-coolpix-s9700-point-shoot-400x400-imadvfgqnuqsdwzg.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Vikash Sharma</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jul 19, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">NICE  PRODUCT---</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Bought this product from Great Eastern Kolkata ----I want to say only ---Nice Camera --Zoom Quality awesome--Nice Pics etc etc
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Amit Chawla</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 6, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Awesome Camera with wonderful features both for amateurs & novices</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I am a photographer and wished to gift a nice camera to my parents on their anniversary. However I needed to have some pro-features too in addition to the usual features. I was super delighted to read all specs of this camera but was a little skeptical if it will be delivered in time. Indeed flipkart kept its promise of timely one-day-guarantee but I was pleased to see the performance of this camera as well. With Wifi & GPS, Shutter priority mode, Aperture priority mode, manual mode and many scene modes backed up with strong battery, high density screen resolution and a very powerful flash gun (built in) it was a great deal.. what what steals the show is its 30x zoom, equivalent to roughly 700 mm on my DSLR. FULL marks to Nikon for product. FULL marks to Flipkart for delivery.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">John Prashant</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 3, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">The best value-for-money Compact Super Zoom in the market</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">While the Coolpix S9700 may not always come out on top in the ratings & rankings of photography equipment analysts; it's perhaps the best value-for-money camera out there amongst its peers; namely the Canon PowerShot SX700 HS, the Sony CyberShot HX60, and the Panasonic Lumix TZ60.Amongst this lot, the Nikon S9700 is the best all-round performer, and is superb value for money.  It's well built, boots up quickly, is reasonably fast to focus, and is an excellent outdoor performer.If there's an design quibble, it's the flash pop-up mechanism, that seems a bit fiddly and delicate.  Also, personally, while the new OLED screen is brighter & sharper; I prefer the LCD screens in the older models, that give a more accurate color reproduction.On the whole, this a highly recommended travel zoom compact camera; and I would whole heartedly recommend this to the casual, holiday and party photographer, who is looking for a hassle-free reliable camera delivering consistent good quality images.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Harsh Maheshwari</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">3</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Apr 9, 2015</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Not so good and having technical problem</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Hi, I bought this camera 6 month back and giving my review comment after using 6 month.I believe pros you can get from every where but i am going to mention just my view:1. It heat alot.2. Flash camera come out and which doesn't look very sustainable thing or need to handle very carefully.3. After 6 month use camera is not working and need to go Customer care.ThanksHarsh
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">S K Das</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 22, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Just go for it.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						This is very good product in this range. The S9700 is a super high-power zoom model equipped with a 30x optical zoom.
				</specsKey>
</root>