<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix L21 Point & Shoot Camera (Pink)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Pink</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.286</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 4,641</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">8 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">TTL</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">6.7-24.0mm / F3.1-6.7</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">3.6x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">169 g</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">92 (W) x 61.1 (H) x 28.3 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">2.5 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Camera, Camera Strap AN-CP19, LR6/L40 (AA-size), Alkaline Batteries, USB Cable UC-E6, Software Suite CD-ROM, User Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">Coolpix L21</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Pink</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with red-eye reduction, Off, Fill flash, Slow sync</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 1 fps up to 5 shots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto mode, Scene modes, Scene auto selector, Smart portrait mode, Movie mode</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto, Preset manual, Daylight, Incandescent, Fluorescent, Cloudy, Flash</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">24</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto mode, Scene modes, Scene auto selector, Smart portrait mode, Movie mode</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG, EXIF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">AVI Movie</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">AA Alkaline Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">19 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/g/z/f/nikon-coolpix-l21-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqsps4tzdmh.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/g/z/f/nikon-coolpix-l21-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq4rsw2h2cz.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/g/z/f/nikon-coolpix-l21-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqhzejgg9eg.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="subimg">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/g/z/f/nikon-coolpix-l21-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqsps4tzdmh.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img_id">Nikon Coolpix L21 Point & Shoot Camera (Pink)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Pankaj  Sharma</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Aug 25, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Awesome Camera....</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						U wont get any camera better than this, at this range...And the quality of the camera is nice...No issues with the camera...And Flipkart is doing an Excellent job out there, they are making me addicted to shop online everytime...Flipkart also provides required accesories with it... Dat i feel very better...
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">R.S</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Sep 16, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">good camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						though camera is very basic widout many options, great camera for its price, image clarity pretty good. service of flipkart was really good. keep d good work going guys. all in all a very pleasant shopping experience
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Dipak Ramani</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Sep 10, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nice economy camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						this is such wonderful to work with itnice colour range, and good warrany period offer
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">S L Narasimhan</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">2</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 6, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Go for something else </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Hey guys , i got a nikon coolpix about a year ago . Well its a decent camera thats what it is nothing more. You will get shaky, blurred images trust me no matter how steady you keep your hands. So nothing really special about it. There are lots of better cameras of sony or better casio or cannon ...If you buying it because of Nikon brand name , you will regret it , trust these low end are not upto mark . So thats about it . Thanx for reading and bye .:)
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">vivek gupta</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Sep 26, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">nice economic camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						this is a very gud digicam for d lowbudget ppl...n gud for startin a fotography...
				</specsKey>
</root>