<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix P300 Point & Shoot Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.562</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 13,904</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/2000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">8 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">12.2 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Glass Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast-detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">4.3 - 17.9 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 24 - 100 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">4.2x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">2x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">189 g</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">103.0 (W) x 58.3 (H) x 32.0 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">TFT LCD Monitor with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Aspect Ratio">4:3, 16:9</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Camera, Camera Strap AN-CP19, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL12, Charging AC Adapter EH-69P, USB Cable UC-E6, Audio Video Cable EG-CP16, View NX 2 CD, User Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">Coolpix P300</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with red-eye reduction, Flash Off, Fill flash, Slow sync</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Range">0.5 - 6.5 m (W), 0.5 - 2.5 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F1.8 - F4.9</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">224 Segment Matrix Metering, Center-weighted Metering</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sync Terminal">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 8 fps (upto 7 Shots), Continuous H: 120 fps (1280 x 960, upto 60 Shots), Continuous H: 60 fps (1600 x 1200, upto 60 Shots)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">Auto (auto gain ISO 160-1600), Fixed range auto (ISO 160 to 400, 160 to 800), Manual selection: ISO 160, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto mode, Scene Modes, Movie Mode, Program, SShutter Priorty, Apertyre Priorty, Manual Exposure Modes, Night Landscape, Backlit Scene HDR</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto, Preset Manual, Daylight, Incandescent, Fluorescent, Cloudy, Flash</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">Yes, 3 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="HDMI">HDMI mini connector</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">26</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Additional Features">Monitor Frame Coverage, In-Camera Image Editing, 26 Languages Supported, Backside Illumination, Backlighting Mode, Filter Effects, Easy Panorama, Operating Temperature: 0Deg - 40Deg C</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4000 x 3000 (12 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto mode, Scene Modes, Movie Mode, Program, SShutter Priorty, Apertyre Priorty, Manual Exposure Modes, Night Landscape, Backlit Scene HDR</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG, EXIF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">Mono, WAV File</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">MOV Movie</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Operating System">Windows 7</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">90 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/f/a/r/nikon-coolpix-p300-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqzwaamksps.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/f/a/r/nikon-coolpix-p300-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqkw3yhdgp3.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/f/a/r/nikon-coolpix-p300-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq3upgnpbky.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/f/a/r/nikon-coolpix-p300-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq4dyex52ye.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/f/a/r/nikon-coolpix-p300-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqhmhzbzztq.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="subimg">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/f/a/r/nikon-coolpix-p300-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqzwaamksps.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img_id">Nikon Coolpix P300 Point & Shoot Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">SAYAN CHATTERJEE</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 19, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">P300</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						THIS IS A EXCELLENT CAMERA FOR PHOTOGRAPHY.ONCE U R EXPERT IN HANDILING THIS CAMERA U CAN EASILY HANDLE A SLR CAMERA.BELIEVE ME ITS A VERY GOOD CAMERA.ONLY PROBLEM IS THAT ITS ZOOM IS LESS BUT STILL IT WILL NOT EFFECT SO MUCH ON THE IMAGE.THERE ARE DIFFERENT MODES.ONCE FULLY CHARGED IT CAN GIVE ABOUT 250-300 SHOTS.ALL TOTAL ITS A VERY GOOD CAMERA.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Jayantika Soni</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 30, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Ultimate features at the price</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I have owned this camera for 9 months now. One of my photographer friend suggested it.Pros: This is a seriously good compact camera, if that's what are you looking for. It comprises of various features and gives you a lot of features to practice before buying a DSLR. I am still practicing. If you don't get the photographic jargon f/1.8 would help you focus nearer objects, which you won't find in this range (trust me I searched thoroughly, though 9 months ago) and its optical and digital zoom are really good (I have umpteen pictures to prove). Charging is also easy (you don't have to take out the battery). The panoramic feature is very good, also you can choose the colour to focus on, try it on its various modes and you'll know.Cons: It doesn't really de-focuses the background much or I'm yet to figure out how to do that.Best to buy at this price. Go for it :)</specsKey>
</root>