<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon L29 Point & Shoot Camera (Design Purple)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Black,Design Purple,Red,Silver</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">3.98</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 4,800</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Two LR6/L40 (AA-size) alkaline batteries, Camera Strap</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">L29</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Processor">Expeed C2 Image-processing System</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Design Purple</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Format">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Total Pixel/Gross Pixel">16.44</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">4.6 - 23.0 mm (35 mm (135) Equivalent 26 - 130 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Focus Features">Digital Zoom Magnification: 35 mm (135) Equivalent 520 mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focus Range">50 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F3.2 - F6.5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">ISO 80 - 1600 (Auto)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">10 cm - Infinity</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Additional Features">One Touch HD 720p Movie Recording, Battery Life of Still Shooting: 200 Shots with Alkaline / 650 Shots with Lithium / 380 Shots with EN-MH2 Batteries, Easy to Hold Handgrip Design, Motion Blur Reduction: Motion Detection (Still Pictures), Smart Portrait System, Easy Auto Mode, Filter Effects</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">5x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Features">4608 x 2592 (16:9)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Size at Megapixels">4608 x 3456 (16 M (High)), 4608 x 3456 (16 M), 3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), 640 x 480 (VGA)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">AA Alkaline Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">160 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">96.4 (W) x 59.4 (H) x 28.9 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">1280 x 720</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">2.7 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/u/f/n/nikon-nikon-l29-point-shoot-400x400-imadtftkpzzrvuwx.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/u/f/n/nikon-nikon-l29-point-shoot-400x400-imadtftkttnjywce.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Krishnaprasad</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Sep 13, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Good product but bad flipkart service</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I bought a Nikon camera last week (ordered on 10-09-2014 to be precise). Disappointed to say that i am not satisfied with flipkart. The reason is, I ordered this camera just because there was an 8GB SD card on offer. But when i got the actual product, it was packaged with a 4GB SD card. When enquired with flipcart customer care, I was told that the offer (8GB SD) was from Thursday (11-09-2014) onwards.But i am 200% sure that when i placed the order, it was displayed with 8GBcard on offer from 10-09-2014 onwards. To be honest, you have put a verybad taste in my mouth. I didnt expect this kind of response from a companylike flipkart.Unfortunately i dont have any proof to show that the 8GB offer was therefrom 10-09-2014 onwards. But as a customer, I am very disappointedI don't want to lie here as i know that what ever i said is 100% accurate.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Subham</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Mar 29, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nice Camera n Awesome Flipkart Service  </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I received my order for this camera a few days ago.......I am really satisfied with flipkart service as the delivery was made one day before the expected date.This a a very nice product at a very low price. Its features include Smile Timer, Blink Proof alerting and Red-Eye Fix. Videos are recorded in 720p. It takes very sharp images in daylight and indoors.One of the cons of this camera is that low light photography is a bit blurry but still decent.A 4GB SDHC card is provided along with the camera.I would surely recommend this camera to my friends........
</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Prasanna N</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">May 20, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Not Ok.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Nikon company gave along with the camera a memory card, charger with rechargeable batteries and a carry pouch. I din't receive the memory card. This is not right. Flipkart didn't bother to solve this. I even checked in the local market. The bundle offer is still available with my local dealer. I will tell you very clearly you have left a bad taste in my mouth.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Rishi Mishra</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">May 5, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">My first Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I was scared at first, as i had never made an investment in cameras before. But i decided to go with the trusted brands of Nikon and Flipkart.Delivery took 3 days and I was fine with that. The Camera came with all essentials - batteries, charger, a pouch, memory card. I used it the very next day on a field trip to Qutb Minar and I was very happy with the picture quality and the ease with which one can use it.Also, the recording feature is excellent. We started shooting when a group of Qawals started singing and it was awesome.I am very satisfied with the product. Thanks
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Anand Chakravarthy</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Sep 17, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Worth the price</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">1. The product is no frills camera, which does what is says2. Has Auto and Easy Auto mode and macro mode also for extreme close up3. Day shots are good but night shots are not upto the mark4. Video recording is good5. It does not have a voice controller during recording.6. Can set photos to be of various sizes eg, 4,8 or16 mp7. Megapixel don't really matter since optical zoom is a very normal 5x8. Main objective is to take photos inside house or in some parties. Dont expect to take fast moving pictures.9. Has a tripod stand and the flash is powerful. Maybe 5-8 feet in dark, images will get captured. 10. Prices vary for camera color, with silver color ones normally the cheapest.11. There is a separate video recording button, which starts immediately on clicking it. No in between pausing of video recording possible. So each time you have to stop and so new file will get created. 12. Has a wifi kind of icon displayed on screen. But has no wifi connectivity. </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Gaurav P</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 2, 2015</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Decent Camera not so good packing by flipkart</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I ordered this camera after reading reviews that its good enough for 4k. Got the product today and its my first digital camera. Pictures look fine and its good enough for the price.However packing by flipkart was below average. No plastic air bags or bubble wrapping was provided. The camera (within Nikon's packing) was stuffed along with other items (case, chargeable batteries). Given the product being electronic goods one would expect better handling from flipkart.As mentioned in the offer i got the case, chargeable batteries + charger and 8GB card.Hope flipkart will not make packing blunders and will provide at least some cushion to electronic goods so a user wont have to face any issues. </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Syam Praveen</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Apr 4, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Beautiful camera within budget</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I ordered this camera for my aunt and received it with excellent packing. If you re looking for a digi camera for beginners then go for it...Excellent product with 16.1 megapixel with which you can click pictures like anything.. Easy adjustable for all conditions and suitable modes. Screen display was also too good!!No doubt .. you can go for it.. 
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Sibi George</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Mar 29, 2015</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Good Camera but a little flimsy</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						It is a nice cute little camera. It is smaller than what we see in this picture. It is very easy to use and pictures are clear. But I felt like it is a little flimsy compared to my old Canon. I think I should not expect more for Rs.3800/- :)WSRetail packaging was NOT up to the mark this time.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Suresh Joshua</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">May 3, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Good Product</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Really Good ProductValue for Money..i like it...i recommended this product who need good camera with low budget
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Sreeraj</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">1</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jun 26, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">not worth..</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Cons:-Lacks features10cm minimum focusing distanceNo optical image stabilisationLow screen resolutionPoor battery life
				</specsKey>
</root>