<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon D5100 (with AF-S 18 - 55 mm VR Kit + Nikon AF-S DX VR Zoom-Nikko DSLR Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">3.667</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 37,290</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB 2.0</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Battery Charger MH-24, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL14, Camera Body, AF-S 18-55mm VR Kit Lens, Audio Video Cable EG-CP14, Eyepiece Cap DK-5, Strap AN-DC3, Body Cap BF-1B, ViewNX 2 CD, Rubber Eyecup DK-20, USB Cable UC-E6, Accessory Shoe Cover BS-1, User Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">D5100 (with AF-S 18 - 55 mm VR Kit + Nikon AF-S DX VR Zoom-Nikko</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Fill-flash, slow sync, auto slow sync, red-eye reduction, auto with red-eye reduction, slow sync with red-eye reduction, auto, slow sync with red-eye reduction, rear-curtain sync, rear-curtain with slow sync.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">APS-C</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16.2 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">Nikon F mount</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">TTL phase detection,11 focus points</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">Approx. 1.5x lens focal length</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Picture Angle">Approx. 1.5x lens focal length</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">3D color matrix metering II</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sync Terminal">1/200 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Continuous shooting mode: Approx. 4fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">ISO 100 to 6400 in steps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Single frame, Continuous: 4fps, Self-timer, Delayed remote, Quick-response remote, Silent shuttle release, D-Movie.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto (TTL white-balance with main image sensor and 420-pixel RGB sensor), Incandescent, Fluorescent ( 7 types ), Direct, Sunlight, Flash, Cloudy, Shade, preset manual.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="HDMI">HDMI output (Type C mini-pin connector)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">22</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4928 x 3264 (L)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Single frame, Continuous: 4fps, Self-timer, Delayed remote, Quick-response remote, Silent shuttle release, D-Movie.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">NEF (12 or 14-bit lossless compressed or compressed RAW), JPEG (Baseline-compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">MOV movie (H.264, MPEG-4 AVC compression format with Linear PCM sound; Stereo sound with external microphone)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Power Supply">EH-5a AC Adapter</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">509 g</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">128 (W) x 96.9 (H) x 78.7 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body & lens.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Viewfinder">Eye-level pentamirror</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ViewFinder">Eye-level pentamirror</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/g/2/u/nikon-d5100-with-af-s-18-55-mm-vr-kit-nikon-af-s-dx-vr-zoom-400x400-imadte3cjxhfffzg.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Chetan Hansdah</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Aug 13, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Best one for starters</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">my dad gifted it to me last year..i have learnt a lot from it in the past year..the image quality is fantastic..u can take NEFs and then process it according to ur choice.there are different modes for one to select from..child, landscape, portrait, monochrome, M S P A..u can also vary the ISO from 100 to 6400..AF MF VR.white balance.different flash modes u can take miniatures, selective colouring, long exposures, bokeh..night photography using high ISO..just love this camera.recently i bought a NIKKOR 50-300 mm zoom lens and its performance is very goodfor newcomers this is the best camera</specsKey>
</root>