<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix S9200 Point & Shoot Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Black,Silver</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">3.944</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 17,950</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/2000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">4.5 - 81.0 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 25 - 450 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">18x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">209 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">108.7 (W) x 59.8 (H) x 30.6 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc. less</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">Wide Viewing Angle TFT LCD Monitor with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Aspect Ratio">16:09</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Camera Strap, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL12 (with Terminal Cover), Charging AC Adapter EH-69P, USB Cable UC-E6, Audio Video Cable EG-CP16, ViewNX 2 Installer CD, Reference Manual CD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">S9200</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Range">0.5 - 5.1 m (W), 1.5 - 3.0 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F3.5 - F5.9</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 6.9 fps (Continuous H), 2 fps up to 6 Images (Continuous L)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">Auto, 125, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200 (Auto gain from ISO 125 - 1600), Fixed Range Auto (ISO 125 - 400, 125 - 800)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Portrait, Close-up, Landscape, Food, Sports, Museum, Night Portrait, Fireworks Show, Party / Indoor, Black and White Copy, Beach, Easy Panorama, Snow, Pet Portrait, Sunset, 3D Photography, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Backlighting), Smart Portrait, Continuous Shooting, Special Effects</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Picture Angle">25 mm Wde-angle to 450 mm Super-telephoto Coverage</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">Yes, 4 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="HDMI">HDMI Mini Connector (Type C)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">256-segment Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">29</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4608 x 3456 (16 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Portrait, Close-up, Landscape, Food, Sports, Museum, Night Portrait, Fireworks Show, Party / Indoor, Black and White Copy, Beach, Easy Panorama, Snow, Pet Portrait, Sunset, 3D Photography, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Backlighting), Smart Portrait, Continuous Shooting, Special Effects</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG (3D), EXIF 2.3, DCF, DPOF, MPF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">WAV, AAC Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">MOV, H.264, MPEG-4 AVC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Power Supply">AC Adapter EH-69P</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">25 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/v/h/y/nikon-coolpix-s9200-point-shoot-400x400-imad72u5smqutkef.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/v/h/y/nikon-coolpix-s9200-point-shoot-400x400-imad72u5tvhgfhyp.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/v/h/y/nikon-coolpix-s9200-point-shoot-400x400-imad72u5mgwthbqn.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/v/h/y/nikon-coolpix-s9200-point-shoot-400x400-imad72u5ah5fzpeg.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">sethupathy</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">3</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 14, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						pic quality very nice n video quality awesome,,, but there s an another factor which should be considered while buyi high priced battery.1. it can take oly 45 mins to discharge HD (1080p).. bt it takes more than 3 hours 2 fully charged..2.can take oly 200 snaps,,, conslu: if u r an taki photos very rarely its very super, u r average user u must have an laptop 2 charge it.. so before buyi tis jst think n decide folks
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Dipu R</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Mar 11, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Good Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I like this camera very much.Picture Quality:Picture quality is awesome while shooting outside.But inside room with flash may give you blurred image.Its zoom is awesome, but you need to use tripod or fix it somewhere to get the good quality picture while zooming.Battery:Battery usage is average, i took around 400 picture for the whole day and still it stand.The camera look is good and its very compact, it will fit on your pocket even with the cover. I am using 8 GB class 10 memory so i get good speed for taking the next picture
</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">kunal goswami</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jun 8, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">high and easy function.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Affordable price, good picture quality, light weight, easy to carry. good and style model. expandable memory can be used upto 32 giga byte. Battery is lithium one. having rechargable concept. so, no need to purchase extra items for battery only.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Siddique ahmad khan</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">2</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 27, 2015</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Battery Problem</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I like this camera due to only quite good of  pic & video qualityBut main problem in this camera is battery prblmeven in case f full charge it can took hardly 150/160 picOr if u keep on video mode it will close with in 1/2 hour.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Akshay Dalal</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jul 14, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">BEST CAMERA EVER!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						don't think too much about it just buy it... I purchased it with 16K but still m happy cos of coolpix. The real essence of natural colours u can capture n see in this camera only...n nikkon is one of the leading brand in cameras rather than sony, fusifilm, samsung n all.....
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Shubham Gathwal</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Mar 29, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">mind boggling</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						the camera quality is amazing infact the best i have ever seen in any camera.I suggest u to buy nikon cameras coz they are jst best at itAfter all they are the leaders man!!!and moreover the quality of videos are just fantastic and the battery backup is pretty fine.
</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Karthika</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 28, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Awesome Camera:):):)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						First of all just wanted to Thank Flipkart for delivering this camera in just one day!! Hats off for this. The camera is too good it has got beautiful features, the zoom is incredible. The clarity of the pics are also amazing.Thanks once again Flipkart!
</specsKey>
</root>