<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix S4300 Point & Shoot Camera (Purple)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Purple</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.385</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 6,360</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/2000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">4 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">4.6 - 27.6 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 26 - 156 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">6x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">139 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">95.5 (W) x 58.9 (H) x 20.8 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc. less</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">TFT LCD Touch Panel with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">460,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Viewfinder">Yes, Optical Zoom</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Aspect Ratio">16:09</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ViewFinder">Yes, Optical Zoom</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL19 (with Battery Case), Reference Manual CD, Camera Strap, Charging AC Adapter EH-62G, USB Cable UC-E6, Audio Video Cable EG-CP14, Stylus TP-1, ViewNX 2 Installer CD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">S4300</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Purple</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Fill-in, Slow Sync, Auto, Flash Off</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Range">0.5 - 4.5 m (W), 0.5 - 2.4 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F3.5 - F6.5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 1.3 fps up to 6 Images</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">ISO 80, 100, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200, Auto: (Auto Gain ISO 80 - 1600), Fixed Range Auto: ISO 80 - 400, 80 - 800</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto, Cloudy, Daylight, Flash, Fluorescent, Incandescent, Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Picture Angle">26 mm Wide-angle</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night portrait, Party, Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk, Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks show, Black and White Copy, Draw, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Special Effects, Smart Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">Yes, 4 cm (Wide-angle Position)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">27</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">256-segment Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4608 x 3456 (16 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night portrait, Party, Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk, Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks show, Black and White Copy, Draw, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Special Effects, Smart Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG, DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">WAV</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">AVI (Motion-JPEG)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Power Supply">AC Adapter EH-69P</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Operating System">Windows 98 SE, Windows XP, Windows 2000, Windows ME, Apple MAC OS 9.2, Apple MAC OS 9, Apple MAC OS X 10.1, Apple MAC OS X 10.2, Apple MAC OS X 10.3, Apple MAC OS X 10.4, Apple MAC OS X 10.5, Apple MAC OS X 10.6, Apple MAC OS X 10.7</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">74 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/c/6/z/nikon-s4300-400x400-imad92rafrxvexm9.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/c/6/z/nikon-s4300-400x400-imad92raxwr6atzt.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/c/6/z/nikon-s4300-400x400-imad92rachawwfdf.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/c/6/z/nikon-s4300-400x400-imad92rbnpthtrwz.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/c/6/z/nikon-s4300-400x400-imad92rbezzbfbh5.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="subimg">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/c/6/z/nikon-s4300-400x400-imad92rafrxvexm9.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img_id">Nikon Coolpix S4300 Point & Shoot Camera (Purple)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Shreyas Bhat</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 16, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Good Camera!!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						This is good product and its CCD Image sensing is good!! There is no problem of red eye. Touch is good!! Scenaries appear very nice & cool!! Even you can have a more zoom in auto   mode. There are lot of options in scene mode. U can edit your images, but not much options are available!! 
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">SYED AKRAMA</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Sep 3, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Great Buy - Better than Canon and other brands.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">This time flipkart took 15 days for delivering this product.On an overall consideration this is a great buy for those who are looking for a new camera with enhanced features.The S4300's body is just 20.8mm deep, meaning you can easily carry it around in your pocket when out and about. There is a 16 megapixel CCD sensor and the 6x optical zoom lens is a 35mm equivalent of 26-156mm. To help counteract camera shake, the S4300 has Lens shift VR (vibration reduction).Auto mode changes the camera settings automatically depending on the scene. Other shooting modes include 19 scenes and smart portrait system with smile timer, blink proof, skin softening and red-eye fix. The camera has subject tracking AF and can also be focused by pressing on the 3 inch LCD touch screen, when the shutter will also be released.Images can be edited after shooting via the retouch menu, which has a range of filter effects. The S4300 shoots videos at 720pSo,All in all it is a nice product and the best feature is that its TOUCH SCREEN</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">rs ft</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jul 27, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Awesome!!!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Very quick delievery  by flipkart and when I used this I found it great n I will suggest u all to go for it if your budget doesn't allows more
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Praveen kumar</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Mar 31, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Good one from Nikkon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Well this camera is perfect for home use, with awesome picture and video quality, it can record hd video, you can use this one for moving object too, 
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Kunal</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 29, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nice product </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Ordered two of them for gifting, so dint opened box packing on receiving.  But later came to know only one had 4 GB free card. In other one it was missing.  Not sure 4 GB free offer was valid on both or not as I have selected both of different color. 
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Lawrence Zacharias</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">3</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 8, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Ok camera for the price</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Not a bad deal at all. But, you cannot expect too much from this as it seems to have a lot of flaws. The pricing was great and for someone to simply point and shoot family pictures, this will work well
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">ANIL KUMAR</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jan 4, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Lovely Digicam-Nikon S4300</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I HAVE BOUGHT FIRST TIME NIKON S4300 DIGICAM FROM FLIPKART AND I AM HAPPY WITH SERVICE AND PRODUCT. LITTLE UNHAPPY DELIVERY OF THE PRODUCT AS I HAVE PLACED ORDER ON 23-DEC.2013 AND I GOT IT ON 31ST. DECEMBER 2013 WHICH IS TOO LATE.PICTURE QUALITY IS GOOD BUT TOUCH SCREEN IS LITTLE UPSET OVERALL IF YOU ARE NEW OR LESS USER OF POINT & SHOOT SO IT IS GOOD PRODUCT AND MUST BUY IT.I AM HAPPY WITH THIS CAMERA AND SERVICE PROVIDED BY FLIPKART. THANKS FLIPFKART. ANIL KUMAR / DELHI
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Stamm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 2, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">legit phone! </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						very promising camera. worth the price and features. the touch screen quality is good; so are the zoom and scene options (quite a few to choose from). offer is decent too ie. parker pen, etc etc. i just wish it had a location for the stylus; no option to hang the stylus onto the camera. so can't lose it! and my suggestion is you buy a screen guard for the screen--its very sensitive to nails so could get damaged....nonetheless awesome camera go for it! 
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">KaranMehra</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 27, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Awesum Product!!!!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						This product is awesum!!!..i bought dis camera yesterday only:) .d touch is quite gud and 6X optical zoom is decent  ,even d screen is quite wider as compared to other cameras at dis price range..all i can say is grab it!!!  
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">debika sadhukhan</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 19, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">awesome picture quality</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						picture quality is amazing.good camera at good price.better than sony, canon, & fujiama cameras which costs nearer Rs. 7000. a must buy camera. you can edit and cartoonify your photo in this camera too. auto flash works wonderfully.
				</specsKey>
</root>