<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon D800 DSLR Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.75</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 169,449</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Microphone">Built-in Monaural</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Super Speed USB 3.0</specsKey>
<specsKey name="PictBridge">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio Output</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/8000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">D800</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">EN-EL15 rechargeable Li-ion battery with terminal cover, USB cable clip, UC-E14 USB cable, BF-1B body cap, BM-12 monitor cover, MH-25 battery charger (AC wall adapter supplied only in countries or regions where required), Strap (AN-DC6 for D800, AN-DC6E for D800E), ViewNX 2 installer CD, BS-1 accessory shoe cover</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Front Curtain Sync, Slow Sync, Rear-curtain Sync, Red-eye Reduction, Red-eye Reduction with Slow Sync, Slow Rear-curtain Sync, Auto FP High-Speed Sync Supported</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Range">12 m</specsKey>
<specsKey name="External Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">Full Frame</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sync Terminal">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 1-4 fps (Continuous Low-speed Mode), 4 fps (Continuous high-speed)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">"ISO 100 - 6400, Low-1 (ISO 50), Hi-1 (ISO 12800), Hi-2 (ISO 25600)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dust Reduction">Image Sensor Cleaning, Image Dust Off Reference Data</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto, Incandescent, Fluorescent, Direct Sunlight, Flash, Cloudy, Shade, Preset Manual can be stored), Color Temperature (2500 K - 10000 K), All with Fine-tuning</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="HDMI">Type C Mini HDMI</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">TTL Exposure Metering</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">23</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Additional Features">Nikon F Lens Mount, Picture Control System: Standard, Neutral, Vivid, Monochrome, Portrait, Landscape, Dual Card Slots, viewfinder Frame Coverage: FX (36 x 24): 100 % Horizontal and 100 % Vertical, 1.2x (30 x 20): 97 % Horizontal and 97 % Vertical, DX (24 x 16): 97 % Horizontal and 97 % Vertical, 5:4 (30 x 24): 97 % Horizontal and 97 % Vertical, 0.7 x Viewfinder Magnification, 17 mm Eyepoint, -3 - m Diopter Adjustment, Focusing Screen: Type B BriteView Clear Matte Mark VIII Screen with AF Area Brackets and Framing Grid, Quick Return Reflex Mirror, Depth-of-field Preview, Lens Aperture: Instant Return, Electronically Controlled, Compatible Lenses: AF NIKKOR Lenses (Type G and D Lenses), DX Lenses, AI-P NIKKOR Lenses, X NIKKOR Lenses, Flash Sync Speed: 1/250 secs, Release Mode: Single Frame, Continuous Low Speed, Continuous High Speed, Quiet Shutter-release, Self-timer, Mirror Up, Metering Method: Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot, Range (ISO 100, f/1.4 Lens, 20 C / 68 F): Matrix or Center Weighted Metering: 0-20 EV, Spot Metering: 2-20 EV, Exposure Meter Coupling: Combined CPU and AI, Exposure Mode: Programmed Auto with Flexible Program (P), Shutter-priority Auto (S), Aperture-priority Auto (A), Manual (M), Exposure Compensation: 5 EV in increments of 1/3 EV, 1/2 EV or 1 EV, Exposure Bracketing: 2 - 9 Frames in Steps of 1/3, 1/2, 2/3, or 1 EV, Flash Bracketing: 2 - 9 Frames in Steps of 1/3, 1/2, 2/3, or 1 EV, White Balance Bracketing: 2 - 9 Frames in Steps of 1, 2, or 3, ADL Bracketing, Exposure Lock, Active D-Lighting: Auto, Extra High, High, Normal, Low, or Off, AF-assist Illuminator, Detection Range: -2 - EV (ISO 100, 20 C/68 F), Lens Servo: Autofocus (AF), Single-servo AF (AF-S), Continuous-servo AF (AF-C), Manual Focus (M), 51 or 11 Focus Points, AF-area Mode, Focus Lock, TTL Flash Control, Flash Compensation: -3 - EV in increments of 1/3, 1/2, or 1 EV, Flash-Ready Indicator, ISO 518 Hot-shoe with Sync Accessory Shoe, Nikon Creative Lighting System (CLS), Live View Modes: Live View Photography (Still Images), Movie Live View (Movies), Live View Lens servo: Autofocus (AF), Single-servo AF (AF-S), Full-time Servo AF (AF-F), Manual Focus (M), External Stereo Microphone, Movie Options: Index Marking, Time-lapse Photography, Playback: Full-frame and Thumbnail, (4, 9, or 72 Images) Playback with Playback Zoom, Movie Playback, Photo and / or Movie Slide shows, Highlights, Histogram Display, Auto Image Rotation, Image Comment (up to 36 Characters), Stereo Mini-pin Jack (3.5 mm diameter) Audio Input, Ten-pin Remote Terminal, 1/4 in. (ISO 1222) Tripod Socket, 0 - 40&deg C Operating Temperature, 85 % operating Humidity</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">TTL Phase Detection</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">36.3 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Other Resolution">5520 x 3680 (M), 3680 x 2456 (S)1.2x (30 x 20) Image area: 6144 x 4080 (L), 4608 x 3056 (M), 3072 x 2040 (S)DX (24 x 16) Image area: 4800 x 3200 (L), 3600 x 2400 (M), 2400 x 1600 (S) 5 : 4 (30 x 24) Image Area: 6144 x 4912 (L), 4608 x 3680 (M), 3072 x 2456 (S) FX-format Photographs Taken in Movie Live View: 6720 x 3776 (L), 5040 x 2832 (M), 3360 x 1888 (S) DX-format Photographs in Movie Live View: 4800 x 2704 (L), 3600 x 2024 (M), 2400 x 1352 (S)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">7360 x 4912 (L)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">NEF (RAW), JPEG, NEF (RAW) JPEG, DCF 2.0, DPOF, EXIF 2.3</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">Linear PCM</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">MOV, H.264 / MPEG-4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Power Supply">EH-5b AC Adapter, Requires EP-5B Power Connector (Sold Separately)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">900 g (without Body Cap), 1000 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">146 (W) x 123 (H) x 81.5 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / UHS-I Compliant SDHC / SDXC / Type I Compact Flash (UDMA Compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3.2 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Viewfinder">Yes, Eye-level Pentaprism</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ViewFinder">Yes, Eye-level Pentaprism</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/a/2/b/nikon-d800e-slr-400x400-imad9hse8nywbehp.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/a/2/b/nikon-d800e-slr-400x400-imad9hsewdm9phu6.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/a/2/b/nikon-d800e-slr-400x400-imad9hsewhcpkvzt.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/a/2/b/nikon-d800e-slr-400x400-imad9hsewu8fyudq.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/a/2/b/nikon-d800e-slr-400x400-imad9hsej7egbjcs.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Aditya Mendiratta</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jun 19, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Brilliant Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						This camera has brilliant features for the price it has to offer. The high ISO is phenomenal and gives way less noise at 6400 as well. I have tested this camera in extreme low light conditions and was satisfied with it.The 45degree curve towards its shutter gives you a good grip while shooting. Nikon did remove some buttons from its previous release the D700 but the new buttons are for the good only.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Amit Kumar Meena</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jul 2, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Excellent!! Waah Nikon!!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Simply a marvel from Nikon. Upgraded from D7000 and loving this awesome piece of engineering. Slight green tint on the LCD is indeed there when compared to other camera screens  but not an issue as such.Pros: Resolution is great! Details are fantabulous! very good dynamic range! auto-Focus and Exposure are excellent! Great value for money.Still have to explore the video mode but initial impressions are good.Cons:Still have to find out except the marginal green tint.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Vineet Mundra</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jun 25, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Green tint on LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I have upgraded from D90. Got this camera a few days back. There is definitely a greenish tint in the LCD, especially photos take with flash indoors. I have compared the same photograph in both D90 and D800 and the photo looks much better and natural on D90 screen. However it seems to be an LCD issue and not image issue as the tint in not there when viewed on computer screen. Other than that, things seem fine, although I havent used all the features yet. But remember that if you want to upgrade from an entry level or mid range DSLR, you will feel that the D800 is bigger and heavier and will feel weird carrying it for casual shots. If you pair it with a pro lens like 24-70 f/2.8, then it gets really heavy for casual use. So weigh your needs and decide accordingly. </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Shaju Joseph</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 14, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">The best from Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">This is my 6th DSLR body from Nikon and the best till date. Its not an everyday camera for hobbyists but the perfect main body for Pro users who are making an income through photography. If you are a hobbyist and not planning on any commercial ventures, but crazy about full frame sensors, look for D600 and D610, that will meet all your needs.I rate it as my best because: 1) D4 is too expensive and heavy for long hours of shooting like a wedding or event.2) D800 gives high details and high ISO performance.3) Same batteries as D600 which is my second body.4) Button layout is the best to wish for as I had a D700 before.Cons: A normal SDHC card may struggle if you are shooting in RAW. Best match would be something in the grade of Sandisk Extreme Pro. I use 16 GB cards. Its more practical to have many 16 GB cards than having one or two 32 GB cards. </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">vijay varma</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jun 16, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">awesome cam </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Hi guys Nikon D 800 is out standing camera which can beat canon 5d mark iii .it as excellent sharpness color brightness and very good qualities i enjoy this cam by having candide photography in wedding it has very good low lite sensors ...and more on its has 36.2 megapix  which can used for advertising H d quality pic s Or movies thank u NIKON i love it .
</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">freebird</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Apr 27, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Best camera for non-wildlife photography - as good as a medium format</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">- Excellent make and results.- DO NOT COMPARE IT WITH SLRs : its not meant to be compared with SLRs as its more like a medium format killer than a SLR replacement or a video camera- DO NOT USE FOR VIDEOS - apart from killing the shutter life, the sensor line skipping gives low quality output compared even blackmagic.- PDR curves are the best way to compare with medium formatsBest Points:* Excellent Dynamic Range* ADL works like a charm* Excellent performance with old block lenses - 1.2f 50mm, 85mm 1.8f etc thus making it easy for portraits and low light caputre* Excellent results in low light life / street photographyPS: decided to write the review as I am very happy with the results and tired to answering questions regarding how it stands compared to another company's flagship. The camera has survived 1+ year of dust, sand, high humidity & rain & works well now. Also, the lenses are all high aperture pro lenses, so the results may vary. The results with old prime lenses are the best thing I have seen in sometime.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Prithu De</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 8, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">You get double of your Money</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I am using this Little Beast for the last one-n-half year in almost all types of photography.36.3 Megapixel is a bliss, you get more detail in less money, if you don't want 36.3, there are options to reduce in smaller sizes.It is an all-metal & Japan manufactured body, D600&D610 both are china plastic.The Dynamic Range is something to be desired from an real advanced technology.It has a pop-up flash, not only for dark subjects, but you can command other speed-lights remotely with this.(Mark 2 or 3 can't do this)Some really crazy in-camera shooting menu introduced.Almost similar button locations for easier upgrade from D700.Great smooth ISO for low light (I saw almost similar in Mark 3 but you pay 1Lac more)There is nothing more to write, everything is excellent and awsome with this camera, I am really loving it.Only few things I wanted the company to look after in the next upgrade:Frame speed/Burst should be little better for a top choice camera like this, megapixels are no excuse, people pay for performance.Should have 2 SD slots, as nowadays SD cards are cheaper and versatile.LCD tilt option could help shooters in better thinking and showing.Better weather sealing. One rainy season, and my viewfinder got some hairline internal fungus, My fault, I should have carried silica in my bag while traveling in rain.This D800 coupled with a professional 24-70 f/2.8 lens costs similar to a MarK-3 body only.Giving 5 star because there are only 5.</specsKey>
</root>