<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix S8100 Point & Shoot Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 12,509</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Camera, Camera Strap AN-CP19, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL12, Charging AC Adapter EH-68P, USB Cable UC-E6, Audio Video Cable EG-CP16, View NX 2 CD, User Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">Coolpix S8100</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with red-eye reduction, Off, Fill flash, Slow sync</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">BSI CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">12.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast Detection with Face Priority and Subject Tracking</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">5.4-54.0mm / F3.5-5.6</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 10 fps up to 5 shots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto, Preset manual, Daylight, Incandescent, Fluorescent, Cloudy, Flash</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto Mode, Scene mode, Scene Auto Selelctor, Night Landscape, Night Portrait, Backlight, Subject tracklight, Auto continous shooting. Using mode dial</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">24</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">10x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">4000 X 3000</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto Mode, Scene mode, Scene Auto Selelctor, Night Landscape, Night Portrait, Backlight, Subject tracklight, Auto continous shooting. Using mode dial</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">MOV Movie</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">184 g</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">104.0 (W) x 59.2 (H) x 29.9 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/y/y/4/nikon-coolpix-s8100-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqar9nxhz29.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/y/y/4/nikon-coolpix-s8100-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqhdwgzg9en.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/y/y/4/nikon-coolpix-s8100-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq43xgrgjgk.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/y/y/4/nikon-coolpix-s8100-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqrfdezyt7z.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/y/y/4/nikon-coolpix-s8100-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqdsaezppev.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="subimg">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/y/y/4/nikon-coolpix-s8100-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqar9nxhz29.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img_id">Nikon Coolpix S8100 Point & Shoot Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">vikram singh</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 17, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Great Price to Feature Ratio Camera.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">.........This is just great camera in its class.......Pros-great macro shooting 1cm (best in class).-good low light sensivity with back-light cmos sensor.-great video quality 1080p @30fps   High speed 240fps video.-good 10X optical zoom with optical stabilization with optic sensor shift.-High resolution 921000 dot screen for g8 visibility in every lighting condition.-fastest shutter speed upto 1/4000 of a sec(best in class).-High speed burst mode with upto 10fps (best in class).cons-Not much manual control (though not needed if you can get g8 pics without it).-30mm wide angle lens (its ok as you can always crop them to make them look lyk wide)..............So guys lots of  ive with minute -ive.............And special thanks to flipkart guys for there g8 service, right now you guys are light year ahead of your Competitors. Keep continuing the good work...THUMBS UP:)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Abhishek Bhardwaj</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jul 10, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Bargain!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						At 11500 Rs. this camera is at a good bargain. The camera isn't in production right now but it is a very good product. I bought it several months ago when it was going to be out of production. Awesome device must say. DSLR rivaling picture taking quality. 
				</specsKey>
</root>