<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon D3100 (Red)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Black,Red</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.604</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 27,499</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">D3100</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Red</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/z/y/f/nikon-d3100-slr-400x400-imad2ugdjybzxfzq.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/z/y/f/nikon-d3100-slr-400x400-imad2wnypucvbjzy.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/z/y/f/nikon-d3100-slr-400x400-imad2wnyepswpe8h.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/z/y/f/nikon-d3100-slr-400x400-imad2wzbtfuxzvk3.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Manav Saxena</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Jul 17, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nikon D3100 best in its class</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">Great quality of the best camera brand i'll rate it 9/10........The D3100 DSLR comes with an AF-S 18-55 mm lens that is fitted on a Nikon F Bayonet mount. This DSLR is compatible with several NIKKOR lenses, thus giving you an opportunity to experiment with several types of lenses. The aperture of this Nikon DSLR ranges from f/3.5 - 5.6, while the shutter speed has a wide range of 1/4000 - 30 seconds. The shutter of the D3100 is an electronically controlled vertical-travel focal plane shutter, and also has a Bulb setting to help you take brighter images even in dim light scenarios.The camera has a 3x optical zoom, which you can increase by interchanging this lens with another zoom lens. The Nikon D3100 has 11 point auto focus module that promises razor sharp focus and the 3D tracking gives you clearly focused images of a subject in motion.The light sensitivity of a DSLR reduces the risk of blurry images when taking pictures at faster shutter speeds or dark situations. The Nikon D3100 has a wide ISO range of ISO 100 - 3200 sensitivity which can be boosted up to ISO 12800. You can further brighten your composition by using the built-in pop up flash and the hot shoe for an attaching an external flash. Nikon D3100 is an entry-level DX-format camera, ideal for photographers preparing to refine their skills in DSLR cameras. This camera has a CMOS image sensor of dimensions 23.1 x 15.4 mm, which enables you to capture fabulous images at 14.2 megapixels. The swift EXPEED 2 processing engine of this digital SLR supports an aspect ratio of 3:2. You can record your memories and shoot full HD movies on the Nikon D3100 at 1920 x 1080 resolution (24 fps).</specsKey>
</root>