<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix P100 Point & Shoot Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">4.571</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 19,019</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">Coolpix P100</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Camera, Camera Strap AN-CP21, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL5, Charging AC Adapter EH-68P, USB Cable UC-E6, Audio Video Cable EG-CP14, Software Suite CD-ROM, Lens Cap LC-CP21, User Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with red-eye reduction, Off, Fill flash, Slow sync, Rear-curtain sync</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 10 fps up to 6 shots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">Auto, 80, 100, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto Mode, Scene mode, Scene Auto Selelctor, Smart portrait mode, Sport continuous mode, Movie mode, Subject tracking mode, P, S, A, and M exposure modes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto, Preset manual, Daylight, Incandescent, Fluorescent, Cloudy, Flash</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">24</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">Nikkor lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">4.6-120.0mm / F2.8-5.0</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">10.3 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto Mode, Scene mode, Scene Auto Selelctor, Smart portrait mode, Sport continuous mode, Movie mode, Subject tracking mode, P, S, A, and M exposure modes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">mono/wav file, MOV movie</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">26x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">481 g</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">114.4 (W) x 82.7 (H) x 98.6 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">460000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Viewfinder">No</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ViewFinder">No</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/g/j/6/nikon-coolpix-p100-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq7jhefxhzp.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/g/j/6/nikon-coolpix-p100-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq3ehcfcthv.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/g/j/6/nikon-coolpix-p100-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqbuwwyzk55.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/g/j/6/nikon-coolpix-p100-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq9hyyjcecs.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/g/j/6/nikon-coolpix-p100-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqf964hhgmn.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/g/j/6/nikon-coolpix-p100-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq3ytkgehp9.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="subimg">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/g/j/6/nikon-coolpix-p100-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq7jhefxhzp.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img_id">Nikon Coolpix P100 Point & Shoot Camera (Black)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Lalatendu Mohanty</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Sep 5, 2011</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Excellent point and shoot camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I have been using it from last 6 months and I am still happy about my decision to buy it. Go for it if you want a point and shoot camera with high optical zoom
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Piyush Baijal</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 13, 2014</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nikon Coolpix P100</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Initially I was confused between Nikon Coolpix P100 and Canon SX160. After much research, opted for Nikon Coolpix P100. Before I could bought it from flipkart (which at time was in stock and had price Rs. 9999), it went out of stock. To my surprise, all other online shopping sites are asking 18000 to 20000 for Nikon Coolpix P100. :o Is this flipkart too generous or other are looting us?
				</specsKey>
</root>