<root>
<specsKey name="id">Nikon Coolpix S30 Point & Shoot Camera (Pink)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="color_list">Pink</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ratingValue">3.733</specsKey>
<specsKey name="price">Rs. 4,740</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/2000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Minimum Shutter Speed">4 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">10.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Focal Length">4.1 - 12.3 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 29.1 - 87.3 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Optical Zoom">3x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Weight">214 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Dimensions">101.9 (W) x 64.8 (H) x 39.4 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Display Resolution">1280 x 720, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey name="LCD Screen Size">2.7 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Aspect Ratio">4:3, 16:9</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Microphone">Mono</specsKey>
<specsKey name="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sales Package">Brush, ViewNX 2 Installer CD, Camera Strap, Reference Manual CD, USB Cable UC-E16, LR6/L40 (AA-size) alkaline batteries (x2)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Model ID">S30</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Color">Pink</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Flash Modes">Auto, On, Off, Red-Eye, Slow-sync</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Size">1/3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Aperture Range">F3.3 - F5.9</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Continuous Shots">Yes, 1.5 fps up to 4 Shots</specsKey>
<specsKey name="ISO Rating">Auto, 80 - 1600 (Auto Gain ISO 80 - 1600)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Choose a Style (Point and Shoot, Shoot Close-ups, Shoot Under Water, Take a Series of Pictures, Shoot at Intervals, Photograph Food, Highlight Colors, Take Soft Pictures, Create a Diorama Effect, Photograph Fireworks)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="White Balancing">Auto, Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Self Timer">Yes, 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Macro Mode">Yes, 5 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Metering">256-segment Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Supported Languages">27</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Sizing">3648 x 2736 (10 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Shooting Modes">Auto, Choose a Style (Point and Shoot, Shoot Close-ups, Shoot Under Water, Take a Series of Pictures, Shoot at Intervals, Photograph Food, Highlight Colors, Take Soft Pictures, Create a Diorama Effect, Photograph Fireworks)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Image Format">JPEG, EXIF 2.3, DCF, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Audio Formats">WAV</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Video Format">AVI (Motion-JPEG)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Battery Type">AA Alkaline Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey name="Inbuilt Memory">47 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/z/2/a/nikon-s30-400x400-imad93ysqzsdrrq9.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/z/2/a/nikon-s30-400x400-imad93ysxdccfqfm.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/z/2/a/nikon-s30-400x400-imad93ysssuhgtwp.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/z/2/a/nikon-s30-400x400-imad93ytxzzzywxh.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/z/2/a/nikon-s30-400x400-imad93ytytbzaur8.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/z/2/a/nikon-s30-400x400-imad93ytw6wwhfzz.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="subimg">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/z/2/a/nikon-s30-400x400-imad93ysqzsdrrq9.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey name="img_id">Nikon Coolpix S30 Point & Shoot Camera (Pink)</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Rohit  Reddy</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Dec 21, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Ok for regular home use, photo clarity not as expected</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I got this camera for as a gift for my dad and using at home, and since its waterproof, it appeal to me as worth buying. But after a few days using it, I felt that though its water and everything else, it wasn't worth a buy for me (I'm used to DLSRs), as photo clarity and colors tones are not very good and button are hard to press.Overall, its a ok-ok camera for beginners and people whose taste in photography is developing, but I wouldn't recommend it for people who are slightly keen on photography.
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Ravi</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Sep 26, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Waterproof camera for creativity</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						I have been using SLR for many years . But do not compare the image quality of SLR or even your point and shoot. But what requires is ur creativity. If your kid is using you can forget about as it is strong and water proof. You need to have lot of spare AA battery to use it. But other wise cheap camera for your under water photography 
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">JayKay</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 16, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Nice camera for kids</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">This camera came with pouch, 4GB (series 4) card, 2 AA cells, 2AA rechargeable cells and a charger.  Value for money!!!Clarity is good in daylight.  Night shots are grainy, even with the flash.  Haven't tried the underwater feature yet.  One issue I noticed is that its not able to record a message with a picture as given in the camera manual.I bought this camera for my 6 years old daughter.  She is absolutely thrilled with her 'own' camera.  The menus are kid friendly and she learnt to use it within minutes.  Well, she had used a Konika Minolta point-and-shoot for last year and a half which she spoilt after dropping it many times.  Fortunately, Nikon S30 is shock proof and waterproof!  Hopefully, it'll last a kids handling longer than her earlier camera.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Bijoy  V J</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">May 13, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Cool little camera</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">Have been using this for 5 months now. Mostly used by my wife for taking my 2-year old son's snaps/videos. Which means, there is no point in having a high-end camera.Pros1. Handy and easy to use for beginners2. Good build quality. Feels quite strong in your hands3. Shock and water proof - Have not tested it yet!!!4. PriceCons:1. Battery eater! Ships with a pair of rechargeable batteries. Keep a charger and a couple of extra batteries handy if you are planning a trip2. Extremely basic. Hardly anything that you can customize. If you have used a medium-end or high-end camera, reconsider buying this. This might be good only for your little kid.</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Vishal Kulshrestha</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Oct 17, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Good camera for using in water and in daytime, but not otherwise</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						Camera quality is reasonably good, though a bit bulkier than other point and shoots in the price range of 5 to 6K.If you frequent beaches, take photo's during rains and your kids want to handle a camera, then think no more, just buy this one.Digital camera's are not so robust, so I got this one hoping that it will last longer, and it works just fine even when my Kid is using it.It is really bad for night use. Doesn't click on time and causes lot of blurring. I had to purchase a regular digital camera for this.
</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Dina Xete Mossurcar</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Aug 3, 2012</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">awesum buy .. best price for cam for its practicality </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						i bo this cam n i got it in 2 days . n its a best buy cos its less price n u can use its ruff n tuff n its waterproof n dust proof n i got free 4gb n puch its an awesum buy for its price n the features it has .. look no other if u want a cam for RUFF N TUFF USE . IF U DO RIVER CORSSING HIKE N ADVANTURE , N ITS CUM WITH 10MP CAM
				</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">Sanjiv Mahato</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Feb 25, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">Value for money!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">I had searched a dozen shops & for couple of years for water proof camera & it finally ended at flipkart.  I guess there are hardly any camera brands which offer you a water proof feature. I had heard about sony providing a water proof casing, but that costed about 4000 rupees. Also, when I enquired about the same in their showrooms, they probably were not aware or sony had stopped manufacturing the same.  Flipkart was a savior for me! This model apparently is not available with retailors/ shopkeers! I love flipkart for this. As for the camera, this works perfectly fine in water, tried & tested. Maynot produce great pictures as a sony/ canon etc digicam, but then that’s not its usp. True value for money.Must buy for water lovers!    </specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerName">shrikant</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewerRating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewedDate">Nov 4, 2013</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewTitle">no worry camera... take anywhere!!!!</specsKey>
<specsKey name="reviewText">
						its really awesome camera... with some unique feature lik.. water proff..dust proff...shock proff  that make u worry free on ur travel...howevr sum feature are dissapionted lik there is auto flash..there battery run out quickly if ur taking video at 720p hd but some how u can manage with these othr than tat ..its really incredible camera.. at a incredible price.. :)
				</specsKey>
</root>